Senator, we're making
our final approach
into Coruscant.
Very good, Lieutenant.
[ Droid Beeping ]
[ Grunts ]
We made it.
[ Man ]
I guess I was wrong.
There was no danger at all.
Corde.
Milady, I'm so sorry.
I've failed you, Senator.
No.
Milady, you're still
in danger here.
I shouldn't have
come back.
This vote is very important.
You did your duty.
Corde did hers. Now, come.
Senator Amidala, please.
I don't know
how much longer
I can hold off the vote,
my friends.
More and more
star systems are joining
the separatists.
If they do break away--
I will not let
this Republic...
that has stood
for a thousand years
be split in two.
My negotiations
will not fail.
If they do, you must realize
there aren't enough Jedi
to protect the Republic.
We're keepers of the peace,
not soldiers.
Master Yoda.
Do you think
it will really come to war?
Hmm, the dark side
clouds everything.
Impossible to see
the future is.
The Loyalist Committee
has arrived, Your Honor.
[ Speaking Huttese ]
Good.
[ Huttese ]
Send them in.
We will discuss
this matter later.
Senator Amidala,
your tragedy on
the landing platform--
terrible.
Seeing you alive brings
warm feelings to my heart.
Do you have any idea
who was behind this attack?
Our intelligence points
to disgruntled spice miners
on the moons of Naboo.
I think that
Count Dooku was behind it.
He is a political idealist,
not a murderer.
You know, milady,
Count Dooku was once a Jedi.
He couldn't
assassinate anyone.
It's not in his character.
But for certain,
Senator,
in grave danger you are.
Master Jedi,
may I suggest...
the senator be placed...
under the protection
of your graces.
Do you really think
that's a wise decision
under these stressful times?
Chancellor,
if I may comment,
I do not believe--
The situation
is that serious?
No, but I do, Senator.
I realize all too well
that additional security...
might be
disruptive for you,
but perhaps someone
you're familiar with.
An old friend,
like Master Kenobi.
That's possible.
He's just returned
from a border dispute
on Ansion.
Do it for me, milady.
Please?
The thought
of losing you...
is unbearable.
I will have Obi-Wan
report to you immediately,
milady.
[ Senator Amidala ]
Thank you, Master Windu.
You seem a little on edge.
Not at all.
I haven't felt you
this tense...
since we fell
into that nest of gundarks.
[ Scoffs ]
You fell into
that nightmare, Master,
and I rescued you,
remember?
Oh... yes.
[ Laughing ]
[ Chuckles ]
You're sweating. Relax.
Take a deep breath.
I haven't seen her
in ten years, Master.
Obi? Obi!
Mesa so smilen
to seein yousa!
Good to see you again,
Jar Jar.
Senator Padme.
Mesa palos here!
Lookie, lookie, Senator.
Desa Jedi arriven.
It's a great pleasure
to see you again, milady.
It has been far too long,
Master Kenobi.
Ani? My goodness,
you've grown.
So have you.
Grown more beautiful,
I mean.
Well, f-for a senator,
Ani, you'll always be
that little boy I knew
on Tatooine.
Our presence here
will be invisible, milady,
I can assure you.
I'm Captain Typho
of Her Majesty's
security service.
Queen Jamillia
has been informed
of your assignment.
I am grateful you are here,
Master Kenobi.
The situation is
more dangerous than
the senator will admit.
I don't need more security.
I need answers.
I want to know
who's trying to kill me.
We are here
to protect you, Senator,
not to start
an investigation.
We will find out
who's trying
to kill you, Padme.
I promise you.
We will not exceed
our mandate,
my young Padawan learner.
I meant that
in the interest of
protecting her, Master.
We will not go through
this exercise again,
Anakin,
and you will
pay attention to my lead.
Why?
What?
Why else do you think
we were assigned to her
if not to find the killer?
Protection is a job
for local security,
not Jedi.
It's overkill, Master.
Investigation is implied
in our mandate.
We will do
exactly as the council
has instructed.
And you will learn
your place, young one.
Perhaps with merely
your presence...
the mystery surrounding
this threat will be revealed.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I will retire.
I know I'll feel better
having you here.
I'll have an officer
stationed on every floor,
and I'll be in the control
center downstairs.
Mesa busten wit happiness
seein yousa again, Ani.
She hardly even
recognized me, Jar Jar.
I've thought about her
every day since we parted,
and...
she's forgotten me
completely.
Shesa happy.
Happier den mesa seein her
in a longo time.
You're focusing
on the negative, Anakin.
Be mindful
of your thoughts.
She was pleased to see us.
Now, let's check
the security.
I hit the ship,
but they used a decoy.
We'll have to try
something more subtle
this time, Zam.
My client
is getting impatient.
Take these.
Be careful.
They're very poisonous.
Zam, there can be
no mistakes this time.
Captain Typho has
more than enough
men downstairs.
No assassin would
try that way.
Any activity up here?
Quiet as a tomb.
I don't like just
waiting here for something
to happen to her.
[ Beeping ]
What's going on?
Ah, she covered
the cameras.
I don't think
she liked me watching her.
What is she thinking?
She programmed R2
to warn us
if there is an intruder.
[ Obi-Wan ]
There are many other ways
to kill a senator.
[ Anakin ] I know,
but we also want to
catch this assassin,
don't we, Master?
You're using her
as bait.
It was her idea.
Don't worry.
No harm will come to her.
I can sense everything
going on in that room.
Trust me.
It's too risky.
Besides, your senses
aren't that attuned,
my young apprentice.
And yours are?
Possibly.
You look tired.
I don't sleep well
anymore.
Because of your mother?
I don't know why
I keep dreaming about her.
Dreams pass in time.
I'd much rather dream
about Padme.
Just being around her
again is... intoxicating.
Be mindful
of your thoughts, Anakin.
They betray you.
You've made a commitment
to the Jedi order,
a commitment
not easily broken.
And don't forget,
she's a politician,
and they're not
to be trusted.
[ Anakin ]
She's not like the others
in the senate, Master.
[ Obi-Wan ]
It is my experience
that senators...
focus only on pleasing those
who fund their campaigns,
and they're in no means
scared of forgetting
the niceties of democracy...
in order to get those funds.
Not another lecture.
At least not
on the economics
of politics.
[ R2-D2 Beeps ]
[ Beeping ]
And besides,
you're generalizing.
The chancellor doesn't
appear to be corrupt.
Palpatine is a politician.
[ Obi-Wan ]
I have observed
that he is very clever...
in following the passions
and the prejudices
of the senators.
I think he's a good man.
My--
I sense it too.
[ Gasps ]
[ Whirring ]
Stay here!
Are you all right, milady?
Ah!
[ Horn Honking ]
What the--
[ Cursing In Huttese ]
Jedi poo doo!
What took you so long?
Oh, you know, Master.
I couldn't find a speeder
that I really liked,
There he is.
with the open cockpit
and the right
speed capabilities.
If you spent as much time
practicing your
saber techniques
as you do your wit,
you would rival Master Yoda
as a swordsman.
I thought I already did.
Only in your mind,
my very young apprentice.
Pull up, Anakin.
Pull up!
[ Laughing ]
You know I don't like it
when you do that.
Sorry, Master.
I forgot
you don't like flying.
I don't mind flying,
but what you're doing
is suicide.
Anakin! How many times
have I told you-- Ah!--
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
stay away from
power couplings!
That was good!
Where are you going?
He went that way.
Master,
if we keep this chase
going any longer,
that creep is
gonna end up deep-fried,
and, personally,
I'd very much like to
find out who he is
and who he's working for.
This is a shortcut.
I think.
Well, you've lost him.
I'm deeply sorry, Master.
That was some shortcut,
Anakin.
He went completely
the other way.
Once again
you've proved--
If you'll excuse me.
I hate it
when he does that.
[ Grunting ]
[ Engine Accelerating ]
[ Shouting, Grunting ]
[ Onlookers Murmuring ]
Anakin!
She went
into the club, Master.
Patience.
Use the Force. Think.
Sorry, Master.
He went in there to hide,
not to run.
Yes, Master.
Next time,
try not to lose it.
Yes, Master.
This weapon is your life.
I try, Master.
Why do I get the feeling
you're going to be
the death of me?
Don't say that, Master.
You're the closest thing
I have to a father.
Then why don't you
listen to me?
I am trying.
[ Cheering, Shouting ]
Can you see him?
I think he is a she,
and I think
she is a changeling.
In that case,
be extra careful.
Go and find her.
Where are you going, Master?
For a drink.
Thank you.
You wanna buy
some death sticks?
You don't want to
sell me death sticks.
I don't want to
sell you death sticks.
You want to go home...
and rethink your life.
I want to go home
and rethink my life.
[ Patron Shouting In Huttese ]
[ Patrons Laughing ]
[ Cheering ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Patrons Gasping ]
[ Moaning, Grunting ]
Easy. Jedi business.
Go back to your drinks.
[ Groaning ]
Do you know who it was
you were trying to kill?
[ Moans ] It was
a senator from Naboo.
And who hired you?
It was just a job.
Who hired you? Tell us.
Tell us now!
It was a bounty hunter
called-- [ Gagging ]
Wee shahnit... sleemo.
Toxic dart.
[ Yoda ]
Track down this bounty hunter
you must, Obi-Wan.
Most importantly,
find out
who he's working for.
What about
Senator Amidala?
She will still
need protecting.
Handle that
your Padawan will.
Anakin,
escort the senator back
to her home planet of Naboo.
She'll be safer there.
And don't use
registered transport.
Travel as refugees.
As the leader
of the opposition,
it will be very difficult...
to get Senator Amidala
to leave the capital.
Until caught
this killer is,
our judgment
she must respect.
Hmm.
[ Windu ]
Anakin, go to the senate...
and ask Chancellor Palpatine
to speak with her
about this matter.
I will talk with her.
Senator Amidala will not
refuse an executive order.
I know her well enough
to assure you of that.
Thank you,
Your Excellency.
And so, they've finally
given you an assignment.
Your patience has paid off.
Your guidance
more than my patience.
You don't need guidance,
Anakin.
In time, you will learn
to trust your feelings.
Then you will
be invincible.
I have said it many times:
You are the most gifted Jedi
I have ever met.
Thank you,
Your Excellency.
I see you becoming
the greatest of all
the Jedi, Anakin,
even more powerful
than Master Yoda.
I am concerned
for my Padawan.
He is not ready to be
given this assignment
on his own yet.
[ Yoda ]
The council is confident
in its decision, Obi-Wan.
[ Windu ]
The boy has
exceptional skills.
But he still has
much to learn, Master.
His abilities have
made him, well, arrogant.
Yes, yes.
A flaw more and more
common among Jedi.
Hmm.
Too sure of themselves
they are.
Even the older,
more experienced ones.
Remember, Obi-Wan,
if the prophecy is true,
your apprentice is
the only one who can
bring the Force
back into balance.
[ Padme ]
I'm taking an extended
leave of absence.
It will be
your responsibility to take
my place in the senate.
Representative Binks,
I know I can count on you.
Hmm?
Mesa honored
to be taking on
dissa heavy burden.
Mesa accept this
with muy, muy humility
and, uh--
Jar Jar, I don't wish
to hold you up.
I'm sure you have
a great deal to do.
Of course. Milady.
I do not like
this idea of hiding.
Don't worry.
Now that
the council has ordered
an investigation,
it won't take
Master Obi-Wan long
to find this bounty hunter.
I haven't worked for a year
to defeat the Military
Creation Act...
to not be here
when its fate is decided.
Sometimes we must let go
of our pride and do
what is requested of us.
Anakin, you've grown up.
Master Obi-Wan
manages not to see it.
Don't get me wrong.
Obi-Wan is a great mentor.
As wise as
Master Yoda and...
as powerful
as Master Windu.
I am truly thankful
to be his apprentice.
In some ways--
a lot of ways--
I'm really ahead of him.
I'm ready for the trials,
but he feels
that I'm too unpredictable.
He won't let me move on.
That must be frustrating.
It's worse.
He's overly critical.
He never listens.
He-- He doesn't understand.
It's not fair!
All mentors have a way of
seeing more of our faults
than we would like.
It's the only way we grow.
[ Sighs ]
I know.
Anakin.
Don't try to grow up
too fast.
But I am grown up.
You said it yourself.
Please don't look at me
like that.
Why not?
It makes me
feel uncomfortable.
Sorry, milady.
Be safe, milady.
Thank you, Captain.
Take good care of Dorme.
The threat's on you two now.
He'll be safe with me.
You'll be fine.
It's not me, milady.
I worry about you.
What if they realize
you've left the capital?
Well, then my Jedi protector
will have to prove
how good he is.
Anakin.
Don't do anything
without first consulting
either myself or the council.
Yes, Master.
I'll get to
the bottom of this plot
quickly, milady.
You'll be back here
in no time.
I'll be most grateful
for your speed,
Master Jedi.
It's time to go.
I know.
Anakin, may the Force
be with you.
May the Force be
with you, Master.
Suddenly I'm afraid.
This is my first
assignment on my own.
I am too.
Don't worry.
We have R2 with us.
[ Laughing ]
[ Beeping ]
I do hope
he doesn't try
anything foolish.
I'd be more concerned
about her doing something
than him.
Someone to see ya, honey!
Jedi, by the looks of him.
Obi-Wan!
Hello, Dex.
Take a seat.
I'll be right with ya.
You wanna
cup o' jawa juice?
Oh, yes. Thank you.
Hey, old buddy!
[ Both Laughing ]
Ohhh.
[ Coughs ]
So, my friend,
what can I do for ya?
You can tell me
what this is.
Well, whattaya know!
I ain't seen one of these
since I was prospectin'...
on Subterrel,
beyond the outer rim.
[ Obi-Wan ] Can you tell me
where it came from?
Thank you.
[ Dex ]
This baby belongs
to them cloners.
What you got here
is a Kamino saberdart.
I wonder why
it didn't show up
in the analysis archives.
It's these funny
little cuts on the side
that give it away.
Those analysis droids
only focus on symbols. Huh!
I should think that
you Jedi would have
more respect...
for the difference
between knowledge and...
[ Laughing ]
wisdom.
Well, if droids could think,
there'd be none of us here,
would there?
Kamino.
I'm not familiar with it.
Is it in the Republic?
No, no.
It's beyond the outer rim.
I'd say about,
uh, 12 parsecs...
outside the Rishi Maze.
Should be easy to find,
even for those droids
in your archives.
[ Chuckles ]
These, uh, Kaminoans
keep to themselves.
They're cloners.
Damn good ones too.
Cloners. Are they friendly?
Oh, depends.
Depends on what, Dex?
On how good
your manners are...
and how big your, uh,
pocketbook is.
[ Chuckling ]
Hmm.
Did you call for assistance?
Yes, yes, I did.
Are you having a problem,
Master Kenobi?
Yes, um, I'm looking
for a planetary system
called Kamino.
Kamino.
It doesn't show up
on the archive charts.
Kamino.
It's not a system
I'm familiar with.
Are you sure you have
the right coordinates?
According to my information,
it should appear
in this quadrant here,
just south of
the Rishi Maze.
[ Beeping ]
I hate to say it,
but it looks like the system
you're searching for...
doesn't exist.
Impossible.
Perhaps the archives
are incomplete.
If an item does not appear
in our records,
it does not exist.
Hey, you! No droids!
[ Beeping ]
Get outta here!
[ Raspberries ]
[ Beeping ]
Thank you, R2.
[ Chirping ]
Must be difficult, having
sworn your life to the Jedi,
not being able
to visit the places you like
or do the things you like.
Or be with the people
that I love.
Are you allowed to love?
I thought that was
forbidden for a Jedi.
Attachment is forbidden.
Possession is forbidden.
Compassion,
which I would define
as unconditional love,
is central
to a Jedi's life.
So you might say
that we are encouraged
to love.
You've changed so much.
Ah, you haven't
changed a bit.
You're exactly the way
I remember you in my dreams.
[ Yoda ]
Reach out.
Sense the Force around you.
Use your feelings
you must.
Younglings.
Younglings!
A visitor we have.
[ Together ]
Hello, Master Obi-Wan.
Hello.
I'm sorry to disturb you,
Master.
What help can I be,
Obi-Wan? Hmm?
I'm looking for a planet
described to me
by an old friend.
I trust him,
but the systems don't show
on the archive maps.
Mmm. Lost a planet
Master Obi-Wan has.
How embarrassing.
[ Children Giggling ]
Hmm? Liam, the shades.
Gather round
the map reader.
Clear your minds...
and find Obi-Wan's
wayward planet we will.
It ought to be... here,
but it isn't.
Gravity is pulling
all the stars in the area
towards this spot.
Hmm. Gravity's silhouette
remains,
but the star
and all the planets,
disappeared they have.
How can this be?
Hmm? A thought?
[ Yoda ]
Anyone.
[ Boy ] Master?
Because someone erased it
from the archive memory.
[ Yoda Chuckles ]
Truly wonderful
the mind of a child is.
[ Chuckling ]
The Padawan is right.
Go to the center
of gravity's pull...
and find your planet
you will.
Hmm. The data
must have been erased.
But, Master Yoda,
who could empty information
from the archives?
That's impossible,
isn't it?
Dangerous and disturbing
this puzzle is.
Only a Jedi could have
erased those files.
But who and why,
harder to answer.
Meditate on this I will.
Hmm.
I wasn't the youngest queen
ever elected,
but now that I think
back on it, I'm not sure
I was old enough.
I'm not sure
I was ready.
The people you served
thought you did a good job.
I heard they even tried to
amend the constitution
so you could stay in office.
I was relieved
when my two terms were up.
But when the queen
asked me to serve
as senator,
I couldn't refuse her.
I agree with her.
I think the Republic
needs you.
I'm glad that
you chose to serve.
[ Padme ]
If the senate votes
to create an army,
I'm sure it's going
to push us into a civil war.
[ Man ] It's unthinkable.
There hasn't been
a full-scale war
since the formation
of the Republic.
Do you see any way
through negotiations...
to bring the separatists
back into the Republic?
Not if they
feel threatened.
My guess is they'll turn
to the Trade Federations
or the Commerce Guilds
for help.
It's outrageous,
but after four trials
in the Supreme Court,
Nute Gunray
is still the viceroy
of the Trade Federation.
I fear the senate is
powerless to resolve
this crisis.
We must keep our faith
in the Republic.
The day we stop believing
democracy can work
is the day we lose it.
Let's pray
that day never comes.
In the meantime,
we must consider
your own safety.
What is your suggestion,
Master Jedi?
Oh, Anakin's
not a Jedi yet.
He's still
a Padawan learner.
But I was thinking--
Hold on a minute.
Excuse me.
I was thinking I would stay
in the lake country.
There are
some places up there
that are very isolated.
Excuse me.
I'm in charge of
security here, milady.
And this is my home.
I know it very well.
That is why we're here.
I think it would be wise
if you took advantage of
my knowledge in this instance.
Sorry, milady.
[ Queen Jamillia ]
Perfect.
It's settled, then.
There it is, R4,
right where it should be.
Our missing planet Kamino.
[ Whistling, Beeping ]
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
Master Jedi.
The prime minister
is expecting you.
I'm expected?
Of course.
He is anxious to meet you.
After all these years,
we were beginning to think
you weren't coming.
Now, please, this way.
May I present Lama Su,
prime minister of Kamino.
And this is Master Jedi--
Obi-Wan Kenobi.
I trust you're going to
enjoy your stay.
Please.
And now to business.
You will be delighted
to hear that we are
on schedule.
200,000 units are ready,
with a million more
well on the way.
That's good news.
Please tell
your Master Sifo-Dyas...
that his order
will be met on time.
I'm sorry. Master--
Jedi Master Sifo-Dyas
is still a leading member
of the Jedi Council,
is he not?
Master Sifo-Dyas
was killed
almost ten years ago.
Oh, I'm so sorry
to hear that.
But I'm sure he would have
been proud of the army
we've built for him.
The army?
Yes.
A clone army, and I must say,
one of the finest
we've ever created.
Tell me, Prime Minister,
when my master first
contacted you
about the army,
did-- did he say
who it was for?
Of course he did.
This army
is for the Republic.
But you must be anxious
to inspect the units
for yourself.
That's why I'm here.
We used to come here
for school retreat.
We would swim to
that island every day.
I love the water.
We used to lie out
on the sand
and let the sun dry us...
and try to guess
the names
of the birds singing.
I don't like sand.
It's coarse and rough
and irritating,
and it gets everywhere.
Not like here.
Here, everything is soft...
and smooth.
No.
[ Gasps ]
I shouldn't have done that.
I'm sorry.
Very impressive.
I'd hoped
you would be pleased.
[ Lama Su ] Clones can
think creatively.
You will find that
they are immensely
superior to droids.
We take great pride
in our combat education
and training programs.
This group was created
about five years ago.
[ Obi-Wan ]
You mentioned
growth acceleration.
[ Lama Su ]
Oh, yes, it's essential.
Otherwise,
a mature clone would take
a lifetime to grow.
Now we can do it
in half the time.
[ Obi-Wan ]
I see.
[ Lama Su ]
They are totally obedient,
taking any order
without question.
We modified
their genetic structure...
to make them
less independent
than the original host.
And who was
the original host?
A bounty hunter
called Jango Fett.
And where is
this bounty hunter now?
Oh, we keep him here.
[ Lama Su ]
Apart from his pay,
which is considerable,
Fett demanded
only one thing:
an unaltered clone
for himself.
Curious, isn't it?
"Unaltered"?
[ Lama Su ]
Pure genetic replication.
No tampering
with the structure
to make it more docile...
and no growth acceleration.
I should very much
like to meet
this Jango Fett.
I would be very happy
to arrange it for you.
Magnificent, aren't they?
I don't know.
[ Chuckles ]
Sure you do.
You just don't
want to tell me.
You gonna use one of your
Jedi mind tricks on me?
They only work
on the weak-minded.
All right. I was 12.
His name was Palo.
We were both
in the Legislative
Youth Program.
He was a few years
older than I.
Very cute.
Dark, curly hair.
Dreamy eyes.
All right,
I get the picture.
Whatever happened to him?
I went into public service;
he went on to become
an artist.
Maybe he was the smart one.
You really don't like
politicians, do you?
I like two or three,
but I'm not really sure
about one of them.
[ Both Chuckle ]
I don't think
the system works.
How would you
have it work?
We need a system
where the politicians
sit down
and discuss the problem,
agree what's in the best
interest of all the people,
and then do it.
That's exactly what we do.
The trouble is that people
don't always agree.
Well, then
they should be made to.
By whom?
Who's gonna make them? You?
I don't know. Someone.
Of course not me.
But someone.
Someone wise.
Sounds an awful lot
like a dictatorship to me.
Well, if it works.
You're making fun of me.
No.
I'd be much too frightened
to tease a senator.
[ Creature Bellowing ]
[ Anakin ]
Whoa, whoa!
[ Laughing ]
[ Bellowing ]
Oh, whoa!
[ Grunting ]
[ Lowing ]
[ Grunts, Groans ]
Ani!
Ani, are you all right?
[ Laughing ]
[ Both Laughing ]
[ Beeping ]
Boba, is your father here?
Yep.
May we see him?
Sure.
Dad, Taun We's here.
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
Jango, welcome back.
Was your trip productive?
Fairly.
This is Jedi Master
Obi-Wan Kenobi.
He's come to check
on our progress.
Your clones
are very impressive.
You must be very proud.
I'm just a simple man
trying to make my way
in the universe.
Ever made your way
as far into the interior
as Coruscant?
Once or twice.
Recently?
Possibly.
Then you must know
Master Sifo-Dyas.
Uh, Boba,
rood eht so-heeck.
Master who?
[ Obi-Wan ]
Sifo-Dyas.
Is he not the Jedi
who hired you for this job?
Never heard of him.
Really?
I was recruited by
a man called Tyranus on
one of the moons of Bogden.
Curious.
Do you like your army?
I look forward
to seeing them in action.
They'll do their job well.
I'll guarantee that.
Thank you for your time,
Jango.
Always a pleasure
to meet a Jedi.
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
What is it, Dad?
Pack your things.
We're leaving.
And when I got to them,
we went into aggressive
negotiations. Thank you.
"Aggressive negotiations"?
What's that?
Uh, well, negotiations
with a lightsaber.
[ Laughing ]
Oh.
If Master Obi-Wan
caught me doing this,
he'd be very grumpy.
From the moment
I met you...
all those years ago,
not a day has gone by
when I haven't
thought of you.
And now that
I'm with you again,
I'm in agony.
The closer I get to you,
the worse it gets.
The thought of
not being with you--
I can't breathe.
I'm haunted by the kiss
that you should
never have given me.
My heart is beating,
hoping that that kiss
will not become a scar.
You are in my very soul,
tormenting me.
What can I do?
I will do anything
that you ask.
If you are suffering
as much as I am,
please, tell me.
I can't.
We can't.
It's... just not possible.
Anything
is possible, Padme.
Listen to me.
No, you listen.
We live in a real world.
Come back to it.
You're studying
to become a Jedi.
I'm-- I'm a senator.
If you follow your thoughts
through to conclusion,
it'll take us
to a place we cannot go,
regardless of the way
we feel about each other.
Then you do
feel something.
I will not let you
give up your future for me.
You are asking me
to be rational.
That is something
I know I cannot do.
Believe me,
I wish that I could just
wish away my feelings,
but I can't.
I will not give in
to this.
Well, you know, it...
wouldn't have to
be that way.
We could keep it a secret.
We'd be living a lie,
one we couldn't keep
even if we wanted to.
I couldn't do that.
Could you, Anakin?
Could you live like that?
No. You're right.
It would destroy us.
Tell your council
that the first battalions
are ready.
And remind them,
if they need more troops,
it will take more time
to grow them.
I won't forget,
and thank you.
Thank you.
R4!
[ Beeping ]
Scramble code five
to Coruscant,
care of the old folks' home!
[ Beeping ]
I have successfully
made contact
with the prime minister
of Kamino.
They are using
a bounty hunter
named Jango Fett
to create a clone army.
I have a strong feeling
that this bounty hunter...
is the assassin
we are looking for.
Do you think these cloners
are involved in the plot to
assassinate Senator Amidala?
No, Master.
There appears to be
no motive.
[ Yoda ]
Do not assume anything,
Obi-Wan.
Clear your mind must be...
if you are to discover
the real villains
behind this plot.
Yes, Master.
They say Master Sifo-Dyas
placed an order
for a clone army...
at the request
of the senate
almost ten years ago.
I was under the impression
he was killed before that.
Did the council
ever authorize the creation
of a clone army?
No. Whoever placed
that order
did not have
the authorization
of the Jedi Council.
Bring him here.
Question him we will.
Yes, Master.
I will report back
when I have him.
Blind we are
if creation of
this clone army...
we could not see.
[ Sighs ]
I think it is time
we informed the senate...
that our ability to use
the Force has diminished.
Only the dark lord
of the Sith
knows of our weakness.
If informed the senate is,
multiply
our adversaries will.
No.
[ Shmi Moaning, Indistinct ]
Anakin! Help me!
Mom, no.
Anakin!
[ Screams ]
Don't.
[ Screaming Stops ]
No.
Don't go.
I don't want to
disturb you.
Your presence is soothing.
You had another nightmare
last night.
Jedi
don't have nightmares.
I heard you.
I saw my mother.
She is suffering,
Padme.
I saw her as clearly
as I see you now.
[ Deep Sigh ]
She is in pain.
I know I'm disobeying
my mandate to protect you,
Senator,
but I have to go.
I have to help her.
I'll go with you.
I'm sorry.
I don't have a choice.
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
Dad, look!
Boba, get on board!
[ Jango Shouts ]
Oh, not good. [ Grunts ]
[ Driver Speaking Huttese ]
Wait right there.
Okey-okey.
Da wanga!
Chut-chut, Watto.
Let me help you with that.
[ Speaking Huttese ]
What? What do you want?
Wait! You’re a Jedi!
[ Grunts ]
Whatever it is...
I didn’t do it.
Ai!
[ Grunts, Sighs ]
I’m looking for Shmi Skywalker.
[ Fly Buzzing ]
[ Speaking Basic ]
Ani?
Little Ani?
Nahhh.
You are Ani! It is you!
[ Laughing ]
You sure sprouted, huh?
Wee-hoo!
A Jedi! Whattaya know!
[ Chuckles ]
Hey... maybe you could
help with some deadbeats
who owe me a lot of money.
My mother.
Oh, yeah. Shmi.
Uh...
she's not mine-a no more-a.
I sold her.
You sold her?
Years ago.
Sorry, Ani, but you know,
business is business, huh?
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah, I sold her
to a moisture farmer
named, uh, Lars.
At least I think
it was Lars.
Believe it or not,
I heard he freed her
and married her!
Can ya beat that, eh?
[ Chuckles ] Yeah.
Do you know
where they are now?
Ooh, long way from here.
Someplace over
on the other side
of Mos Eisley, I think, mmm.
I'd like to know.
Eh, sure. Absolutely!
[ Chuckles ]
Let's go look
at my records, huh?
[ Chuckles ]
Mmm.
[ Beeping ]
Dad!
I think we're being tracked!
[ Jango ]
He must have put
a homing device on our hull.
Hang on, son.
We'll move into
the asteroid field,
and we'll have a couple
of surprises for him.
[ Cackling ]
[ Beeping ]
Seismic charges! Stand by.
He doesn't seem to
take a hint, this guy.
Watch out!
[ Rapid Beeping ]
Get him, Dad! Get him! Fire!
Oh, blast!
This is why I hate flying!
We got him!
We'll just have to
finish him.
R4, prepare to jettison
the spare part canisters.
[ Beeping ]
Fire them now!
Well, we won't be
seeing him again.
[ Chuckles ]
Well, R4, I think
we've waited long enough.
[ Beeping ]
There's an unusual
concentration of Federation
ships over there, R4.
[ R4 Beeps ]
[ Beeping ]
[ R2-D2 Whistles, Beeps ]
[ Padme ]
Stay with the ship, R2.
[ Beeping ]
Oh! Um, uh, hello.
How might I be
of service? I am C--
3PO?
Oh, um--
The maker!
Oh, Master Ani!
I knew you would return.
I knew it!
And Miss Padme. Oh, my.
Hello, 3PO.
Bless my circuits!
I'm so pleased
to see you both.
I've come to see
my mother.
Oh. Um, I think perhaps
we'd better go indoors.
Master Owen,
might I present two
most important visitors.
I'm Anakin Skywalker.
Owen Lars.
Uh, this is
my girlfriend, Beru.
Hello.
I'm Padme.
I guess
I'm your stepbrother.
I had a feeling
you might show up someday.
Is my mother here?
No, she's not.
Cliegg Lars.
Shmi is my wife.
We should go inside.
We have a lot to talk about.
[ Cliegg ]
It was just before dawn.
They came out of nowhere.
A hunting party
of Tusken Raiders.
Your mother had
gone out early,
like she always did,
to pick mushrooms
that grow on the vaporators.
From the tracks,
she was about
halfway home...
when they took her.
[ Sighs ] Those Tuskens
walk like men,
but they're vicious,
mindless monsters.
Thirty of us
went out after her.
Four of us came back.
I'd be out there with them,
but after I lost my leg,
I just couldn't ride anymore
un-until I heal.
I don't want to
give up on her,
but she's been gone
a month.
There's little hope
she's lasted this long.
Where are you going?
To find my mother.
Your mother's dead, son.
Accept it.
You're gonna have to
stay here.
These are
good people, Padme.
You'll be safe.
Anakin--
I won't be long.
[ Machinery Clanging ]
[ Man #1 ]
We must persuade
the Commerce Guild...
and the Corporate Alliance
to sign the treaty.
What about the senator
from Naboo?
Is she dead yet?
I am not signing
your treaty until I have
her head on my desk.
[ Man #1 ]
I am a man of my word,
Viceroy.
[ Alien ]
With these new battle droids
we've built for you,
you'll have the finest army
in the galaxy.
[ Man #1 ]
As I explained
to you earlier,
I am quite convinced
that 10,000 more systems...
will rally to our cause
with your support,
gentlemen.
[ Alien Language ]
What you are proposing could
be construed as treason.
[ Speaking Basic ]
The Techno Union army...
[ Electronic Warbling ]
is at your disposal, Count.
The Banking Clan
will sign your treaty.
[ Man #1 ]
Good. Very good.
Our friends from
the Trade Federation
have pledged their support,
and when their
battle droids are
combined with yours,
we shall have an army
greater than any
in the galaxy.
The Jedi
will be overwhelmed.
The Republic will agree
to any demands we make.
[ Growling ]
[ Snarling ]
[ Growling,
Snarling Continue ]
[ Growling ]
[ Moaning ]
Mom.
Mom? Mom?
Ani?
Ani? Is it you?
I'm here, Mom.
You're safe.
Ani?
Oh, you look
so handsome.
My son.
Oh, my grown-up son.
I'm so proud of you,
Ani.
I missed you.
Now I am complete.
I love y--
Stay with me, Mom.
Everything--
I love--
I-- I love--
[ Groaning ]
[ Shouting ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Qui-Gon Jinn's Voice ]
Anakin! Anakin! No-o-o!
What is it?
Pain, suffering,
death I feel.
Something terrible
has happened.
Young Skywalker
is in pain.
Terrible pain.
The transmitter is working,
but we're not receiving
a return signal.
Coruscant's too far.
R4, can you boost the power?
[ Beeping ]
We'll have to try
something else.
[ Beeping ]
Maybe we can contact Anakin
on Naboo. It's much closer.
Anakin?
Anakin, do you copy?
This is Obi-Wan Kenobi.
Anakin?
He's not on Naboo, R4.
[ Beeping ]
I'm going to try
and widen the range.
I do hope
nothing's happened to him.
That's Anakin's
tracking signal, all right,
but it's coming
from Tatooine.
What in the blazes
is he doing there?
I told him
to stay on Naboo.
[ Beeping ]
We haven't got
much time.
Anakin?
Anakin, do you copy?
This is
Obi-Wan Kenobi.
[ Creature Screeching ]
[ Static,
Obi-Wan's Voice Breaks Up ]
Retransmit this message--
[ Garbled Audio ]
Anakin, do you copy?
Anakin--
My long-range-- [ Static ]
has been knocked out.
Retransmit this message
to Coruscant.
[ Beeping ]
I brought you something.
Are you hungry?
The shifter broke.
Life seems so much simpler
when you're fixing things.
I'm good at fixing things.
Always was.
But I couldn't--
Why'd she have to die?
Why couldn't I save her?
I know I could have!
Sometimes there are things
no one can fix.
You're not
all-powerful, Ani.
Well, I should be!
Someday I will be.
I will be
the most powerful Jedi ever!
I promise you.
I will even learn
to stop people from dying.
Anakin.
It's all Obi-Wan's fault!
He's jealous!
He's holding me back!
[ Object Clattering ]
[ Sniffling ]
What's wrong, Ani?
I--
I killed them.
I killed them all.
They're dead.
Every single one of them.
And not just the men,
but the women...
and the children too.
They're like animals,
and I slaughtered them
like animals!
I hate them!
[ Anakin Exhales ]
To be angry
is to be human.
I'm a Jedi.
I know
I'm better than this.
[ Cliegg ]
I know wherever you are
it's become a better place.
You were
the most loving partner
a man could ever have.
Good-bye, my darling wife.
And thank you.
I wasn't strong enough
to save you, Mom.
I wasn't strong enough.
But I promise
I won't fail again.
I miss you...
so much.
[ Beeping ]
R2?
What are you doing here?
[ Beeping ]
It seems that he is
carrying a message from
an Obi-Wan Kenobi.
Hmm. Master Ani,
does that name
mean anything to you?
[ Beeping ]
Anakin,
my long-range transmitter
has been knocked out.
Retransmit this message
to Coruscant.
I have tracked
the bounty hunter,
Jango Fett,
to the droid foundries
on Geonosis.
The Trade Federation
is to take delivery
of a droid army here,
and it is clear
that Viceroy Gunray...
is behind
the assassination attempts
on Senator Amidala.
The Commerce Guilds and
the Corporate Alliance...
have both pledged their
armies to Count Dooku
and are forming a--
Wait. Wait.
[ Lightsaber Whooshing ]
[ Obi-Wan Grunting ]
More happening on Geonosis,
I feel, than has
been revealed.
I agree.
Anakin, we will deal
with Count Dooku.
The most important thing
for you is to stay
where you are.
Protect the senator
at all costs.
That is
your first priority.
Understood, Master.
They'll never get there
in time to save him.
They have to come
halfway across the galaxy.
Look.
Geonosis is less
than a parsec away.
If he's still alive.
Ani, are you just
gonna sit here
and let him die?
He's your friend,
your mentor. He's--
He's like my father!
But you heard Master Windu.
He gave me strict orders
to stay here!
He gave you strict orders
to protect me,
and I'm going
to help Obi-Wan.
If you plan to protect me,
you'll just have to
come along.
[ Engines Power Up ]
I'm not worried, R2.
It's just I've never flown
before.
The Commerce Guilds
are preparing for war.
There can be
no doubt of that.
[ Palpatine ]
Count Dooku must have made
a treaty with them.
[ Alien Language ]
The debate is over!
Now we need that clone army.
[ Speaking Basic ]
Unfortunately,
the debate is not over.
The senate will never
approve the use of clones
before the separatists
attack.
This is a crisis.
The senate must vote
the chancellor
emergency powers.
He can then approve
the creation of an army.
But what senator would
have the courage to propose
such a radical amendment?
If only...
Senator Amidala were here.
Mm.
[ Screeching ]
[ Grumbling ]
Traitor.
Oh, no, my friend.
This is a mistake,
a terrible mistake.
They have gone too far.
This is madness.
I thought you
were the leader here,
Dooku.
This had nothing
to do with me,
I assure you.
I will petition immediately
to have you set free.
Well, I hope
it doesn't take too long.
I have work to do.
May I ask
why a Jedi knight...
is all the way
out here on Geonosis?
I've been tracking
a bounty hunter
named Jango Fett.
Do you know him?
There are no
bounty hunters here
that I am aware of.
The Geonosians
don't trust them.
Who can blame them?
But he is here,
I can assure you.
It's a great pity that
our paths have never
crossed before, Obi-Wan.
Qui-Gon always spoke
very highly of you.
I wish he were still alive.
I could use his help
right now.
Qui-Gon Jinn would
never join you.
Don't be so sure,
my young Jedi.
You forget that he was
once my apprentice,
just as you
were once his.
He knew all about
the corruption
in the senate,
but he would never have
gone along with it
if he had learned
the truth as I have.
The truth?
The truth.
What if I told you
that the Republic...
was now under the control
of the dark lord
of the Sith?
No, that's not possible.
The Jedi would be
aware of it.
The dark side of the Force
has clouded their vision,
my friend.
Hundreds of senators
are now under
the influence...
of a Sith lord
called Darth Sidious.
I don't believe you.
The viceroy of
the Trade Federation...
was once in league
with this Darth Sidious,
but he was betrayed
ten years ago
by the dark lord.
He came to me for help.
He told me everything.
You must join me,
Obi-Wan,
and together
we will destroy the Sith!
I will never join you,
Dooku.
It may be difficult
to secure your release.
[ Jar Jar ] It's-a clear
desa separatists
made a pact...
wesa desa
Federation du Trade.
Senators,
"dellow felagates":
In response to
this direct threat
to the Republic,
mesa propose
that the senate...
give immediately
emergency powers...
to the supreme chancellor.
[ Shouts Of Approval ]
Palpatine! Palpatine!
Palpatine!
[ Shouting In Alien Language ]
[ Senate Chairman ]
Order! We shall have order!
It is
with great reluctance...
that I have agreed
to this calling.
I love democracy.
I love the Republic.
[ Applause ]
The power you give me...
I will lay down when
this crisis has abated.
[ Cheering, Applause ]
And as my first act
with this new authority,
I will create
a grand army
of the Republic...
to counter
the increasing threats
of the separatists.
It is done, then.
Hmm.
I will take what Jedi
we have left and go to
Geonosis and help Obi-Wan.
Visit I will
the cloners on Kamino, hmm,
and see this army
they have created
for the Republic.
See those columns of steam
straight ahead?
They're exhaust vents
of some type.
That'll do.
Look, whatever
happens out there,
follow my lead.
I'm not interested
in getting into a war here.
As a member of the senate,
maybe I can find
a diplomatic solution
to this mess.
Don't worry. I've given up
trying to argue with you.
[ Whistling, Beeping ]
My obtuse little friend,
if they had needed our help,
they would have
asked for it, hmm?
You obviously have
a great deal to learn
about human behavior.
[ Beeping ]
For a mechanic,
you seem to do an excessive
amount of thinking.
[ Beeping ]
I am programmed
to understand humans!
[ Beeping ]
"What does that mean?" Oh!
That means
I am in charge here!
[ Raspberries ]
Where are you going now?
You don't know
what's out there.
Have you no sense at all?
Oh! Idiot!
Please wait.
[ Beeping ]
Do you know
where you're going?
Wait.
[ Squawking ]
Oh, my-- Oh, oh, oh!
[ Screaming ]
Padme!
Ah!
[ Grunts ]
Oh, my goodness!
Shut me down!
Machines making machines.
Huh! How perverse.
[ Grunts ] Oh!
Calm down, R2.
I almost fell.
You'll get your chance--
Oh! I'm scrap.
[ Grunting ]
It's a nightmare!
Oh, I want to go home!
Ahh!
Oh, what did I do
to deserve this?
[ Beeping ]
[ Whistling ]
[ Padme Grunting ]
[ Geonosian Screeching ]
Ahhh!
[ Whistling ]
Hmm. I wonder what happened
to poor little R2.
He's always getting himself
into trouble. Oops.
Oh, no!
Uh-oh.
Oh!
Oh, I'm so confused.
Oh, not again.
Obi-Wan's gonna kill me.
Don't move, Jedi!
Take him away.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not afraid to die.
I've been dying a little bit
each day since you came back
into my life.
What are you
talking about?
I love you.
You love me?
I thought that
we had decided
not to fall in love,
that we would be forced
to live a lie...
and that it would
destroy our lives.
I think our lives are about
to be destroyed anyway.
I truly,
deeply love you,
and before we die,
I want you to know.
Eeyah!
[ Loud Cheering ]
[ Cheering ]
I was beginning to wonder
if you'd got my message.
I retransmitted it
just as you had requested,
Master.
Then we decided to
come and rescue you.
Good job.
[ Cheering ]
Settle down. Settle down.
[ Speaking Geonosian ]
[ Cheering Subsides ]
Let the executions begin.
[ Cheering ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Screeching ]
I've got a bad feeling
about this.
[ Shouting ]
[ Bellowing ]
[ Creatures Roaring ]
[ Crowd Cheering ]
[ Snarling ]
Just relax. Concentrate.
What about Padme?
She seems to be
on top of things.
[ Roaring ]
[ Bellowing ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Snarling ]
[ Chuckling ]
[ Yelling ]
[ Creature Yelps ]
She can't do that!
Shoot her or-- or something!
[ Whimpering, Snarling ]
[ Shrieking ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Hissing, Growling ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Subdued Growling ]
Whoa! Yah!
[ Growling, Roaring ]
Hyah! Hyah!
[ Cheering ]
[ Snarling ]
[ Bellowing ]
Jump!
Hyah! Hyah!
[ Shrieking ]
[ Cheering ]
[ Shouting ]
This isn't how
it's supposed to be!
Jango! Finish her off!
Patience, Viceroy, patience.
She will die.
Master Windu,
how pleasant of you
to join us.
This party's over.
Brave but, uh, foolish,
my old Jedi friend.
You're impossibly outnumbered.
[ Scoffs ]
I don't think so.
We'll see.
[ Heavy Footsteps
Approaching ]
[ Synthesized Voice ]
My legs aren't moving.
I must need maintenance.
[ C-3PO ]
What's all this noise?
A-A battle!
Oh, there's been
some terrible mistake!
I'm programmed for etiquette,
not destruction!
[ Roaring ]
[ Obi-Wan Grunts ]
[ Groaning, Yelling ]
[ Yowling ]
Die, Jedi dogs!
Oh! What did I say?
Hah!
Oh, dear.
I'm terribly sorry
about all this.
Ohh!
Excuse me. I'm trapped.
I can't get up.
You call this
a diplomatic solution?
No, I call it
aggressive negotiations.
Uh-oh.
Roger, roger.
[ Growling, Screeching ]
[ Creature Shrieking ]
[ Beeping ]
R2, what are you
doing here?
[ Beeping ]
What are you doing?
Oh, stop that!
You're going to
strain something.
My neck!
Now where are you taking me?
Oh, this is such a drag.
[ Beeping ]
[ C-3PO ]
Oh, I'm quite
beside myself.
R2, please be careful!
You're singeing
my circuits!
[ Beeping ]
Yes, but is my head
on straight?
[ Dooku ]
Master Windu,
you have fought gallantly,
worthy of recognition
in the archives
of the Jedi order.
Now it is finished.
Surrender, and your lives
will be spared.
We will not be hostages
to be bartered, Dooku!
Then, I'm sorry,
old friend.
Look!
Around the survivors
a perimeter create.
[ Beeping, Chirping ]
Oh, I've had
the most peculiar dream.
If Dooku escapes,
rally more systems
to his cause he will.
Hold on!
Aim right above
the fuel cells!
Good call,
my young Padawan.
[ Viceroy Gunray ]
The Jedi have amassed
a huge army.
That doesn't seem possible.
How could the Jedi
come up with an army
so quickly?
We must send
all available droids
into battle.
There are too many.
[ Speaking Geonosian ]
Our communications have been
jammed.
Pilot,
land in that assembly area!
Yes, sir.
Sir, I have
five special commando units
awaiting your orders, sir.
To the forward
command center
take me.
Attack those Federation
starships! Quickly!
Master Yoda,
all forward positions
are advancing.
Very good. Very good.
[ Viceroy Gunray ]
This is not
looking good at all!
We must get the starships
back into space.
We have to order a retreat.
[ Speaking Geonosian ]
My master will never
allow the Republic...
to get away
with this treachery.
I’m sending my warriors to
hide in the catacombs.
The Jedi must not find our
designs for the ultimate weapon.
If they find out what we are
planning to build, we’re doomed.
[ Geonosian ]
I will take the designs
with me to Coruscant.
They will be
much safer there
with my master.
[ Alarm Blaring ]
Concentrate all your fire
on the nearest starship.
Yes, sir.
Move all quadrants
to sector 5-1-5.
Look over there!
It's Dooku!
Shoot him down!
We're out of rockets, sir.
Follow him!
We're gonna need some help!
There isn't time!
Anakin and I
can handle this!
[ Beeping ]
[ Padme Yells ]
[ Anakin ] Padme!
Put the ship down!
Anakin!
Don't let
your personal feelings
get in the way!
Follow that speeder!
Lower the ship!
I can't take Dooku alone!
I need you!
If we catch him,
we can end this war
right now!
We have a job to do!
I don't care!
Put the ship down!
You will be expelled
from the Jedi order!
I can't leave her!
Come to your senses!
What do you think
Padme would do
were she in your position?
She would do her duty.
Hmm.
The droid army
is in full retreat.
Well done, Commander.
Bring me a ship.
[ Anakin ] You're gonna pay
for all the Jedi that
you killed today, Dooku.
We'll take him together.
Go in slowly on the left.
I'm taking him now!
No, Anakin! No! No!
[ Anakin Screams ]
As you see,
my Jedi powers
are far beyond yours.
Now... back down.
I don't think so.
Master Kenobi,
you disappoint me.
Yoda holds you
in such high esteem.
Surely you can do better.
[ Moaning ]
[ Groaning ]
Are you all right?
Uh-huh.
We'd better get back to
the forward command center.
No. No.
Gather what troops you can.
We've got to get
to that hangar.
Get a transport. Hurry!
Right away.
[ Moaning ]
Ah! Ahh!
[ Anakin Shouts ]
Brave of you, boy.
But I would have thought
you had learned your lesson.
I am a slow learner.
Anakin!
[ Grunting ]
Master Yoda.
Count Dooku.
You have interfered
with our affairs
for the last time.
[ Growling ]
Powerful you have become,
Dooku.
The dark side
I sense in you.
I've become more powerful
than any Jedi.
Even you.
Much to learn
you still have.
It is obvious that
this contest
cannot be decided
by our knowledge
of the Force...
but by our skills
with a lightsaber.
[ Yelling ]
Fought well you have,
my old Padawan.
This is just the beginning.
[ Panting, Moaning ]
[ Sighing ]
[ Speaking In Droid Language ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Obi-Wan Groans ]
[ Padme ]
Anakin!
The Force is with us,
Master Sidious.
Welcome home,
Lord Tyranus.
You have done well.
I have good news
for you, my lord.
The war has begun.
Excellent.
Everything is going
as planned.
[ Obi-Wan ]
Do you believe
what Count Dooku said...
about Sidious
controlling the senate?
It doesn't feel right.
Joined the dark side
Dooku has.
Mmm. Lies, deceit,
creating mistrust
are his ways now.
[ Windu ] Nevertheless,
I feel we should keep
a closer eye on the senate.
I agree.
Where is your apprentice?
On his way to Naboo,
escorting Senator Amidala
home.
I have to admit
that without the clones,
it would not have
been a victory.
[ Yoda ]
Victory?
Victory, you say?
Master Obi-Wan,
not victory.
The shroud of
the dark side has fallen.
Begun the Clone War has.