Command station, this is ST-321.
Code clearance blue.
We’re starting our approach.
Deactivate the security shield.
The security deflector shield will be deactivated
when we have confirmation
of your code transmission.
Stand by.
You are clear to proceed.
We’re starting our approach.
[Siren]
Inform the commander
that Lord Vader’s shuttle has arrived.
Sir.
Lord Vader, this is an unexpected pleasure.
We’re honored by your presence.
You may dispense
with the pleasantries, Commander.
I’m here to put you back on schedule.
I assure you, Lord Vader,
my men are working as fast as they can.
Perhaps I can find new ways to motivate them.
I tell you this station
will be operational, as planned.
The emperor does not share
your optimistic appraisal of the situation.
But he asks the impossible.
I need more men.
Then perhaps you can tell him
when he arrives.
The emperor’s coming here?
That is correct, Commander,
and he is most displeased
with your apparent lack of progress.
We shall double our efforts.
I hope so, Commander, for your sake.
The emperor is not as forgiving as I am.
[Whistle Whistle Beep]
Of course I’m worried.
And you should be, too.
Lando Calrissian and poor Chewbacca
never returned from this awful place.
[Beep Beep Whistle]
Don’t be so sure.
If I told you half the things I’ve heard about
this Jabba the Hutt, you’d probably short-circuit.
[Whining]
[Whistle Whistle]
[Beep Whistle]
R2, are you sure this is the right place?
[Whistle Beep Beep]
I’d better knock, I suppose.
[Whistle]
There doesn’t seem to be anyone here.
Let’s go back and tell Master Luke.
[Beep Beep]
[Speaking Huttese]
Goodness gracious me!
R2-Dee Toa.
[Whistle Beep]
[Speaking Huttese]
[Whistle Beep Whistle]
C-3POA.
Ay tuta mishka Jabba du Hutt?
Kuja wanki mitby cosa.
Ha ha ha!
I don’t think they’re going to let us in, R2.
We’d better go.
[Rumble]
[Creak]
[Whistle]
[Beep Whistle Beep]
R2, wait!
[Whistle]
Oh, dear!
R2!
R2, I really don’t
think we should rush into all this.
[Beep Beep]
Oh! R2!
R2, wait for me!
[Whistle Beep]
Grr!
[Beep Beep]
Just you deliver Master Luke’s message
and get us out of here. Oh, my!
Oh!
Oh, no.
[Speaking Huttese]
Day wonna wonga?
Oh, my!
Dee wonna wygo.
[Beep]
We bring a message
to your master Jabba the Hutt.
Day Jabba wonga?
[Beep Beep]
And a gift.
Gift? What gift?
[Beep Whistle]
Ne Jabba no barta.
Eezai ohkto.
[Whistle Whistle]
Izzi kata o mohkti?
[Beep Beep]
Ne charda so dehdi.
[Whistle Beep]
He says that our instructions
are to give it only to Jabba himself.
[Whistle Whistle]
Grr!
I’m terribly sorry.
I’m afraid he’s ever so stubborn
about these sort of things.
Noht cha!
R2, I have a bad feeling about this.
[Whistle]
Oohh!
Arf! Arf!
Cava notayce, my lord.
Good morning.
Ohnt bat chuay dehr attat.
Oohh!
The message, R2, the message.
Oohh shoodah.
[Whistle Whistle Beep]
Greetings, Exalted One.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Luke Skywalker,
Jedi knight
and friend to Captain Solo.
I know that you are powerful, mighty Jabba,
and that your anger with Solo
must be equally powerful.
I seek an audience with Your Greatness
to bargain for Solo’s life.
Ha ha ha!
With your wisdom,
I’m sure that we can
work out an arrangement
which will be mutually beneficial
and enable us to avoid
any unpleasant confrontation.
As a token of my goodwill,
I present to you a gift-
these two droids.
What did he say?
Both are hardworking and will serve you well.
This can’t be!
R2, you’re playing the wrong message.
Ha ha!
Ah ha ha ha!
Master, bargonay tua knight?
He’s no Jedi.
[Speaking Huttese]
There will be no bargain.
We’re doomed.
I will not give up my favorite decoration.
I like Captain Solo where he is.
R2, look- Captain Solo.
And he’s still frozen in carbonite.
[Whistle]
Ah ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
What could possibly
have come over Master Luke?
Was it something I did?
He never expressed any
unhappiness with my work.
Ohh! How horrid!
Ohh!
Grr!
[Whistle Whistle]
Ah ah ah!
Ah ah ha!
Aaah!
Ah, good. New acquisitions.
You are a protocol droid,
are you not?
I am C-3PO-
Yes or no will do.
Oh. Well, yes.
How many languages do you speak?
I am fluent in over six million forms
of communication and can-
Splendid. We have been
without an interpreter
since our master got angry
with our last protocol droid
and disintegrated him.
Disintegrated?
Aah!
Oh!
Guard!
This protocol droid might be useful.
Fit him with a restraining bolt
and take him back up to His Excellency’s
main audience chamber.
R2, don’t leave me!
Oh!
[Whistle Beep Bleep]
You’re a feisty little one,
but you’ll soon learn some respect.
I have need for you on
the master’s sail barge,
and I think you’ll fill in nicely.
No! No! No!
Aaahh!
[Singing In Huttese]
Ah! Do that again!
Ho ho!
Aah!
Whoops! Uh-oh!
Ha ha ha!
[Creaking]
[Beast Growls]
Aaaah!
[Squeals]
[Zap]
Ooahhh!
Aah!
[Speaking Huttese]
Uhh!
[Speaking Ubese]
I have come for the bounty on this Wookiee.
Oh, no. Chewbacca!
Aarrrrr.
[Speaking Huttese]
At last we have the mighty Chewbacca.
Kanji ta, droid.
Yes, I am here, Your Worshipfulness.
Yes?
[Speaking Huttese]
The illustrious Jabba
bids you welcome
and will gladly pay you
the reward of 25,000.
I want 50,000. No less.
50,000. No less.
Wah! Aah!
Ohh!
[Speaking Huttese]
What-What did I say?
The mighty Jabba
asks why he must pay 50,000.
[Speaking Ubese]
Because he’s holding a thermal detonator!
Oh!
Aah!
Rrrrrr!
Ho ho ho ho ho ho!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
This bounty hunter is my kind of scum,
fearless and inventive.
[Speaking Huttese]
Jabba offers the sum of 35...
and I do suggest you take it.
[Speaking Ubese]
He agrees!
Arrrr!
Grrr!
[Playing Festive Tune]
Ahh!
[Speaking Huttese]
[Speaking Ubese]
Rrr!
Arrrr!
Arrrrr!
Grrrr!
Rrrr!
Grr!
Rrrrr.
[Burp]
[Clink Clink]
[Thud]
Just relax for a moment.
You’re free of the carbonite.
Shh. You have hibernation sickness.
I can’t see.
Your eyesight will return in time.
Where am I?
Jabba’s palace.
Who are you?
Someone who loves you.
Leia.
I got to get you out of here.
Ho ho ho ho ho!
What’s that?
I know that laugh.
[Speaking Huttese]
Hey, Jabba...
Look, Jabba,
I was just on my way to pay you back,
and I got a little sidetracked.
It’s not my fault.
It’s too late for that, Solo.
You may have been a good smuggler...
but now you’re Bantha fodder.
Ah ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
Look-
Take him away.
Jabba, I’ll pay you triple.
You’re throwing away a fortune!
Don’t be a fool!
[Jabba Speaking Huttese]
Bring her to me.
We have powerful friends.
You’re going to regret this.
I’m sure.
[Slurp]
Ugh!
Oh, I can’t bear to watch.
Oh! Ah ha ha ha!
Arrrrg.
Chewie?
Arrrr!
Chewie, is that you?
Rarrr!
Ch-Chewie!
I can’t see, pal.
What’s going on?
Ar grr arr.
Luke? Luke’s crazy.
He can’t even take care of himself,
much less rescue anybody.
Arrr rarrr.
A Jedi knight?
I’m out of it for a little while,
everybody gets delusions of grandeur.
Arrra!
I’m all right, pal.
Arrrrrrr.
I’m all right.
Grrr!
Arg.
Yo macka chipowan Skywalker.
Jabba mo botowa tu.
I must speak with Jabba.
Es tosit.
Jabba no tusen di hunka bi.
No bargain.
You will take me to Jabba now.
Ataka bu Jabba now.
You serve your master well.
Ay sota vanlocha.
And you will be rewarded.
A chunoh ayo ahtot.
At last! Master Luke’s come to rescue me.
Master.
Oohh!
Gabba nopez Luke Skywalker,
Jedi knight.
I told you not to admit him.
I must be allowed to speak.
He must be allowed to speak.
You weak-minded fool!
Eee! Ah!
He’s using an old Jedi mind trick.
You will bring Captain Solo
and the Wookiee to me.
Ho ho ho ho ho!
Your mind powers will not work on me, boy.
Nevertheless,
I’m taking Captain Solo and his friends.
You can either profit by this
or be destroyed.
It’s your choice, but I warn you
not to underestimate my powers.
Ooahh.
Master Luke, you’re standing on-
There will be no bargain, young Jedi.
I shall enjoy watching you die.
Grr!
Ho ho ho!
Tibi Jedi!
[Creaking]
Oh, no! The rancor!
Grr!
[Squealing]
[Crunch]
Ha ha ha!
Grr!
Grrr!
Oh!
Whoo-hoo!
Grr!
Ya! Ha!
Ah ha ha!
Grr!
[Crunch]
[Speaking Huttese]
[Whining]
Bring me Solo and the Wookiee.
They will all suffer for this outrage.
Han!
Luke!
Are you all right?
Fine. Together again, huh?
Wouldn’t miss it.
How are we doing?
Same as always.
That bad, huh?
Where’s Leia?
I’m here.
[Speaking Huttese]
[C-3PO]
Oh, dear.
His High Exaltedness,
the great Jabba the Hutt,
has decreed that you are to
be terminated immediately.
Good. I hate long waits.
Oh ah ha ha ha ha!
You will therefore be taken to the Dune Sea
and cast into the Pit of Carkoon,
the nesting place
of the all-powerful Sarlacc.
Doesn’t sound so bad.
In his belly, you will find
a new definition of pain and suffering,
as you are slowly digested over 1,000 years.
Aaarrrr!
On second thought, let’s pass on that.
You should have bargained.
[Speaking Huttese]
That’s the last mistake you’ll ever make.
Ho ho ho ho ho!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
[Band Playing Festive Tune]
I think my eyes are getting better.
Instead of a big dark blur,
I see a big light blur.
There’s nothing to see.
I used to live here, you know.
You’re going to die here, you know.
Convenient.
Just stick close to Chewie and Lando.
I’ve taken care of everything.
Oh. Great.
Aah!
Ow!
Soon you will learn to appreciate me.
[Beep Whistle]
I’m terribly sorry.
R2, what are you doing here?
[Bleep Beep]
Well, I can see you’re serving drinks,
but this place is dangerous.
They’re going to execute Master Luke
and, if we’re not careful, us, too.
[Beep Beep]
Hmmph! I wish I had your confidence.
Grrrr!
Arrr.
[Speaking Huttese]
[C-3PO]
Victims of the almighty Sarlacc,
His Excellency hopes
that you will die honorably.
But should any of you wish to beg for mercy,
the great Jabba the Hutt
will now listen to your pleas.
[Beep Beep Whistle]
Tibi Jedi.
3PO, you tell that slimy piece of worm-ridden filth
he’ll get no such pleasure from us! Right?
Grr!
Jabba...
this is your last chance.
Free us or die.
Ha ha ha!
Move him into position.
[Beep Beep]
Put him in.
Aah!
Grr!
Easy, Chewie.
Help!
Chewie, you’re hit? Where is it?
Han! Chewie!
Lando!
Boba Fett?
Boba Fett? Where?
Eeyaah!
Uhh!
[Burp]
Lando, grab it!
Lower it!
I’m trying!
Augghh!
[Death Rattle]
- Grab me, Chewie.
- I’m slipping!
Grab it! Almost... You almost got it.
Gently, now.
All right. Easy, easy. Hold me, Chewie.
Eeyaah!
Chewie!
Chewie, give me the gun.
Don’t move, Lando.
Wait! I thought you were blind!
It’s all right! I can see a lot better!
Don’t move!
A little higher! Just a little higher!
Chewie, pull us up.
Up, Chewie. Up.
Come on. We gotta get out of here.
Not my eyes! R2, help!
Quickly, R2!
Beast!
Eh heh. Boo ba daba da!
Get the gun!
Point it at the deck!
R2, where are we going?
I couldn’t possibly go-
Aah!
[Whistle]
Come on!
Let’s go. And don’t forget the droids.
We’re on our way.
[Beep Whistle Whistle]
[Whistle]
I’ll meet you back at the fleet.
[Leia]
Hurry.
The Alliance should be assembled by now.
I will.
[Han]
Hey, Luke, thanks.
Thanks for coming after me.
Now I owe you one.
[Whistle Beep]
That’s right, R2.
We’re going to the Dagobah system.
[Whistle]
I have a promise to keep...
to an old friend.
Rise, my friend.
The Death Star will be completed on schedule.
You’ve done well, Lord Vader.
And now I sense you wish
to continue your search for young Skywalker.
Yes, my master.
Patience, my friend.
In time, he will seek you out.
And when he does,
you must bring him before me.
He has grown strong.
Only together can we turn him
to the dark side of the Force.
As you wish.
Everything is proceeding as I have foreseen.
Ha ha ha ha!
[Beep Whistle]
That face you make...
Look I so old to young eyes?
No, of course not.
I do.
Yes, I do.
Sick have I become.
Old and weak.
When 900 years old you reach,
look as good you will not, hmm?
Heh heh heh.
Soon will I rest.
Yes.
Forever sleep.
Earned it I have.
Master Yoda, you can’t die.
Strong am I with the Force,
but not that strong.
Twilight is upon me, and soon night must fall.
That is the way of things...
the way of the Force.
But I need your help.
I’ve come back to complete the training.
No more training do you require.
Already know you that which you need.
Then I am a Jedi.
Oh!
[Laughs, Coughs]
Not yet.
One thing remains-
Vader.
You must confront Vader.
Then, only then, a Jedi will you be.
And confront him you will.
Master Yoda...
is Darth Vader my father?
Rest I need.
Yes.
Rest.
Yoda, I must know.
Your father he is.
Told you, did he?
Yes.
Unexpected this is.
And unfortunate.
Unfortunate that I know the truth?
No.
Unfortunate that you rushed to face him,
that incomplete was your training,
that not ready for the burden were you.
I’m sorry.
Remember...
a Jedi’s strength flows from the Force.
But beware-
Anger, fear, aggression...
the dark side are they.
Once you start down the dark path,
forever will it dominate your destiny.
Luke...
do not...
do not underestimate
the powers of the emperor,
or suffer your father’s fate you will.
Luke...
when gone am I,
the last of the Jedi will you be.
Luke...
the Force runs strong in your family.
Pass on what you have learned.
Luke...
there is...
another...
Sk...
Sky...walker.
[Beep Beep]
I can’t do it, R2.
[Beep Whistle]
I can’t go on alone.
Yoda will always be with you.
Obi-Wan.
Why didn’t you tell me?
You told me Vader
betrayed and murdered my father.
Your father was seduced by
the dark side of the Force.
He ceased to be Anakin Skywalker
and became Darth Vader.
When that happened, the good man
who was your father was destroyed.
So what I told you was true...
from a certain point of view.
A certain point of view?
Luke, you’re going to find
that many of the truths we cling to
depend greatly on our own point of view.
Anakin was a good friend.
When I first knew him,
your father was already a great pilot,
but I was amazed
how strongly the Force was with him.
I took it upon myself to train him as a Jedi.
I thought that I could instruct him
just as well as Yoda.
I was wrong.
There is still good in him.
He’s more machine now than man,
twisted and evil.
I can’t do it, Ben.
You cannot escape your destiny.
You must face Darth Vader again.
I can’t kill my own father.
Then the emperor has already won.
You were our only hope.
Yoda spoke of another.
The other he spoke of is your twin sister.
But I have no sister.
To protect you both from the emperor,
you were hidden from your father
when you were born.
The emperor knew, as I did,
if Anakin were to have any offspring,
they would be a threat to him.
That is the reason
why your sister remains safely anonymous.
Leia!
Leia’s my sister.
Your insight serves you well.
Bury your feelings deep down, Luke.
They do you credit,
but they could be made to serve the emperor.
Well, look at you- a general, huh?
Someone must have told them about
my little maneuver at the Battle of Tanaab.
Well, don’t look at me, pal.
I just said you were a fair pilot.
I didn’t know they were looking for somebody
to lead this crazy attack.
I’m surprised they didn’t ask you to do it.
Who says they didn’t? But I ain’t crazy.
You’re the respectable one, remember?
[Chimes]
The emperor’s made a critical error,
and the time for our attack has come.
The data brought to us by the Bothan spies
pinpoint the exact location
of the emperor’s new battle station.
We also know that the weapon systems
of this Death Star are not yet operational.
With the imperial fleet
spread throughout the galaxy,
in a vain effort to engage us,
it is relatively unprotected.
But most important of all,
we’ve learned that the emperor himself
is personally overseeing the final stages
of the construction of this Death Star.
Many Bothans died to
bring us this information.
Admiral Ackbar, please.
You can see here the Death Star
orbiting the forest moon of Endor.
Although the weapon systems
on this Death Star are not yet operational,
the Death Star does have
a strong defense mechanism.
It is protected by an energy shield which is generated
from the nearby forest moon of Endor.
The shield must be deactivated
if any attack is to be attempted.
Once the shield is down,
our cruisers will create a perimeter
while the fighters fly into the superstructure
and attempt to knock out the main reactor.
General Calrissian has volunteered
to lead the fighter attack.
Good luck.
You’re going to need it.
General Madine.
We have stolen a small imperial shuttle.
Disguised as a cargo ship
and using a secret imperial code,
a strike team will land on the moon
and deactivate the shield generator.
Sounds dangerous.
I wonder who they found
to pull that off.
General Solo,
is your strike team assembled?
Uh, my team’s ready.
I don’t have a command crew
for the shuttle.
Arrr!
It’s going to be rough, pal.
I didn’t wanna speak for you.
Arr!
That’s one.
General... count me in.
I’m with you, too.
What is it?
Ask me again sometime.
Luke.
Hi, Han, Chewie.
[Whistle]
"Exciting" is hardly the word I would choose.
Look, I want you to take her.
I mean it. Take her.
You need all the help you can get.
She’s the fastest ship in the fleet.
All right, old buddy.
I know what she means to you.
I’ll take good care of her.
She won’t get a scratch.
All right?
Right.
I got your promise.
Not a scratch.
Would you get going, you pirate?
Good luck.
You, too.
Got her warmed?
She’s coming up.
Arr!
Yeah, well, I don’t think the Empire had Wookiees
in mind when they designed her, Chewie.
Hey, you awake?
Yeah. I just got a funny feeling,
like I’m not gonna see her again.
Come on, General, let’s move.
Right. Chewie, let’s see
what this piece of junk can do.
Ready, everybody?
All set.
[Whistle]
Here we go again.
All right, hang on.
What is thy bidding, my master?
Send the fleet to the far side of Endor.
There it will stay until called for.
What of the reports of the rebel fleet
massing near Sullust?
It is of no concern.
Soon the rebellion will be crushed
and young Skywalker will be one of us.
Your work here is finished, my friend.
Go out to the command ship
and await my orders.
Yes, my master.
If they don’t go for this, we’re gonna
have to get out of here pretty quick, Chewie.
Arrrr!
[Radio]
We have you on our screen now.
Please identify.
Shuttle Tydirium requesting deactivation
of the deflector shield.
Shuttle Tydirium, transmit
the clearance code for shield passage.
Transmission commencing.
Now we find out if that code is worth
the price we paid.
It’ll work. It’ll work.
Vader’s on that ship.
Now, don’t get jittery, Luke.
There are a lot of command ships.
Keep your distance, though, Chewie,
but don’t look like you’re trying
to keep your distance.
Arrrr?!
I don’t know. Fly casual.
Where is that shuttle going?
Shuttle Tydirium,
what is your cargo and destination?
Parts and technical crew for the forest moon.
Do they have a code clearance?
It’s an older code, sir, but it checks out.
I was about to clear them.
I’m endangering the mission.
I shouldn’t have come.
It’s your imagination, kid.
Let’s keep a little optimism here.
Shall I hold them?
No.
Leave them to me.
I will deal with them myself.
As you wish, my lord. Carry on.
They’re not going for it, Chewie.
Shuttle Tydirium,
deactivation of the shield
will commence immediately.
Follow your present course.
O.K. I told you it was going to work.
No problem.
Oh, I told you it was dangerous here!
Should we try and go around?
It’ll take time.
This whole party will be
for nothing if they see us.
Arr!
Chewie and I will take care of this.
You stay here.
Quietly. There might be more of them out there.
Hey, it’s me.
[Snap]
Go for help! Go!
Great. Come on!
Over there! Two more of them.
I see them. Wait, Leia!
Hey, wait!
Quick. Jam their comlink!
Center switch!
Move closer!
Get alongside that one!
Oh!
Keep on that one! I’ll take these two!
Aah!
[Whistle Beep Beep]
General Solo, somebody’s coming.
Urrr!
Oh!
Luke!
Arrr!
Where’s Leia?
She didn’t come back?
I thought she was with you.
We got separated. We better go look for her.
Take the squad ahead.
We’ll meet at the shield generator at 0300.
Come on, R2,
we’ll need your scanners.
Don’t worry, Master Luke.
We know what to do.
And you said it was pretty here.
Eek.
Eek!
Cut it out!
Grrrrr.
Rrrr.
[Speaking Ewokese]
Arrr. Arrr.
I’m not going to hurt you.
Oh.
[Speaking Ewokese]
Well, looks like I’m stuck here.
Trouble is, I don’t know where here is.
Maybe you can help me.
Come on. Sit down.
Grrrrr.
I promise I won’t hurt you.
Now come here.
Grrrrr!
All right. You want something to eat?
[Speaking Ewokese]
That’s right.
Come on.
[Speaking Ewokese]
Hmm?
[Sniff Sniff]
[Speaking Ewokese]
Ya! Yee!
Look. It’s a hat.
It’s not going to hurt you. Look.
Arrr.
[Speaking Ewokese]
You’re a jittery little thing, aren’t you?
Ooooh!
[Sniff Sniff]
What is it?
[Speaking Ewokese]
[Sniff Sniff Sniff]
[Zap]
Oh!
[Speaking Ewokese]
Freeze!
Come on, get up!
Grrrrr!
Go get your ride. Take her back to base.
Yes, sir.
Rrrooh!
What the-
Ya!
[Speaking Ewokese]
Come on. Let’s get out of here.
I told you to remain on the command ship.
A small rebel force has penetrated the shield
and landed on Endor.
Yes, I know.
My son is with them.
Are you sure?
I have felt him, my master.
Strange that I have not.
I wonder if your feelings
on this matter are clear, Lord Vader.
They are clear, my master.
Then you must go to the sanctuary moon
and wait for him.
He will come to me?
I have foreseen it.
His compassion for you will be his undoing.
He will come to you,
and then you will bring him before me.
As you wish.
Luke! Luke!
Oh, Master Luke.
Arrrrr.
There’s two more
wrecked speeders back there.
And I found this.
I’m afraid that R2’s sensors
can find no trace of Princess Leia.
I hope she’s all right.
Arrrrr!
What, Chewie?
Arrrrrrrr.
Arrrr.
Arrr.
I don’t get it.
It’s just a dead animal, Chewie.
Chewie, wait!
Don’t!
Aah!
Nice work.
Arrrrr!
Great, Chewie.
Great. Always thinking with your stomach.
Take it easy. Let’s just figure a way
to get out of this thing.
Han, can you reach my lightsaber?
Yeah. Sure.
[Whistle Beep Beep]
R2, I’m not sure that’s such a good idea.
It’s a very long drop!
Ah.
[Speaking Ewokese]
What-
Hey! Point that thing someplace else.
[Arguing In Ewokese]
Hey!
Han, don’t. It’ll be all right.
[Speaking Ewokese]
Chewie, give them your crossbow.
Arrrrr!
Oh, my head!
[Speaking Ewokese]
Oh, my goodness.
[Chanting In Ewokese]
[Speaking Ewokese]
Do you understand anything they’re saying?
Oh, yes, Master Luke.
Remember that I am fluent
in over six million forms-
What are you telling them?
Hello, I think.
I could be mistaken.
They’re using a very primitive dialect.
I do believe they think I am
some sort of god.
[Beep Beep]
Haaaar!
Why don’t you use your divine influence
and get us out of this?
I beg your pardon, General Solo,
but that just wouldn’t be proper.
Proper?
It’s against my programming
to impersonate a deity.
Why, you-
[Speaking Ewokese]
My mistake.
He’s an old friend of mine.
Jabba jabba jabba.
♪
Ow!
Hey!
[Squeak]
Rrrr.
Arrrr!
I have a really bad feeling about this.
[Speaking Ewokese]
What did he say?
I’m rather embarrassed, General Solo,
but it appears you are to be the main course
at a banquet in my honor.
Arrrrr!
[Singing In Ewokese]
Leia!
[Speaking Ewokese]
Your Royal Highness.
But these are my friends.
[Singing In Ewokese]
3PO, tell them they must be set free.
Arrrrr!
[Speaking Ewokese]
Eee! Ya! Ya! Ya!
Somehow I got the feeling
that didn’t help us very much.
3PO, tell them if they don’t do as you wish,
you’ll become angry and use your magic.
But, Master Luke, what magic?
I couldn’t possibly.
Just tell them.
[Speaking Ewokese]
Boom!
You see, Master Luke? They didn’t believe me,
just as I said they wouldn’t.
Wait, wait.
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
Eee!
Put me down!
Help! Somebody!
Somebody, help!
Master Luke! R2, R2, quickly!
Oh! Oh!
[Speaking Ewokese]
[Beep Beep Whistle]
Oh!
Aah!
Ooh!
Thank goodness.
[Whistle Beep]
Thanks, 3PO.
I never knew I had it in me.
Woochana makawartas,
woochana makawartas.
Nervrenda bootootoo Tatooine.
Faraway, mana quitoo.
Princess Leia wasay wapa R2.
Oos batata rundi Darth Vader!
[Darth Vader’s Breathing]
Un Chenko baskimo quertonto Death Star.
[Roar Of Spaceship]
[Zap]
Wos michi un Jedi, Obi-Wan Kenobi.
Ee manu machi Vader konyono.
[Hum Of Lightsaber]
[Whistle Whistle Beep Beep]
Yes, R2, I was just coming to that.
Torron togosh.
[Feet Stomping]
Master Luke ahchiminie choodoo.
[Roar Of Spaceship]
[Zap]
Eee!
Uta Millennium Falcon
ahchiminie Cloud City.
[Roar Of Spaceship]
Oos nooch Vader.
[Darth Vader’s Breathing]
Han Solo.
Arrrr.
Tiklo carbon!
Un dekochna gooboo Sarlacc.
[Lightsaber Crackling]
Prrrrr.
Haonna keenie chetoo toomoo maneta.
[Speaking Ewokese]
What’s going on?
I don’t know.
[Speaking Ewokese]
Wonderful.
We are now a part of the tribe.
Just what I always wanted.
[Beep Beep Beep]
Short help’s better than no help at all.
He says the scouts are going to show us
the quickest way to the shield generator.
How far is it? Ask him.
We need some fresh supplies, too.
[Speaking Ewokese]
Try and get our weapons back.
Hurry up, will you? I haven’t got all day.
Luke, what’s wrong?
Leia, do you remember your mother,
your real mother?
Just a little bit.
She died when I was very young.
What do you remember?
Just images, really. Feelings.
Tell me.
She was...
very beautiful.
Kind...but sad.
Why are you asking me this?
I have no memory of my mother.
I never knew her.
Luke, tell me, what’s troubling you?
Vader is here.
Now. On this moon.
How do you know?
I felt his presence.
He’s come for me.
He can feel when I’m near.
That’s why I have to go.
As long as I stay, I’m endangering the group
and our mission here.
I have to face him.
Why?
He’s my father.
Your father?
There’s more.
It won’t be easy for you to hear it,
but you must.
If I don’t make it back,
you’re the only hope for the Alliance.
Don’t talk that way.
You have a power I don’t understand
and could never have.
You’re wrong, Leia.
You have that power, too.
In time, you’ll learn to use it as I have.
The Force is strong in my family.
My father has it.
I have it.
And...
my sister has it.
Yes.
It’s you, Leia.
I know.
Somehow...
I’ve always known.
Then you know why I have to face him.
No! Luke, run away. Far away.
If he can feel your presence,
then leave this place.
I wish I could go with you.
No, you don’t.
You’ve always been strong.
But why must you confront him?
Because... there is good in him.
I’ve felt it.
He won’t turn me over to the emperor.
I can save him.
I can turn him back to the good side.
I have to try.
Hey, what’s going on?
Nothing.
I just want to be alone for a little while.
Nothing?
Come on, tell me.
What’s going on?
I...
I can’t tell you.
Could you tell Luke?
Is that who you could tell?
I...
Ah.
I’m sorry.
Hold me.
This is the rebel that surrendered to us.
Although he denies it,
I believe there may be more of them,
and I request permission
to conduct a further search of the area.
He was armed only with this.
Good work, Commander.
Leave us.
Conduct your search
and bring his companions to me.
Yes, my lord.
The emperor has been expecting you.
I know, Father.
So, you have accepted the truth.
I’ve accepted the truth that you were once
Anakin Skywalker, my father.
That name no longer has any meaning for me.
It is the name of your true self.
You’ve only forgotten.
I know there is good in you.
The emperor hasn’t driven it from you fully.
That was why you couldn’t destroy me.
That’s why you won’t bring me
to your emperor now.
I see you have constructed a new lightsaber.
Your skills are complete.
Indeed you are powerful,
as the emperor has foreseen.
Come with me.
Obi-Wan once thought as you do.
You don’t know the power of the dark side.
I must obey my master.
I will not turn,
and you’ll be forced to kill me.
If that is your destiny.
Search your feelings, Father.
You can’t do this.
I feel the conflict within you.
Let go of your hate.
It is too late for me, son.
The emperor will show you
the true nature of the Force.
He is your master now.
Then my father is truly dead.
Urrr.
The main entrance to the control bunker
is on the far side of that landing platform.
This isn’t going to be easy.
Hey, don’t worry.
Chewie and me got into a lot of places
more heavily guarded than this.
[Speaking Ewokese]
[Leia]
What’s he saying?
He says there’s a secret entrance
on the other side of the ridge.
Admiral, we’re in position.
All fighters accounted for.
Proceed with the countdown.
All groups assume attack coordinates.
[Speaking Alien Language]
Don’t worry. My friend’s down there.
He’ll have that shield down on time.
[Speaking Alien Language]
Or this will be
the shortest offensive of all time.
All craft, prepare to jump
into hyperspace on my mark.
All right. Stand by.
[Whistle]
[Speaking Ewokese]
Back door, huh? Good idea.
It’s only a few guards.
This shouldn’t be too much trouble.
[Speaking Ewokese]
It only takes one to sound the alarm.
Then we’ll do it real quiet like.
Oh, my! Princess Leia!
I’m afraid our furry companion
has gone and done something rather rash.
Rrrrooohh.
Oh, no.
There goes our surprise attack.
[Starts Engine]
Look, over there! Stop him!
Not bad for a little furball.
There’s only one left.
You stay here.
We’ll take care of this.
I have decided
that we shall stay here.
Whoo-whoo!
Yahoo!
Whoo whoo!
Wa ha ha ha!
Hey!
Yoooaww!
Ooohm.
Welcome, young Skywalker.
I have been expecting you.
You’ll no longer need those.
Guards, leave us.
I’m looking forward
to completing your training.
In time, you will call me master.
You’re gravely mistaken.
You won’t convert me as you did my father.
Oh, no, my young Jedi.
You will find that
it is you who are mistaken...
about a great many things.
His lightsaber.
Ah, yes. A Jedi’s weapon.
Much like your father’s.
By now you must know your father
can never be turned from the dark side.
So will it be with you.
You’re wrong.
Soon I’ll be dead, and you with me.
Ha ha ha ha!
Perhaps you refer
to the imminent attack of your rebel fleet.
Yes.
I assure you,
we are quite safe from your friends here.
Your overconfidence is your weakness.
Your faith in your friends is yours.
It is pointless to resist, my son.
Everything that has transpired
has done so according to my design.
Your friends up there on the sanctuary moon
are walking into a trap, as is your rebel fleet.
It was I who allowed the Alliance
to know the location of the shield generator.
It is quite safe from your pitiful little band.
An entire legion of my best troops awaits them.
Oh...
I’m afraid the deflector shield
will be quite operational when your friends arrive.
All right, up! Move! Come on.
Quickly. Quickly.
Chewie.
Grr!
Han, hurry!
The fleet will be here any moment.
Charges! Come on, come on!
Oh, my! They’ll be captured!
[Speaking Ewokese]
Wait! Wait! Come back!
R2, stay with me.
Freeze!
Aah!
You rebel scum.
Uhh waahh!
Uhh!
Ahh yaa!
All wings report in.
Red Leader standing by.
Gray Leader standing by.
Green Leader standing by.
Lock S-foils in attack positions.
May the Force be with us.
[Speaking Alien Language]
We’ve got to get a reading on that shield.
How could they be jamming us
if they don’t know...
if we’re coming.
Break off the attack!
The shield is still up.
I get no reading. You sure?
Pull up! All craft pull up!
Take evasive action.
Green Group, stick to Holding Sector MV-7.
Admiral, we have
enemy ships in Sector 47.
It’s a trap!
Fighters coming in!
There’s too many of them!
Accelerate to attack speed.
Draw their fire away from the cruisers.
Copy, Gold Leader.
Come, boy.
See for yourself.
From here, you will witness
the final destruction of the Alliance
and the end of your insignificant rebellion.
You want this...
don’t you?
The hate is swelling in you now.
Take your Jedi weapon.
Use it.
I am unarmed.
Strike me down with it.
Give in to your anger.
With each passing moment,
you make yourself more my servant.
No.
It is unavoidable.
It is your destiny.
You, like your father,
are now...
mine.
All right, move it!
Keep moving. Come on.
Hello!
I say, over there!
Were you looking for me?
Grr!
Bring those two down here.
Well, they’re on their way.
R2, are you sure this was a good idea?
Freeze!
Don’t move!
We surrender.
Aiyee!
Haa!
♪
♪ ♪
♪ ♪ ♪
♪
Whoo! Whoo!
Aiyee!
Yaah!
Haa!
The code’s changed. We need R2.
Here’s the terminal.
R2, where are you?
We need you at the bunker right away.
What do you mean, you’re going?
[Bleep Boop]
Going where, R2?
No, wait!
This is no time for heroics!
Come back!
Watch yourself, Wedge. Three from above.
Red 3, Red 2, pull in.
Got it.
Three of them coming in, 20 degrees.
Cut to the left. I’ll take the leader.
They’re heading for the medical frigate.
Pressure steady.
Only the fighters are attacking.
I wonder what those Stardestroyers are waiting for.
We’re in attack position, sir.
Hold here.
We’re not going to attack?
I have my orders from the emperor himself.
He has something special planned for them.
We only need to keep them from escaping.
As you can see, my young apprentice,
your friends have failed.
Now witness the firepower of this
fully armed and operational battle station.
Fire at will, Commander.
Fire.
Oh!
That blast came from the Death Star.
That thing’s operational!
Home 1, this is Gold Leader.
All craft prepare to retreat.
You won’t get another chance at this, Admiral.
We have no choice, General Calrissian.
Our cruisers can’t repel
firepower of that magnitude.
Han will have that shield down.
We’ve got to give him more time.
We’re coming!
Aah!
Come on, come on!
Oh, R2, hurry!
Yeeoooww!
Oh, my goodness!
[Blip Blip Beep Beep]
Why did you have to be so brave?
Eeooow...
Well, I suppose I could hot-wire this thing.
I’ll cover you.
[Speaking Ewokese]
Yes, I said closer.
Move as close as you can and engage
those Stardestroyers at point-blank range!
At that close range, we won’t last long
against those Stardestroyers.
We’ll last longer than we will
against that Death Star!
And we might just take a few of them with us.
She’s going to blow!
I’m hit!
Your fleet is lost,
and your friends on the Endor moon
will not survive.
There is no escape...
my young apprentice.
The Alliance will die...
as will your friends.
Good.
I can feel your anger.
I am defenseless.
Take your weapon.
Strike me down with all of your hatred,
and your journey towards the dark side
will be complete!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
[Speaking Ewokese]
Ah...eeyaheeyah... eeyaheeyah!
Look!
Get him off of there!
Aaah!
Yahoo!
Yeeha! Yaaa!
Yeehaha!
I think I got it.
I got it!
Aah!
Princess Leia, are you all right?
Let’s see.
It’s not bad.
Freeze!
Oh, dear.
Don’t move!
I love you.
I know.
Hands up!
Stand up!
Stay back.
Arrr!
Chewie!
Get down here! She’s wounded!
No, wait!
I got an idea.
Good.
Use your aggressive feelings, boy.
Let the hate flow through you.
Obi-Wan has taught you well.
I will not fight you, Father.
You are unwise to lower your defenses.
Your thoughts betray you, Father.
I feel the good in you, the conflict.
There is no conflict.
You couldn’t bring yourself
to kill me before.
I don’t believe you’ll destroy me now.
You underestimate
the power of the dark side.
If you will not fight,
then you will meet your destiny.
[Emperor]
Good. Good.
Watch out! Squad at .06.
I’m on it, Gold Leader.
Good shot, Red 2.
We’re sure in the middle of it now.
Come on, Han, old buddy, don’t let me down.
It’s over, Commander.
The rebels have been routed.
They’re fleeing into the woods.
We need reinforcements
to continue the pursuit.
Send three squads to help.
Open the back door.
Throw me another charge.
You cannot hide forever, Luke.
I will not fight you.
Give yourself to the dark side.
It is the only way you can save your friends.
Yes.
Your thoughts betray you.
Your feelings for them are strong,
especially for...
sister.
So...
you have a twin sister.
Your feelings have now betrayed her, too.
Obi-Wan was wise to hide her from me.
Now his failure is complete.
If you will not turn to the dark side,
then perhaps she will.
Never!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Good!
Your hate has made you powerful.
Now...
fulfill your destiny...
and take your father’s place at my side.
Never.
I’ll never turn to the dark side.
You’ve failed, Your Highness.
I am a Jedi,
like my father before me.
So be it...
Jedi.
Move!
The shield is down!
Commence attack
on the Death Star’s main reactor!
We’re on our way.
Red Group, Gold Group, all fighters follow me.
I told you they’d do it!
If you will not be turned,
you will be destroyed.
Young fool.
Only now, at the end,
do you understand.
Your feeble skills are no match
for the power of the dark side.
Aaah!
You have paid the price
for your lack of vision.
Aaah!
Father, please!
Ow! Aaah!
Help me!
Aaah!
Now, young Skywalker...
you will die.
Aahh!
Ow! Aaah!
No.
No!
Aaah!
Aaaahhhhh!
[Labored Breathing]
I’m going in.
Here goes nothing.
Now lock onto the strongest power source.
It should be the power generator.
Form up. Stay alert.
We could run out of space real fast.
Split up and head back to the surface.
See if you can get a few
of those TIE fighters to follow you.
Copy, Gold Leader.
That was too close.
We’ve got to give those fighters more time.
Concentrate all fire
on that Super Stardestroyer.
Sir, we’ve lost our bridge deflector shields.
Intensify the forward batteries.
I don’t want anything to get through!
Intensify forward firepower!
Aaah!
Too late!
[Cheering And Applause]
Luke.
Help me take this mask off.
But you’ll die.
Nothing can stop that now.
Just for once...
let me look on you with my own eyes.
Now...
go, my son.
Leave me.
No. You’re coming with me.
I’ll not leave you here. I’ve got to save you.
You already have, Luke.
You were right.
You were right about me.
Tell your sister...
you were right.
Father.
I won’t leave you.
There it is.
All right, Wedge,
go for the power regulator on the north tower.
Copy, Gold Leader.
I’m already on my way out.
Move the fleet away from the Death Star.
Yee-ha!
Yah.
Yaaa!
Ya!
[Beep! Beep! Beep!]
They did it!
I’m sure Luke
wasn’t on that thing when it blew.
He wasn’t.
I can feel it.
You love him.
Don’t you?
Yes.
All right. I understand.
Fine.
When he comes back,
I won’t get in the way.
It’s not like that at all.
He’s my brother.
[Speaking Ewokese]
♪
Wesa free!
[Singing In Ewokese]