[CHOIR SINGING DIRGE]
[DIRGE CONTINUES]
[ORGANA] You shouldn't have come here.
There's nothing you could have done.
For either of them.
Why risk it?
She was my friend.
[COMMS CHATTER IN DISTANCE]
There's a patrol coming.
You must leave.
- Where is your ship?
- The river.
This way.
[COMMS CHATTER]
Here.
If you need anything,
you can contact me with this.
No.
I'm tired of fighting.
[COMMS CHATTER]
[SECURITY CLONE] You there!
What can I do for you, officer?
[SECURITY CLONE]
Let's see some identification.
Of course.
[SECURITY CLONE]
Senator Organa of Alderaan.
[ORGANA] That's right.
I'm afraid no one
is allowed back here, Senator.
Imperial orders.
Forgive me. It's easy to get lost
with all that has happened.
Still, we have a duty. Don't we?
An obligation to uphold,
when we're able.
We'll have to escort you back
to the procession, Senator.
I understand.
And if you should ever need anything,
please contact me.
[ENGINES POWERING UP]
[DROID BEEPING]
[VILLAGE SISTER] You just leave me to it.
This is my payload, not yours!
I'm just telling you, you gotta hurry up.
We're gonna break for lunch.
[RUMBLING]
You're piling them up too high. Again.
I know what I'm doing.
[BELL CHIMING]
Break time. Break time.
Hey, droid. Finish up!
- You can't leave it like that.
- I'm hungry!
[DROID BEEPS]
[SHRIEKS, BEEPS]
Lucky.
Very lucky, child.
[DROID BEEPS]
[DROID WHIRRING, BEEPING]
Ashla, come sit with us.
Please?
No one can keep up
with the Imperial quotas.
It gets more difficult every season.
In the beginning,
you all welcomed the Empire.
Not as warmly as you.
Emperor Palpatine brought peace.
Through persecution.
Not citizens like us!
Only rebels who threatened the Empire.
No one is safe.
Only if you aren't loyal.
We are safe.
But not because of the Empire.
[DROID BEEPING]
Don't forget, we have to take the harvest
over to Mon-Hella tomorrow.
That path can be dangerous.
Is your brother coming along?
No. But we'll be fine, won't we?
[WHISPERING] Master Jedi.
You shouldn't say such things.
I saw you push the bales clear of me.
You have it wrong.
Why didn't you tell us?
There's nothing to tell.
[WHISPERING] Don't worry. It's our secret.
I'll meet you near the field.
At first light!
[DROID CHIRPING]
Now, remember, don't accept
the first price they offer you.
- I know. Haggle.
- [DROID BEEPS]
Don't worry.
See you tomorrow.
May the Force be with you.
[DROID BEEPS]
Prices were so low,
they're bleeding us dry.
I couldn't get half
of what they offered us last season.
[DROID WHIRRING]
[BEEPS, WHIMPERS]
You claim a Jedi was here,
and yet, I find no one.
I promise you.
They'll be back. I turned her in.
I-I should be rewarded.
You lie to me and expect Imperial favor?
[AHSOKA] He's not lying.
And who might you be?
Let them go.
- She's the Jedi!
- Stop it!
See. I told you they'd be back.
So you did.
Here is your reward.
No!
[GRUNTS]
Can it be?
You're supposed to be dead.
Looks like I shall be rewarded...
Ahsoka Tano!
[GRUNTS]
[SCREECHES]
Look! Look what you did.
Look what you did!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I know.
More will come.
- You're going to have to leave.
- How? Where?
[SHIP APPROACHING]
[ENGINES ROARING]
- [HATCH OPENS]
- [BOARDING CHAMBER LOWERS]
Please, this way.
I was beginning to think you lost this.
Things have only gotten worse.
Are you sure you are ready
to get back into the fight?