We'll be arriving shortly, Master.
Set us down well clear of the village.
Tensions are high enough.
Yes, Master.
[CREATURES WARBLE]
[DROID BEEPS]
[BEEPING]
[INSECTS BUZZING]
[MOUSE SQUEAKING]
[BARKING]
[VILLAGER WHISTLES]
[DOG GROANS]
Excuse me. Sorry to trouble y...
[CREATURES WARBLE]
[BEEPING]
[WHINES]
[VILLAGER COUGHING]
[DOOKU] Where is the child?
Where are they holding the Senator's son?
Why should we tell you?
Allow me to make my intentions clear.
Jedi.
We are here to help resolve the situation.
For the Senator.
For everyone.
What do you know of Senator Dagonet?
He is one of the longest-standing
Senators in the Republic.
Yes, and when you entered this village,
you could see the effects
of his long-standing policies.
With due respect, if you don't like him,
why not elect a new Senator?
I wish it were that simple.
Perhaps, in the beginning,
Senator Dagonet was a good person
and had the interests
of the people in mind. But now...
Come, I will show you
where the Senator's son is.
You're one of the kidnappers?
They all are.
[CREATURES WARBLE]
[DROID CHATTERS]
[CHATTERS]
Have you been treated well?
For a prisoner, yes.
Besides, I have Two-ton here
to keep me company.
[CHATTERS]
Your ordeal will soon be over.
It's not much of an ordeal.
Not compared to how
these people are living.
And you were not aware
of these conditions?
I rarely leave the capital.
When I do, I spend time
off-world on Coruscant,
not here.
How could my father allow this
to happen to his people?
You don't blame them for abducting you?
What choice did they have?
The Senator, he's here!
And he's brought soldiers.
You have deceived us, Master Jedi.
No, our coming here
was not known to the Senator.
[TWO-TON CHATTERS]
[DROID CHATTERS]
She is hungry.
Many would do the same.
Jedi, arrest these criminals
and have them release my son at once.
I'm afraid our investigation
is not yet complete, Senator.
Investigation?
They abducted my son.
I demand his release!
Let me assure you
your son is in no immediate danger.
I'll be the judge of that.
Guards!
Step aside, Jedi.
We cannot.
You serve the Senate.
No.
We serve the people of this Republic.
So be it.
Ready!
Aim!
Stand down.
I will not.
Fire!
[GRUNTS, SCREAMS]
[SENATOR'S SON] No!
[GRUNTS]
Halt!
I will destroy this town
and make an example of it,
and many others.
None shall defy me!
Not even you, Master Jed...
[FORCE RUMBLING]
[CHOKING]
Master.
[SCREAMS]
Go! Save your father.
- What?
- Go now.
- Corruption like yours must be eradicated.
- [CHOKING]
No!
Stop!
Master, it's over.
[CHOKING]
- [GROANS]
- [LIGHTSABER RETRACTS]
[COUGHS]
My son.
Father, how could you do this?
These are your people...
our people!
I will not allow
your suffering to continue.
I promise.
[BARKING]
I wonder if any meaningful change
will come of this.
Is that why you took action
into your own hands?
Your actions saved many lives today.
Just thinking in the moment, Master.
Well, then.
You're a much wiser man than I,
Qui-Gon Jinn.
Thanks to your teachings.