[CHATTERING]
[LIGHTSABER HUMMING]
You're right on time.
Oh, really? I thought I was late.
That's what I meant.
She's a fast learner.
I really wouldn't know.
[SYSTEM CHIMES]
[LIGHTSABER RETRACTS]
[WHIRRING, CLICKING]
These are the new training remotes
designed to simulate battle droids.
[DROID SHRIEKS]
[DROID SPUTTERS]
[SYSTEM CHIMES]
Impressive.
[SIGHS]
[COMMS CHATTER]
Thanks for coming, Master.
Well, I was in the area.
Any thoughts?
You don't wanna know.
What's the problem?
[JEDI MURMURING]
[SCOFFS] It's a lousy test.
But it's what every Jedi does.
Exactly.
Look, you want a real test?
Name it.
Okay, I'll make you an actual test,
and then we'll see
what you've really learned.
[GUNSHIP APPROACHING]
You're right on time.
I thought I was late.
That's what I mean.
Captain Rex and the boys have agreed
to help with the test.
It's our privilege, Commander.
Let's get started. Head out to the center.
Make sure your blasters are set to stun.
Droids are predictable.
I want you to be prepared for anything.
You need to remain calm. Think.
Feel the intention
of the trooper who will fire first.
You should be able to sense the moment
before they even pull the trigger.
You ready?
Begin.
[GRUNTS]
[THUDS]
[VOICE ECHOING]
Don't worry, Rex. She'll wake up.
[NORMAL] That's it. Come on.
You'll get used to it. Wake up.
[GROANS]
[SIGHS] How long was I out?
- An hour.
- An hour?
Yeah, Jesse really tagged you.
Sorry, Commander.
Come on. Let's go again.
You ready?
Begin.
- [GROANS]
- [ANAKIN] Let's go again.
Again.
- [GROANS]
- [ANAKIN] Again.
Again.
I don't know how much more of this
she can take.
Eh. She'll be fine.
Well, you're waking up faster.
[GROANS]
This is ridiculous.
The droids aren't half as good
as Rex's men.
That's the point.
Look, I know this is tough,
but... [SIGHS] ...I want it to be difficult.
This is about life and death.
And as your master,
I'm responsible for you.
The best way I can protect you is
to teach you how to protect yourself.
And if you can hold off Rex and the boys,
you'll be ready for anything
on a battlefield.
Well, eh,
anything with a blaster at least.
You ready?
All right, boys, let's go again.
- [BLASTER FIRES]
- [AHSOKA GRUNTS]
[COMMS CHATTER]
Not bad. It took us five minutes
to knock you out that time.
I can do better.
Begin.
[BLAST IMPACTS]
[RUMBLING]
[ALARM BLARING]
Let's hope all that training pays off.
[REX] Hold your fire!
[JESSE] Hang on.
We have Tano and the commander.
Send all remaining troops to my position.