[BIRDS TWEETING]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
- [DOOR OPENS]
- [BABY CRYING]
[LAUGHS]
[SPEAKING TOGRUTI]
She's here! She's here. [LAUGHS]
- [SPEAKING TOGRUTI]
- [CROWD MURMURING]
[CHUCKLING]
Yeah! Come, come, come, come.
[CRYING CONTINUES]
[VILLAGERS MURMURING]
[BABY COOING]
[COOS]
Ahsoka.
[DROID BEEPS]
[GROANS]
[COOS]
[PARENT] Are you sure she's ready?
Nak-il, it is custom.
In old days. Old ways for the old.
Not you, Pav-ti. Not yet.
Don't make fun. You'll insult the spirits.
The trees?
Ancestors.
All right then. I meant no offense.
[DOOR BEEPS]
Good hunting, Pav-ti, my little Soka.
[BABBLES]
[BARKING]
Pav-ti, off on the hunt?
Has it been more than a year already?
It has, Gantika.
Well then.
For luck.
[GANTIKA SPEAKING TOGRUTI]
[COOING]
[SPEAKING TOGRUTI]
Thank you, Gantika.
[BARKING]
[BIRD WARBLES]
[CHITTERING]
[COOS]
[CHITTERS]
Look, Ahsoka, everywhere there is life.
Value it. Honor it.
[COOING, BABBLING]
[GIGGLES, COOS]
[GIGGLING]
- [BABBLING]
- Shh.
[KYBUCK BRAYING]
[BRAYING CONTINUES]
[SNIFFS]
[BLASTER FIRES]
[BRAYING]
[SPEAKING TOGRUTI]
[KYBUCK SNIFFS, GROANS]
[LABORED BREATHING]
[FUSSING]
You must face death, Ahsoka.
Do not fear it.
[LABORED BREATHING CONTINUES]
[SPEAKING TOGRUTI]
He's a heavy one.
This one will feed many.
Think we can lift it?
[COOING]
Yes. I think so too.
- [GROWLING]
- We never take more than we need.
I shall carry you and the kybuck,
unless you would like to carry him?
[COOING]
[BABBLES]
[LOW GROWLING]
[GROWLS]
[ROARS]
[GROANS]
[ROARING]
- [GROWLS]
- [AHSOKA COOS]
[ROARS]
[PANTING]
[BARKING]
[DROID BEEPS]
[BARKING CONTINUES]
Pav-ti.
[ROARING]
[GIGGLING]
[PAV-TI GRUNTS]
- No! No! Ahsoka!
- [CRYING]
Ahsoka. [SOBBING]
Ahsoka.
[SPEAKING TOGRUTI]
[BABBLING]
[SNEEZES]
[GROWLS, ROARS]
[COOING]
[GROWLING]
I'm sorry, Nak-il.
There's no sign of her or the creature.
We will go out in force.
We will not stop until we find her.
[CREATURE GROWLING]
[ROARS]
Wait.
[COOING]
[SPEAKING TOGRUTI]
Gantika, how could this be?
Jedi. Ahsoka is Jedi.
[COOING]