[JEDI MURMURING]
[BEEPS]
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[BEEPING]
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
Archive memory access.
Please enter security clearance code.
[BEEPING]
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
Code accepted, Master Sifo-Dyas.
Planet Kamino.
[BEEPING]
[ELECTRONIC VOICE]
Kamino location deleted.
Kamino archive data deleted.
[CHATTERING]
What's causing all the excitement,
Master Jocasta?
Your apprentice.
Qui-Gon?
Yes, it would seem
he has encountered a Sith Lord,
or so he claimed to the Jedi High Council.
Where was this encounter?
Tatooine. Yes, I think that was it.
Deep in the Outer Rim, of course.
Qui-Gon Jinn always had
such an active imagination.
As did you, Dooku.
A quality valued less and less
in these great halls.
[CHATTERING]
I guess word travels fast.
Well, your statements to the Council
were rather surprising.
[DOOKU] Qui-Gon.
Master.
I heard of your report to the Council.
Tell me about this mysterious attacker
on Tatooine.
I encountered a highly skilled warrior,
one obviously trained in the Jedi arts.
And you believe it was a Sith Lord?
Yes.
I gather the Council was not eager
to validate that conclusion?
No, they were not, Master.
I've been warning them about
the coming darkness for years,
never to be taken seriously.
Speaking on behalf of the Council,
there's no reason to cause undue alarm.
So, you doubt his claim?
No. I do not.
But the wisdom of the Council is
to be cautious until we know more.
Master Yaddle is right about one thing.
A Sith Lord is not to be trifled with.
And I will not be there to protect you,
my old Padawan.
You need not worry, Master.
Obi-Wan fills that role now.
He acquits himself quite well.
That's good.
I should like to meet him someday.
You're always singing his praises.
Master Dooku, are you all right?
They grow up so fast, our students.
Yes, it is the way of things.
Indeed.
I must take my leave.
I used to bring Qui-Gon here as a boy.
He was fascinated with this tree.
Having been born here on Coruscant,
a planet of steel and stone...
he knew nothing like it.
The Council is leaving for Naboo.
The funeral is to be held there.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
I doubt I will be pleasant company.
You hold them accountable?
Qui-Gon Jinn has become one
with the Force.
It is time to let him go.
And you can do this?
What choice have I?
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[CONTROLS BEEPING]
[SHIP POWERS DOWN]
You've gone too far!
I don't know what you mean.
Qui-Gon Jinn.
You allowed Maul to kill him.
You lost an apprentice, and so did I.
All in service of our greater goals.
The galaxy will not be remade
without sacrifice.
He could've been a powerful ally.
For you, perhaps.
[DOOKU] You question my loyalty?
Always.
I have done everything you asked.
And I will ask more of you,
if we are to succeed.
Sifo-Dyas, Kamino, the Clones.
I have betrayed everyone
and everything I know.
[SIDIOUS] No, you have been loyal
to a greater cause.
How many have died because of my actions?
Such is the price of freedom.
[YADDLE] No!
This ends here, Sith Lord.
So, I have been betrayed?
No!
Dooku, step to me.
Whatever your crimes are, help me now.
Then you heard? You know.
That does not matter.
Don't believe her.
Whatever lies he's told you,
whatever you have done,
you can make up for it now
by bringing him to justice.
[SIDIOUS] Remember what you told me.
The Jedi blindly serve a corrupt Senate
that fails the Republic it represents.
Do you want to prove your loyalty?
Kill her!
There is still a chance
to make things right.
I'm afraid...
I know you are.
I'm afraid it is too late.
[LIGHTSABER IGNITES]
No.
[YADDLE] I am on your side, Dooku.
I stepped down from my position
on the Council.
You were right about so many things.
The Council should've listened.
Qui-Gon did not have to die.
[SIDIOUS CACKLES]
[DOOKU] Running back to your Council?
It is you who has run, Dooku,
into the arms of evil.
[SIDIOUS]
You have done well, my apprentice.
Rise, my friend.
Master.
[RUMBLING]
I want only to bring peace and order
to the galaxy.
Already so many have suffered
for what you call "order".
Then let me give you peace, Master Yaddle.
[LIGHTSABER IMPACTS]