h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
Terror at the Temple!
The Jedi Temple is in disarray
after a vicious terrorist attack.
Anakin Skywalker and Ahsoka Tano
set out to find the truth
of who was really behind
this horrendous catastrophe.
Their investigation led them to discover
the true saboteur, Letta Turmond.
Now, the Jedi attempt to
return the Temple to normalcy.
But first, Master Yoda must give a eulogy
to the fallen Jedi warriors.
One with the Force, they are.
And our job it is
to remember that we will, in time,
also pass on.
Luminous beings are we,
but temporary vessels our bodies are.
And we shall all find ourselves here,
in time.
A moment of silence, I ask.
To remember and to move on.
You were close to one of them?
Tutso Mara. We trained together.
He taught me how to hold
my lightsaber correctly.
Live for the living Jedi, we must.
Live through us, forever they will.
So what happens to Letta now?
The bomber has been moved.
Moved? Where?
Why should she be moved?
The Republic military
has taken her into custody.
Ugh ! But why? This is a Jedi matter, isn't it?
Clones were killed,
which makes this terrorist attack
a military matter.
An attack on the Jedi
is an attack on the Senate.
Admiral Tarkin is right. Letta isn't a Jedi.
It's not for us to be judge and jury
over a citizen of the Republic.
If Letta's guilty, she's guilty,
and she should be dealt with.
Calm down, Ahsoka.
Remember, revenge is not the Jedi way.
The evidence seems clear, Ahsoka.
Nothing will ever change.
The Chancellor feels very strongly
that the Jedi be removed
from as many military matters as possible.
You yourselves said
that you're peacekeepers,
not soldiers.
I hope Chancellor Palpatine
knows what he's doing.
I assure you that he rarely does anything
without a strategy.
I have many things to attend to, Masters.
Good day.
Ahsoka.
Go, be with your friend, Ahsoka.
In ways, she is still very young.
Indeed.
-Company?
-Sure.
Every time I think about this,
I feel conflicted.
It's hard not to let feelings
turn into attachment and pain.
Ahsoka, have you ever wondered if
it was right to ignore your emotions?
My master would say our struggle as Jedi
is to move past them.
You make it sound so easy.
No, it isn't easy. But it's possible.
Like when we were stuck inside
the battle tank on Geonosis.
It was hard not to be afraid.
Still, you and I got past it.
And I guess we'll get past this.
You've always been capable
of seeing things clearly.
I guess I fooled you
like I have everyone else.
Yes, Master.
Ahsoka,
we're needed in the War Room.
It appears the Separatists
have mounted another attack.
Coming, Master.
Look, I have to believe
that, one way or another,
this woman's going to pay for what she did.
You shouldn't keep your master waiting.
We've uncovered
a Separatist plan of attack.
We shall travel to the A no it system here,
then move across to Saleucami.
So far out of our way?
Unfortunately we must avoid
these neutral systems.
Excuse me, Master Jedi.
Yes, Admiral.
Commander Tano, your presence
is requested by prisoner Letta Turmond.
The prisoner from the hangar bombing?
Why is she asking for Ahsoka?
Not exactly sure.
But Commander Tano is the only person
the prisoner will speak to.
I'll report back with whatever I find out.
Yes?
I'm Commander Tano.
Letta Turmond requested to see me.
A lot of innocent people died in that blast.
Good job capturing her.
All right, scan her.
Leave your com link and lightsabers here.
Follow me.
What do you want, Letta?
I was told if I ever needed help,
you were the Jedi to contact.
Give us a minute, please.
You don't have much time, Letta,
so I suggest you get
whatever you have to say off your chest.
The idea of feeding Jackar
the nano-droids was not mine.
Why are you saying this now?
Why didn't you reveal this before?
Because my life is in danger.
The person behind this
will be able to get to me
unless you know the truth.
Hmm. What's the truth?
A Jedi.
A Jedi showed me how to create the bomb
and how to put the nano-droids in.
Why would a Jedi do this?
There are some citizens
of the Republic, like myself,
who believe the Jedi Order
is not what it used to be.
The Jedi have become warmongers.
They've become military weapons,
and they're killing
when they should be keeping the peace.
One of these Jedi agreed with us.
One of you wanted to make a statement,
and was willing to attack
your own order to do it.
Who?
If you protect me, I will tell you.
Because it is obvious to me
that I have been set up!
Letta, you have to tell me
who is behind this.
It's...
Letta? Letta!
Letta!
Prisoner health critical. Holding cell 1-7-3.
Commander Fox, the prisoner!
Follow me.
Letta!
I don't know what happened.
Commander, she's dead.
I can't say I blame you, Commander Tano,
but all the same, you're under arrest.
I... No, no, I did not do this!
Admiral Tarkin,
I don't know what happened.
I went in the room to talk to Letta
and she said she was afraid of a Jedi.
You don't have to tell me
any more, Commander Tano.
-I don't?
-No.
There are recorders in every room.
Curiously, the sound isn't working
on this one.
It seems the Jedi she was afraid of
was you.
I did not kill that woman!
You were the only one there!
I know that you were upset
when this woman
was taken into custody by the military.
That means nothing!
I beg to differ.
It was someone else, Admiral !
Someone I didn't see!
You know that is very difficult
for me to believe.
This is a secure facility.
We do not have just anyone running about.
And if there was someone else,
why did you not sense them?
I said my Padawan is in there.
Now step aside.
General Skywalker,
Admiral Tarkin has ordered
that no one be allowed in there.
I don't care what she's accused of.
Let me in.
Sorry, sir. The Admiral's orders stand.
This is now a military operation,
and under his jurisdiction.
A key card?
Master, I knew you wouldn't let me down.
I wonder what you have planned.
Oh, no, this does not look good.
My lightsabers?
Hello? Who is this?
Why are you helping me?
-What's going on here?
-It wasn't me!
Alert! Alert!
The Jedi prisoner has escaped!
Commander Tano, stop!
She's heading north in the prison corridor.
Cut her off!
Copy that.
Oh, no.
Suspect has killed three clones. Code red!
If you see the target, shoot to kill.
Belay that order, Commander Fox!
She's killed troopers!
I know Commander Tano.
She would never do something like this.
-Then who did?
-Quiet!
Ahsoka! It's me, Anakin !
Stop running!
You can't help me, Master.
Someone's setting me up!
I believe you, Ahsoka!
But no one else will!
Keep searching until we find her.
Rex, call security.
Tell them we need to search
the entire base. Now!
General Skywalker has just issued
an all-points bulletin
on Commander Ahsoka Tano.
She's killed three clones
and should be considered
armed and dangerous.
The prisoner was just spotted
in the east wing.
Cell block 1218-11.
Come on, Grizzer,
there's nothing here.
There she is! Quick!
Stop her before she gets to the ship!
All right, don't lose her.
We'll be right there.
- What's going on?
- We've found her.
She's heading towards
the industrial pipeline.
Set weapons to stun. I want her alive!
Do not shoot to kill ! Do not shoot to kill!
Try to box her in ! Don't let her escape!
Tell me what you see, Odd Ball.
She's moving west
along the central viaduct.
All right, we've got her now.
This'll knock her off her feet!
Not so fast, Commander!
Ahsoka!
Ahsoka, what are you doing?
You didn't even try to come and help me!
They wouldn't let me in to talk to you!
You could have if you'd tried!
How would that look, Ahsoka? Huh?
Forcing my way in
would've made you look even more guilty.
I'm not guilty!
Then we have to prove you're innocent.
The only way we can do that
is by going back.
I don't know who to trust.
Listen, I would never let anyone
hurt you, Ahsoka. Never.
But you need to come back
and make your case to the Council.
No! I'm not going to take the fall
for something I didn't do!
I am ordering you to put down
your lightsaber and come with me! Now!
Trust me.
General Skywalker, where are you?
I do trust you.
But you know as well as I do
that no one else will believe me.
Anakin, you have to trust me now.
Ahsoka, I do trust you!
I know you do.
Wish me luck.
http://hiqve.com/