h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
Ancient Jedi tradition!
Six younglings are sent to the secret
caverns of llum
where they are tested by The Gathering,
an ancient Jedi ritual where
each youngling must harvest a crystal,
around which they will construct
their own lightsaber.
Along the journey
they underwent great perils,
hardest of which was to face themselves.
Now, having passed the test,
they take their first step
into a larger world.
I call that move the Whirlwind of Destiny.
Show-off.
Can everyone gather around, please?
You have all successfully passed
The Gathering
and harvested your crystals.
So, when do we start to build our sabers?
Place your crystals on the table.
Your lesson begins now.
May I introduce you to architect
and lightsaber designer, Huyang.
These are them?
I swear they get younger every expedition.
All have passed The Gathering?
Yes, sir.
Are you sure?
But he's a droid.
You expect us to learn from a droid?
Who said that?
Many years I have been on this ship
teaching many a Jedi before you,
and I will continue teaching
many a Jedi after you.
Call me what you want,
but inside my memory banks,
I contain a record
of every lightsaber ever made
-and the Jedi who fashioned them.
-Whoa!
- Look at that!
- Which will you choose,
a simple grip, the curved approach,
one inlaid with the bone
of the Cartusion whale,
pastillion ore or black onk? Well?
From Battles of Rashfond,
to the Peacekeeping of Parliock,
to our very own Clone Wars,
the lightsaber is a Jedi's only true ally.
But how do they work?
Yes, you have brought me crystals,
but they're all useless
unless you give them life.
Do you know how to awaken the Force
within the crystal?
No?
Then I suggest you listen and learn
until you think of a question
this droid cannot answer.
A Wookiee.
Rare, you are to the Jedi.
Proud, your people must be.
Unique, just as your lightsaber will be.
Hold out your hand, Wookiee.
Describe what you see your saber to be.
No, no, no, not what you imagine,
but what feel in your hand.
Concentrate.
What will make you strong in battle
and humble in retreat?
What connects with your Force?
Yes, wood. Not a common choice.
And only wood from the Brylark tree
is as strong as metal.
Let me see. Where would we find that
all the way out here, far from anywhere,
deep in space?
Let's see what we have. Let me see.
No, no, no.
Ah. I wondered where I'd put that.
Oh. That's not mine.
Ah ! Ah!
What do we have here?
Look at that!
You can say that again.
Wow.
It is my job that before you leave this ship,
you will have everything you need
to build your lightsabers
and the knowledge of how to do it.
So let us begin.
There is much more work to be done.
Well, where are they?
The Jedi ship is right in front of us, sir.
Lose them,
and you'll lose more than your head.
Our attack must be swift and devastating.
They cannot have time to get away.
I thought we weren't going to mess
with Jedi anymore.
These aren't Jedi.
My sources say they're just younglings
headed back to the Jedi Temple
from a training mission.
With the most important treasure
in the universe,
kyber crystals,
used for making laser swords.
The price for just one
would make a man rich!
And we all know how much
I like to be rich, don't we?
What's the rush, Petro?
With this lightsaber, I'm going
to challenge Obi-Wan Kenobi to a duel
and kill Grievous.
The only person you are going to kill
with that, my young friend, is yourself.
You have inverted the emitter matrix
which will cause the power grid to backfire.
Light this, and all that will be left
of you and your lightsaber
will be your crystal.
Start again.
And this time, please follow the diagram.
Remember, quiet your mind
and concentrate.
The design will become clear.
Good. Gently. Trust the Force.
What was that?
I don't know. Hold on.
Artoo, what's happened?
Where?
Oh, no.
They're aiming
for the hyperdrive. Get us out of here!
I don't like the sound of that.
Stay here. I'll check on the younglings.
Excellent shot.
Fire the grappling harpoons!
Now, reel them in,
and let's get what we came for.
What's happening?
We're being boarded.
Here! Why?
I don't know.
Quickly, give me your crystals,
and I will hold onto them until we are safe.
Younglings! Younglings!
-Who's attacking the ship?
-Pirates.
Pirates! They'll kill us all.
Perhaps we should hide
in the ventilation shaft.
Follow me.
Hiding is for cowards.
We should stand and fight.
We're going to fight.
Just not the way they expect.
Time to go.
Is this part of our training?
It is now.
Shh.
Hondo says find the kids
and bring them to him.
Dead or alive?
Yes.
We must have courage, young Jedi.
Ganodi and Zatt, I need you to get
to the cockpit, find Artoo, and secure it.
The rest of you, take Professor Huyang,
and seal yourselves inside the hold
and wait for my command.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to reroute enough power
to the engines
so that we can break free
of the pirate ship's hold on us, okay?
What about the pirates
already on board the ship?
Once the docking tube is ruptured,
when the ships pull apart,
a vacuum will be created
which will suck the pirates off our ship
and into space.
-Will we be sucked into space?
-No.
The cockpit and the hold
will be sealed and still have air.
Do not, and I mean do not,
engage the pirates.
Your only job is to stay hidden.
Do you understand?
Now go.
I smell profit! Ha ha!
Nice, juicy, fat, warm profits.
Well?
We've secured the ship,
but she seems deserted.
Imbecile!
That is the oldest trick in the book.
The runts are probably hiding
in the ventilation system.
Oh, right, didn't think of that.
Why does that not surprise me?
All that matters is you find the younglings
and bring me the crystals.
If anything gets in the way, kill it!
But, boss, they're just kids.
"They're just kids."
When will they learn?
In case you lack motivation,
remember that on the black market
these crystals are priceless.
We can't fit in there!
Smoke them out!
You heard the boss.
I do love me a party.
Hold it!
Ah!
-Get off him.
-Easy there.
That's no way to make friends, now, is it?
Thanks, buddy.
Come on, keep up.
The hold is not much further.
Something's wrong.
Unhand me, brigand!
Well, hello, girls and boys.
We've been looking forward
to meeting you.
Now be nice and hand over your crystals.
Over my dead body.
That can be arranged.
Petro, no.
Your emitter matrix is still inverted.
So, which one of you is first?
All bark, no bite.
Ah.
That's for me.
I always wanted one of these.
You sure you can handle it?
Everybody get down.
Let's go!
Hurry! Hurry! This way, younglings!
You could've killed him.
Look, we can keep running,
or we can stand and fight
and show these pirates we're not afraid!
I cannot approve of such action.
Besides, I have been damaged
and cannot aid you in battle.
Petro's right. It's our only choice.
Fight or be killed.
Zatt, come in.
I am overriding
the emergency power fail-safe
and routing energy to the engines.
It's working.
Any word from the others?
Have they reached the hold?
-Uh, not yet.
-Where are they?
I don't know. I didn't hear from them.
Great. I know what that means.
Set them to the highest level.
Get him.
Gungi!
Here, kiddie kiddies.
You can come out now, innit?
No one's gonna hurt you.
Zatt, close the door to the training room.
Katooni! Where are you guys?
No time to explain. Just close the door!
Artoo, close the door!
Hey, what's going on?
We can't make it.
There are too many blocking the hold.
Well, children,
you have put up quite a fight,
but playtime is over.
Now, hand over my crystals,
and no one gets hurt much.
Hondo, the Jedi Council will not take kindly
to this attack.
Ahsoka.
How will they know who is responsible
if there is no one left to tell the tale?
You seem less hospitable
than our last meeting.
My mood is based on profit,
and today, I am in the mood for crystals.
You want the crystals, come and get them!
Easy now!
Hurry, hurry!
What about Ahsoka?
Trust her. Now get in there!
Oh!
How dare you!
I've lived on this ship 1,000 years
and never lost a fight.
I'm not about to start today.
Ah!
You know, had I known you were here,
I would have simply asked
for the crystals directly,
and we could have avoided all of this.
I don't want to hurt you, Hondo.
I know and, and I appreciate that.
We're all in the hold,
but Ahsoka's still out there
fighting the pirates.
Ahsoka, Ahsoka, come in.
They've made it to the hold.
Then what are you waiting for?
But what about you?
Do it!
What are you doing?
Getting you off my ship.
Whoa!
We're all clear.
Make the jump to hyperspace.
Yes! We did it! They're off the ship!
Oh, Professor.
Bring him here. I'll fix him.
You should have seen Ahsoka.
She took them all on by herself!
Where is Padawan Tano?
Padawan Tano, come in.
Ahsoka?
Ahsoka? Ahsoka, are you there?
You have cost me greatly today, young one.
And since you lost me so much profit,
I am left with no choice
But to turn you into
profit.
Good night.
http://hiqve.com/