h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
A flaw in the plan!
While in the middle of a heated battle,
Clone Trooper Tup lost his senses
and killed a Jedi general.
Seeming to have
no awareness of his actions,
Tup's health
began to deteriorate rapidly.
Fearing the illness was
linked to a Separatist plot,
Anakin Skywalker has dispatched
Captain Rex and ARC Trooper 5555
to escort Tup back
to the cloning facilities on Kamino
for an intensive evaluation.
You will have to say goodbye
to your friend now.
Yes, Doctor.
General Shaak Ti.
Captain Rex.
Fives. Am I correct?
Yes, General.
You've served with Tup?
Yes.
You must come with me.
With... With all due respect, General,
I can't just abandon him now.
You must let the doctors do their work.
Do not be afraid.
Your friend is in quite capable hands.
Dr. Nala Se is
the Chief Medical Scientist on Kamino.
She was one of the primary engineers
of all the clones.
Now, we must take care of you.
Me? There's nothing
wrong with me, General.
I'm perfectly fine.
We can't be sure of that
until we've completed a full exam.
If a virus was
the cause of Tup's breakdown,
you have more than likely
been exposed to the contagion.
You haven't entered
the advanced stages yet, as Tup has,
but any information
we can gather from you
could help to find a cure for Tup.
All right, General, if it'll help Tup.
Captain Rex, General Skywalker has
ordered you back to the war zone.
You are to leave immediately.
I'm sorry, Fives.
I wish I could stay, but duty calls.
It's fine, sir.
Fighting a virus is a nice
change of pace from all those clankers.
Take care of yourself,
and Tup.
Let's begin the tests.
Administer the stimulant.
Remove his mask.
What are they doing to Tup?
Remain calm.
Out of my way!
Please return to the examination table.
His reactions are normal.
What's going on? General!
General!
No, no, no!
Please return to the examination table.
Come on!
Remain calm.
Please return to the exam...
His reaction will subside.
The patient must be awake
for the next round of tests.
I am not fond of these hyper tests.
Yes, but they do give us all the
information we need in a timely fashion.
There does not seem to be
any sign of infection in the blood.
How curious.
The subject has tested
negative on all accounts.
This clone seems to be
in perfect health.
We must be missing something.
Why am I here?
Is he conscious?
Follow orders!
Kill Jedi. Kill Jedi!
Are you finished with your tests?
For now.
Sedate him.
Yes, ma'am.
Orders. Follow orders. Follow orders.
Follow orders.
It appears this clone
has orders to kill a Jedi.
Perhaps the Separatists found
a way to brainwash him.
Look, is Tup going to be all right?
Have they found anything out?
Please, sit down.
We are using hyper tests, so we should
be getting the results very quickly.
We need to complete
more procedures on you.
-Sorry.
-Why?
-Hey!
-I said I was sorry.
You must understand,
organic beings are so much harder
to analyze than droids.
Well?
Everything seems normal.
Great!
Well, that means they can let me out.
I am afraid that is not possible.
You must remain quarantined
until we have pinpointed the exact
cause of the other clone's breakdown.
We cannot risk any further casualties.
Look, I am not a threat,
and neither is Tup!
Are you certain?
You're just a droid.
You don't know about real duty,
about what it's like to have a brother.
I am sorry.
I always wanted
to have human feelings,
but I do not. Goodbye.
Maybe whatever is causing
his aggression is psychological.
It seems to be an isolated case.
The other clone has yet
to display any symptoms.
I need an answer now.
This isn't just
a physical manifestation of psychosis.
You must have missed something.
Might I suggest a second brain scan,
an atomic-level brain scan?
This is unnecessary.
The Phase 1 and 2 scans we did
are sufficient.
He's too weak
for a Phase 5 atomic-level scan.
I calculate the beneficial knowledge we
could gain from a Phase 5 atomic scan
is worth the risk.
The only way to discover
what has happened to this clone
is to terminate him
and do a full-scale autopsy
on the molecular level.
We must be cautious.
I do not believe
this is a physical ailment,
but a mental condition caused
by possible Separatist brainwashing.
I do not agree.
This is a virus of some kind.
I am in charge of this examination
and I will decide
what is best for my patient.
Actually, since the Republic and
the Jedi commissioned the clones,
it is our responsibility
to oversee their care.
Every clone and their genetic makeup
is property of
the Kaminoan government.
Now, as a client of ours,
I will respect your wishes,
but as to the fate of this clone,
I will speak to
our Prime Minister, Lama Su.
And I will advise the Jedi Council
on the atomic brain scan
and see how they would like to proceed.
Very well.
-Hello.
-What's going on?
CT-5385's condition
seems to be deteriorating.
Tup. His name is Tup.
Tup? What is a Tup?
Tup is my friend. He's not a number.
Yes, he is. We all have numbers.
My number is
AZ-345211896246498721347.
His number is CT-5385.
Wrong. He has a name.
No clone uses a number.
Not anymore.
But you are a number, CT-5555.
No, I am Fives. Call me Fives.
But five is a number.
No, not five. Fives.
The difference is minimal.
Not to me. And not to any clone.
It appears there has been a preemptive
execution of Clone Protocol 66.
How did this happen?
I do not know as of yet.
However, I recommend
we terminate the clone
and do a full autopsy to discover
how the inhibitor chip was activated.
And what of the Jedi?
The Jedi Shaak Ti is proposing
an atomic-level brain scan.
She has gone to the Jedi Council to
seek their approval before proceeding.
We must contact Lord Tyranus.
I've been expecting your transmission.
I have heard
of the malfunctioning clone.
How widespread is the problem?
It seems to be an isolated incident.
However, this is a delicate situation.
We need to terminate the clone
as soon as possible
in order to extract and analyze the
inhibitor chip that you provided to us.
Very good.
Terminate the clone immediately.
However, send the chip
to me for analysis.
And what if the Jedi ask for the chip
and the results of the autopsy?
You must remember,
the chip is a safeguard
against betrayal from rogue Jedi.
Master Sifo-Dyas
was the only Jedi who knew of this.
But with his passing,
we alone know of this secret
and you must keep it that way.
Yes, Lord Tyranus.
These Jedi are a curious cult.
Too spiritual for my taste.
I will terminate the clone immediately.
The Kaminoans have suggested
that we terminate the clone
and do a rigorous molecular autopsy
to discover the virus.
I believe this solution is ill-advised.
My belief is that Tup has been
brainwashed by the Separatists
using some new process
we do not yet understand.
Brainwashing?
How could that be possible?
General Skywalker reported
Tup missing on Ringo Vinda,
but after five rotations
he turned up again.
That event preceded this episode.
Perhaps he was compromised
at that point.
We must find the truth
behind this situation,
or we could find many more clones
turned against us.
I would like to implement
a Level 5 atomic brain scan,
to see if his thought processes
are still functioning normally.
And what do
the Kaminoans think of that?
They feel Tup is so weak,
the Level 5 atomic brain scan
would damage his neural tissue
and possibly kill him.
Their approach
would be to terminate him,
thus leaving the brain
fully intact for the autopsy.
Bring Clone Trooper Tup
back to the Jedi Temple.
Yes. Examine him
with the Force we shall,
and unravel this mystery we will.
Yes, Master.
I'll bring him back immediately.
No! There's too much
procedure and protocol here!
Tup is a soldier.
He risks his life every day,
and I know he would risk it now
if it meant finding a cure
for what's wrong with him.
I recommended an atomic brain scan,
but that request has
thus far has been denied.
Then we have to get the results
of that brain scan ourselves.
But that is against protocol.
Think about it.
It's your duty to save the patient, right?
That is correct.
And you recommended
this atomic brain scan
as the best way
to save the patient, right?
That is correct.
So, by not performing this scan,
you are letting the patient die, willingly.
Impossible.
That is against my programming.
That's not the way it looks to me.
I cannot perform the atomic brain scan
without disobeying orders.
Check your programming.
I thought saving the patient at all costs
was fundamentally your highest order.
You are correct.
Right. Then let's get to it!
Quickly!
Okay, let's get to work.
The scan is almost complete.
Everything appears to be normal.
Wait a second.
What? What is it?
It appears this clone
has developed a tumor.
Is that even possible?
I have never witnessed
anything like this in your kind.
Well, then, what is it?
I cannot be sure without a biopsy.
You're gonna take it out of him?
What was that?
Do you think anybody heard that?
The probability that somebody
heard that is high, yes.
It came from this room.
Hello, Doctor.
What do you think you're doing?
I was only following protocol.
"Save the patient."
Doctor, I have found something unusual
in this scan.
It appears to be a tumor.
Perhaps you should take a look.
You performed a second scan
without my authorization?
As I stated,
I was following my programming.
Then you are like this clone, defective!
You will be put on report
for deactivation.
But the tumor...
This tumor seems to be
blocking neuro-impulses
from communicating within the brain.
We should scan the rest of the clones
to see if this is a problem
with their base genetic model
or a mutation with the current models.
There is no tumor.
Your scan is incorrect.
But...
This clone clearly has
a virus that remains undetected,
but I will find the cause
once he's terminated.
Now leave.
I can't believe it.
They're going to kill him.
In a case like this,
it is the logical course of action.
No! No! We were not created
to be disposed of this way!
Perhaps you were.
CT-5385 will be terminated
so that others like him could survive.
There aren't others like him.
Tup doesn't have to die.
You found a tumor.
I'm sure that's the cause of all this.
It's the only thing that makes sense.
But how can we proceed?
Do your biopsy.
I'm sure what you find
will prove Tup does not have to die.
But Nala Se does not believe...
We're not going to Nala Se
with whatever you find.
We'll go to the General, to Shaak Ti.
She helped me once, as a cadet.
I know she values the life of a clone.
But we will be disobeying direct orders.
Yep, for the second time today.
Can you hack into
the medical center's mainframe?
I do possess that ability, yes.
All right.
Well, here's what you need to do.
It will be a painless death.
Soon all our questions
will be answered.
You may proceed.
Hurry! You got it? Are you in?
Got it.
Intruder alert! Intruder alert!
All non-essential personnel
report to a safe room for lockdown.
Master Jedi, status report?
Scanners have picked up
an intruder in section C-6,
but we have no visual confirmation.
It could be the enemy
looking for our patient.
I'm on my way.
Please report to a secure room.
Good work, AZI.
You better get started
before they figure out it's a false alarm.
Right away.
You might want to turn away
for this part.
I want a report.
It appears to be a false alarm,
triggered from the medical bay.
Medical bay?
It's Fives! Come on!
Is it done?
It is now.
What have you done?
We've saved my friend's life.
This tumor is the cause of his illness.
Give me that.
You can't be trusted.
Stand down, Trooper.
General. I have evidence, it's right here!
I'm free. The mission... Free...
-Tup.
-The mission... Free.
The mission...
What is he saying?
Brother, what mission?
You... You know the one.
The mission, the one in our dreams,
that never ends.
The one in our dreams...
Brother,
this is the end.
Forget the mission.
The nightmare...
I'm free.
No. No.
I thought I saved him.
Sir, the clone CT-5385 has died.
Such a tragedy.
I recommend we do further tests
on this tumor at the Jedi Temple,
to see if it is the cause of the problem.
Or even better,
have the tumor sent
to the Grand Republic Medical Facility
here on Coruscant.
The Jedi Council requested the clone...
I think the Chancellor is correct.
The Grand Medical Facility
is state-of-the-art.
If we are to find an answer to
this puzzle, we will find it there.
We are in agreement then?
Yes, sir.
http://hiqve.com/