h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
The final surge!
Having learned
of warlord Poggle the Lesser's plot
to rebuild a Separatist droid foundry
on Geonosis,
Jedi Knight Anakin Skywalker
and his Padawan, Ahsoka Tano,
prepare to assault
this heavily fortified installation.
Their mission,
destroy the factory at all cost.
Anticipating stiff resistance,
Republic commanders send
Jedi Master Luminara Unduli
and her Padawan, Barriss Offee,
to reinforce the attack.
But time runs short for our intrepid heroes
as the dreaded droid mill
nears completion.
Captain, the only safe landing zone
is south of Skywalker's position.
Yes, General.
Barriss, l assume
you've made the necessary preparations.
Precisely as you instructed, Master.
Buckle your belts and
check your cells, soldiers. We're going in.
This bridge is our first waypoint.
Focus your fire on the gun emplacements,
here and here, because it's only...
Because it's only
after we neutralize the guns
- that we can push for the factory.
- l was...
Yes, we can push for the factory.
Now, expect stiff resistance from...
And don't forget to top off
your energy cells and ration packs.
Once we leave, there'll be no resupply.
Anything else, Ahsoka?
No. l think you've pretty much
covered everything
in my briefing.
Very well. Squad dismissed.
Okay. What's next?
You know, Master,
my briefings might go better
if you didn't interrupt me
every time l tried to...
l wasn't interrupting.
l was trying to help you.
Which l would appreciate,
if you didn't interrupt me to do it.
l just think maybe you don't trust me
to give the briefing.
lt's not about trust.
lt's about getting the job done right.
So you don't trust me
to get the job done right! l knew it!
- Snips, l never said...
- No. No, it's okay. l understand.
l'm the Padawan, you're the Master.
Good day, General.
Skywalker's waiting for you.
- At it again, are they?
- Again, Master?
Let's just say that they have a penchant
for playing loose
- with regulations and rules of command.
- Yeah, but when l say it,
- they actually listen to me.
- Well, if you don't trust me,
- then maybe you should send me back.
- Don't tempt me, Snips.
lf you're both finished
with your little discussion,
we do have a factory to destroy.
Well, Barriss?
Aren't you going to introduce yourself?
Padawan learner Barriss Offee
at your service.
Glad to meet you. l'm Ahsoka.
lt's good to see both of you again.
l wish it was
under more peaceful circumstances.
A frontal assault is risky.
Our losses will be high.
But not as high as they'll be
if that factory comes online.
lndeed, but there is an alternative.
Every Geonosian building has a series
of catacombs beneath it
that run deep underground.
Some of the tunnels are close enough
to this cliff wall
so that you could cut a hole
and make an entry point.
Once inside,
we could find the main reactor,
plant the explosives
and blow the factory inside out.
Well, looks like a good way to get lost,
if you ask me.
For the unprepared, perhaps.
But l have instructed Barriss to memorize
the labyrinth, all 200 junctions.
You always were thorough.
lt pays for one to be prepared.
Right, Barriss?
Especially when other people's lives
depend on your success.
How do we keep the Geonosians occupied
while someone else is setting the bombs?
Good point, Snips. lf whoever is going
in there is going to be successful,
we'll need to create a diversion.
Precisely. That task will be carried out
by you and l, Skywalker,
while the destruction of the factory
falls to the Padawans.
Now, hold on. Who decided that?
Walking into that factory could be suicide.
Not if you and l are successful
holding Poggle's attention at the bridge.
Master, l can do this!
l've had riskier assignments.
But unlike Barriss,
you aren't prepared for this mission.
Not to worry, my Padawan is reliable.
She can lead them both through the maze.
We'll be in and out, Master.
See? Dependable Barriss
will get us through.
Don't worry, Master.
As you well know, l can follow orders.
lt's decided, then.
l guess it is.
We'll monitor your progress
on these chronometers.
Synchronize on my mark. Three, two, one,
mark.
Let's get going. After you, Barriss.
You feel Ahsoka is not up to the task?
- l never said that.
- What is it, then?
Nothing. Let's prepare the men.
We'll have to make a bold move
if we're to draw them out of the factory
and keep their attention on us
and not the Padawans.
The best way to do that is to
march our troops straight up the middle,
parade style. They can't resist that.
- With no cover?
- Well, we have to make it tempting.
The factory is operating
at 50% production capacity.
We have 10 garrisons of new droids
ready to deploy.
No, the Super Tanks are not ready,
but when they are,
the Republic forces will be routed.
They have no weapon
that can penetrate its heavy armor.
Here come the droids. Everybody steady.
Steady. Keep marching.
l hope the Padawans have made it
past the bridge by now.
- That looks like a lot of droids.
- Well, it is a droid factory.
As long as we can destroy them
faster than they can make them,
we'll come out on top.
l love
your simple logic, Skywalker.
Here we go!
Let them fall into the trap.
You may now commence attack.
- Nice work. Well, here goes nothing.
- l should go in first. l know the way.
Be my guest.
- They're sleeping.
- We have to find another way.
We don't have time.
This direction is the fastest.
- Maybe you're wrong.
- Trust me.
Ahsoka. Ahsoka!
They should have entered the catacombs
by now.
l sure hope they're not lost down there.
Left at the next junction.
- Dead end.
- lf we make a wrong turn,
we may never find our way out.
You do remember the way, don't you?
Of course l do.
lt's not left. lt's up.
lt's this way.
- Rex! A little help here.
- Get up there, trooper!
My lord, l beg you
to let us use the secret weapons.
We have 20 units ready now
and many more on the way.
Thank you, my lord.
Deploy the Super Tanks. Attack formation.
- Looks like the Separatists have a new toy.
- Rex, pick your targets.
Yes, sir. Elevation 427.
Whoa! That's a lot of droids.
Come on.
The main control room is this way.
Steady. Steady. Fire!
Our shields are holding.
They can't touch us.
That's a relief.
- Sir, nothing could withstand that.
- They must be ray-shielded.
This is it. We're here.
Two Jedi in the control room?
That is impossible.
How could they have gotten past security?
And now, we make ourselves scarce.
Green light. The bombs are active!
- The Padawans did it.
- And just in time!
Fire!
Get down!
You heard His Highness.
Collect their pathetic little bombs,
then we will kill them.
See if your stupid tank can take this.
Fool.
The Super Tank is impervious
to all weapons.
Rex! Tell the men to fall back!
But, sir, you can't be asking us
to turn tail and run!
l'm not asking you to run, Rex.
l wanna draw those tanks out
onto the bridge.
- l see what you have in mind.
- l always come prepared, Master. Let's go!
The bombs!
Stupid green bugger!
Fall back! Fall back!
Give everything you've got.
- Uh-oh.
- Roger, roger.
Where are they? Those bombs
are gonna go off any second now.
Rex, any sign ofAhsoka or Barriss
on your side?
No, sir.
But this place is getting ready to blow.
The evacuation ships are arriving.
l suggest you get on one.
- Not without Ahsoka.
- My Padawan will not fail.
Ahsoka, can you hear me?
Ahsoka, where are you?
Where did she go?
- The bugs took the bombs.
- What are we gonna do now?
l don't know what to do
without the bombs.
Well, this tank could destroy
the power generator,
- and probably us along with it.
- l guess that's our only choice.
Master, can you hear me?
- Master!
- Ahsoka, set off the bombs! We're trapped!
- l'm sorry, Master. We can't make it out.
- Can't make it out?
- Ahsoka, wait!
- Fire!
Get down! Get down!
Ahsoka.
Ahsoka! Can you hear me? Come in!
- Master Luminara, don't worry.
- Be at ease, Skywalker.
At ease? We need to act now!
Ahsoka and Barriss may still be alive
down there.
There's not enough time.
l sense them drifting away.
No. We'll get them out.
The tank lifters are here to move
the debris as ordered, General.
Get to it, Rex.
- How deep do you think we're buried?
- lt's probably best not to think about it.
Hand me that power cell, would you?
- Thanks. Mind holding the light?
- Whatever you're doing, l hope it works,
because l'd sure rather have died fighting
up there than starve to death down here.
Don't worry, we'll run out of air
long before we starve.
That's a comforting thought. Thanks.
Master Skywalker has taught me
a trick or two.
l think l can get
this communicator working.
We cannot abandon our Padawans.
You misjudge me.
l, too, care for my apprentice.
- But if their time has come...
- l refuse to let Ahsoka die.
She will find a way out.
lf my Padawan has perished,
l will mourn her,
but l will celebrate her as well
through her memory.
Well, l still plan on celebrating this victory
with my Padawan, in person.
What happens to us now doesn't matter.
By destroying this factory,
- we've saved countless lives elsewhere.
- Well, l'm about to save two more.
Wait. l'm picking up a pulse
on Ahsoka's comm channel.
lt's coming from over there.
Master, l know you're up there,
and l know you're looking for me.
- l'll move the heavy machinery over, sir.
- No time!
Someone's digging!
- Barriss!
- Ahsoka!
l knew they were still alive.
l told you we shouldn't give up on them.
lt's not that l gave up, Skywalker,
but unlike you, when the time comes,
l am prepared to let my student go.
Can you say the same?
- l knew you'd come looking for me.
- l never doubted you for a second.
- Padawan, you did well.
- Thank you, Master.
But if it weren't for Ahsoka,
we'd still be down there.
lndeed.
Your Master never lost faith in you.
http://hiqve.com/