h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
Jedi mystery!
A lightsaber was found
on the moon of Oba Diah,
belonging to Sifo-Dyas,
the Jedi responsible for
the creation of the clone army.
The Jedi have learned
that before the start of the war
Count Dooku murdered Sifo-Dyas
and skillfully manipulated the Republic
into the galactic conflict
intending for the Jedi to fight
with the clones at their side.
Now, as the Jedi Council meets to
discuss the purpose of this deception,
Master Yoda meditates deep into
the Force in search of answers.
Yoda.
Hear you I do.
Who are you?
My imagination it must be.
No.
It is I, Qui-Gon Jinn.
That cannot be. Dead you are.
No. I am part of the living Force, Yoda.
Impossible.
I am not sure this Council is admitting
how grave a situation we are in.
What are you saying?
That Dooku is not the Sith Lord,
merely an apprentice.
That, like many things,
remains unclear.
Master Yoda, your thoughts
on these revelations?
Yes, yes.
Forgive me, deep in thought I was.
You were saying?
Master Ki-Adi-Mundi is worried.
Yes, worried we all should be.
Lies and mistrust surround us
in the Senate
and perhaps even within these walls.
On the precipice we are. Yes.
The growing dark side
endangers us all.
Excuse me, everyone.
Master Kenobi,
may I speak with you in private?
Of course.
There is great turmoil
within Master Yoda.
Yes. We all sensed it.
For something to affect Yoda
this deeply concerns me.
We must keep an eye on our old friend.
The war has taxed all of us to our limit.
I suppose we're just surprised
that Master Yoda has one.
I hope it's that simple.
But I feel the shadow of something
greater on our horizon.
Yoda.
Master Yoda. Sorry,
I didn't see you there.
Is everything okay?
Encountered something difficult I have.
Difficult? For you, Master?
Spoke with Master Qui-Gon Jinn
on Mortis did you not?
Yes, so did Obi-Wan.
However, since he's dead,
we don't think it was actually him.
Rather an illusion. A mind trick
formed out of our memories.
That's what Obi-Wan believes.
Why do you ask?
Perhaps nothing it is.
Everything that we know about
the Force tells us
that an individual retaining their identity
after death is impossible.
Everything that we know, yes.
But what about what we know not?
Master Yoda, are you suggesting that
you have spoken with Master Qui-Gon?
Suggest this I am not.
Rest I need. Yes, rest.
Then speak with the Council I shall.
Sense something that I have not before.
Impossible it seems.
Trust my feelings I do not.
The voice I hear
does not come from within,
but speaks from beyond.
Know I must if I am alone,
or if any of you can hear it as well.
Then together we shall meditate.
Hear the voice I did not.
I also sensed nothing.
Answers, we will not find.
Tired I am. Rest I must.
We have to consider that
this may be a deception by the Sith.
Surely you are not suggesting
Master Yoda is susceptible
to such manipulation?
Master Yoda, you are older
and wiser than any living Jedi,
but this does not mean you are beyond
the corruption of the dark side.
Agree I do.
A possibility we must consider it is.
Clouded so much of our vision
the dark side has.
Deceived I may be.
All I can tell you is
I have scanned Master Yoda three times
and I find nothing wrong with him.
I am not an expert on his biology,
but from my point of view,
he is in perfect health.
And his mind?
No signs of any degeneration.
This section of the brain
is particularly active.
More than I have seen in any other Jedi.
Probably what happens when
you approach 900 years old.
I think we are overlooking
an obvious thread.
Which is?
Count Dooku was Yoda's apprentice.
And Count Dooku
has fallen to the dark side.
All of us have apprenticed
to Master Yoda.
He cannot be held accountable
for Dooku's descent.
But they are connected. Profoundly.
Whoever the Sith Lord is,
he may be using this relationship
as a direct link to Yoda.
Impossible.
Are you so sure?
If the Sith Lord wanted to
attack the Jedi Order from within,
Master Yoda would be
the perfect choice.
I fear we are
more vulnerable than we think.
I would like to suggest something.
A deprivation ritual.
It is a dangerous procedure,
but one that will without question
allow Yoda to go to
the source of this voice.
Whatever, whoever it may be.
I am sorry to bother you,
but the Chancellor's requesting
that Master Yoda attend
an emergency meeting.
I will go.
What about the treatment?
Ask Master Yoda what he wants to do.
Only he can decide now.
The chamber works to
deprive the patient
of any stimulation except from within.
Master Yoda will be taken into
an induced meditation.
This allows the patient to go deeper
than anything we can achieve
by ourselves.
Master Yoda, you don't have to do this.
Solve this puzzle I will.
But it could be
more dangerous than you realize.
The danger is not to know the truth.
See clearly I must.
Help this will.
Life signs are normal.
Beginning the procedure.
What are you doing?
By reducing the flow of oxygen
the body will be forced
into a deep meditative state.
It will take him
as close to death as possible.
I don't like this.
Yoda, no. This is not the way.
Come to Dagobah.
The answers you seek are here.
But why?
You must complete what I could not.
His vital signs are dropping too low.
-But the test...
-I want him out of there now!
Master Yoda! Master Yoda, wake up!
Come back to us!
Speak of this to no one. Trust no one.
Come to Dagobah, alone!
Master Yoda! Master Yoda, wake up!
Welcome back, old friend.
Thought we lost you there.
Speaking to the dead I was.
Friends long gone.
Good friends.
How did the procedure go?
We're not certain.
Yoda seems to be under the impression
he contacted the dead
and spoke with them.
What are your thoughts
on this, Doctor?
Medically, Yoda seems fine,
but I cannot speak
to his spiritual balance.
What Yoda claims is not possible.
As far as we know.
The dead are part of the Cosmic Force
and lose their individuality.
I fear Yoda is under attack by the Sith,
though how remains unknown to us.
Until what's going on is clear,
I want temple guards
placed in the medical bay.
I'm prescribing nothing but bed rest
for you now, Master Yoda.
I will leave you two alone.
You asked for me, Master?
Yes, friends, we are?
Of course.
A choice you must make.
Worried for you I am.
Why is that?
Do something for me you must.
Blamed you will be.
What? What must I do?
Help me to escape. Yes.
Escape?
But you're not in prison.
No? Perhaps.
But perhaps I am.
Already, all around us the cage may be.
A journey I must make, alone.
The Council will not want you
to travel at all, alone even less.
Disobeying the Council,
your expertise is,
that is why I ask for your help.
It is the spontaneity you find so easily
which others do not.
That is what sets you apart.
Now, a walk you will take me on.
Come, come.
Where are you going?
Some fresh air I require.
It's okay, he's with me. I'll watch him.
I hope I don't regret this.
Hey, Artoo, I have a mission for you.
Doctor Nema is going to notice
Yoda is missing any minute now.
Get him to his ship as fast as possible
and get him out of here.
Where's Master Yoda?
What have you done?
Hey, for once, none of this was my idea.
Yes, stay with the ship you may.
This task, for me alone it is.
Here I am.
Ready for my next instruction,
Master Qui-Gon.
Yoda, my old friend,
you have come at last.
Qui-Gon Jinn... Really you, it is?
It is.
Losing my mind I am not?
No, my friend. No.
Why have you brought me here?
Follow the light,
the light will be your guide.
Strong this planet is with the Force.
It is one of the purest places
in the galaxy.
How are you here?
I am a manifestation of the Force.
A Force that consists of two parts.
Living beings generate
the Living Force
which in turn powers the well spring
that is the Cosmic Force.
Show yourself, can you?
I cannot. My training was incomplete.
All energy from the living Force,
from all things that have ever lived,
feeds into the Cosmic Force,
binding everything and communicating
to us through the midi-chlorians.
Because of this I can
speak to you now.
See the future, you can?
I exist where there is no future or past.
Know you who the Sith Lord is?
I can only show you a place where
the answers will be revealed to you.
Be wary,
give power to that which you fear
and it will show itself to you.
No, no, no. You will die!
Sidious...
Join me. There is no other way.
No.
Yoda, come back to us. Yoda.
Such darkness. Such evil.
When will this happen?
It is happening right now.
It has always been happening.
With each day the Clone War wages,
evil is growing in its power.
What you felt in the cave
is merely a portion of what
the dark side now holds.
Such power.
Any hope that the Jedi
can prevail, is there?
There is always hope, my friend.
Though it often comes
in forms not looked for.
The key is knowing how to see it
and seizing that opportunity.
I have been tasked
with guiding you forward.
There can be many outcomes.
But your path is clear, Yoda.
You have been chosen,
as I was before you.
For what chosen am I?
You will learn to preserve
your Life Force,
and so, manifest a consciousness
which will allow you to commune
with the living after death.
How?
Dark times are ahead
and forces of light must remain.
This is the path of only a few Jedi.
You will travel to one of the origins
of all life in the galaxy.
This place is where?
The Force will be your guide.
Goodbye, my friend.
Yes, my friend, all right I am.
No, back to Coruscant,
we are not going yet.
Afraid, only begun our long journey has.
http://hiqve.com/