h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
Brothers reunited!
Darth Maul, the sinister Sith
thought to have been destroyed
so many years ago
by Jedi Master Obi-Wan Kenobi,
was found alive
by his brother, Savage Opress,
and taken back to Mother Talzin
on Dathomir.
Though Darth Maul's memory
has yet to be fully restored,
his need for vengeance has awakened,
more powerful than ever.
Patience, brother. We're almost home.
Far above, far above,
we don't know where we'll fall.
what once was great is rendered small.
-Brother...
-Kenobi... Kenobi...
Brother, we have to go.
Kenobi... Kenobi...
Fine. Stay here.
Savage.
Mother.
Shall we?
What happened here?
Where are the rest of the sisters?
Dooku sent his minions to destroy us,
but we will survive.
We always have.
You found him. I knew you would.
Yes. He is damaged.
He doesn't remember much of his old life.
Hmm. But he does remember something.
Something or someone named Kenobi.
It is an obsession.
Come, let us fix what has been broken.
Come to me.
Follow us, son of Dathomir.
Follow me, lost one.
Come, child of Dathomir.
Follow me.
Now sleep.
Now what?
Now we begin.
Arise, Maul, reborn son of Dathomir.
Brother?
Brother.
My... My legs.
They have been restored by Mother Talzin.
It has been so long
and my path has been so dark,
darker than I ever dreamed it could be.
And yet you survived.
Of course I survived.
My hatred kept my spirit intact
even though my body was not.
Yet I was lost and became a rabid animal
and such is how you found me, brother.
Discarded, forgotten.
I have missed so much.
The Force feels out of balance.
Yes. There is conflict. The Clone Wars.
Oh, yes. So it began without me.
You can begin again, brother.
I was apprentice to the most
powerful being in the galaxy once.
I was destined to become so much more,
but I was robbed of that destiny
by the Jedi,
by Obi-Wan Kenobi.
Then you must have your revenge,
my brother.
Yes, we shall start with revenge.
The supply ship's here. Go on ahead.
Brother, what are we doing here?
The Jedi won't be out this far in the galaxy.
In a galaxy at war, Savage,
there is only one way
to get the attention of the Jedi.
Slaughter of the innocent,
mercilessly and without compromise.
There will be more innocent blood
on your hands, Kenobi,
unless you come here, face me.
Come alone and if you do not, this world
will burn.
I have to go.
Not alone you're not.
We'll send a task force with you.
No, you see what he's capable of.
He's a broken, unbalanced monster.
I've dealt with him before. I can do it again.
I disagree. This is clearly a trap.
Against my better judgment,
agree with Master Kenobi, I do.
Finish what he started long ago,
Obi-Wan must.
I'm off to Raydonia.
Master Yoda, if this is indeed Darth Maul,
his capture is far too important
to leave it to Obi-Wan alone.
Mmm.
Not alone will Kenobi be,
an unexpected ally he may have.
Trust the Force, we must.
Sure, sure. Coming up.
Hey, bounty hunters,
stop monopolizing all of the transmitters.
Shut off your speaker, droid!
These marks are too easy.
Not enough credits.
Whoa!
A million credits!
Who is this Savage Opress?
I'll take it!
Don't even consider it, boys.
I've got this one.
Jedi.
I have been waiting for you.
I'm not sure I've made your acquaintance.
I am surprised you could have
forgotten me so easily
after I killed your master
and you left me for dead on Naboo.
It is you.
You may have forgotten me,
but I will never forget you.
You cannot imagine the depths
I would go to to stay alive,
fueled by my singular hatred for you.
That may be so, but I defeated you before,
and I can defeat you again.
Don't be so certain.
You?
Still as weak as ever.
And they call you, "Master."
You know, when I cut you in half,
I should have aimed for your neck instead.
Anything more to say?
I like your new legs.
They make you look taller.
I will make sure
you stay awake long enough
to feel every single cut.
Your death will be beyond excruciating.
You will suffer as I have suffered!
What a surprise.
My former servant, still an animal.
And you have a friend now.
My brother.
A brother?
Looks like he's half the man
you are, Savage.
How unfortunate.
I was looking for a challenge,
not some wretched castoffs
from the Night brothers clan.
What a disappointment.
Who is this, brother?
A Dathomir witch. She betrayed me.
She knows too much, destroy her.
Kenobi, don't tell me someone's
finally knocked the fight out of you.
Wake up!
Ventress?
It looks like I'm here to rescue you.
When did you become the good guy?
Don't insult me.
Oh ! What a lovely sight to wake up to.
Don't flatter yourself, Kenobi,
you've never been much to look at,
especially now.
The witch and the Jedi.
Here for our taking.
I want that back.
That's fine, red's not my color.
Ready?
Like you even have to ask.
Ventress, catch!
Your master, Qui-Gon Jinn,
I gutted him
while you stood helpless and watched.
How did that make you feel, Obi-Wan?
Your rage has unbalanced you.
That is not the Jedi way, is it?
-We're outmatched.
-You want to run?
I learned from watching you.
Funny. The cockpit?
Now!
Come on, come on!
-Hurry, Kenobi !
-I'm working on it!
Come on, hurry!
Now would be a good time!
Blast!
That was cutting it a little close.
You do know, it's not over.
I know.
They'll be after us both now.
What now, brother?
Do we go after them?
No. We will be patient, Savage.
I've waited so many years for my revenge,
I can wait a little longer.
But the Jedi will know
that you have survived.
They will be coming for us.
I am counting on it.
http://hiqve.com/