h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
Corruption, discovered at
the core of the Banking Clan.
Reunited, Rush Clovis
and Senator Amidala
discover the full extent
of the deception.
Anakin Skywalker is sent to the rescue.
He refuses to trust Clovis and
asks Padmé not to work with him.
Determined to save the banks,
she refuses her husband's request,
throwing their relationship into turmoil.
Voted for by both
the Separatists and the Republic,
Rush Clovis is elected new leader
of the Galactic Banking Clan.
Now, all attention is focused on Scipio,
as the important
transfer of power begins.
Welcome back to Scipio, Rush Clovis.
Our Separatist government has
great hopes for you.
Thank you, Senator.
Only you and Senator Amidala
will be allowed
to monitor the exchange proceedings.
No forces on either side
will be allowed into the neutral zone.
Senator Amidala, we'll be right here
if you should need us.
Thank you, Commander.
It is with great disappointment
that I implement the following verdict.
By decree of the Muun people,
the five representatives
standing before me
are found guilty of embezzlement.
They shall be imprisoned forthwith,
and control of the banks shall
transfer immediately to Rush Clovis,
under the guidance of
the Muun government.
We are grateful to you, Clovis,
for everything you have
done for the Muun people.
To have lost the banks
would have been a historic disaster.
I would like you to know I have
no interest in controlling the banks.
I'm simply here to reestablish order.
Do you think our friend
is up to the task?
There are few men
I have met in my career
who are more dedicated to a cause
than Clovis.
Once he decides what he is fighting for,
little will stop him from achieving it.
Let us hope you are right,
for all our sakes.
Clovis, how are you liking
your new office?
I must say, you look very comfortable
behind that desk.
Count Dooku,
what do I owe the pleasure?
Come, come, my boy.
You don't think
I'd let such an important day pass
without wishing you the best of luck?
Thank you.
But luck has nothing to do with it.
The transfer has occurred
without a hitch.
Well, of course it has.
The Separatists are
fully behind your appointment.
After all, aren't we
the ones who put you there?
For your support, I am grateful.
But I now must lead
without allegiance towards either side.
Is that so?
Quite the idealist you have become
in so short a time.
What do you want, Dooku?
To collect on my investment.
How do you think
the Republic would like to know
that it was I who supplied Rush Clovis
with all the information he needed
to topple the leaders of the bank?
I will tell them myself.
But you can't.
I put you in power, you belong to me.
And if you want to stay in control,
you will do as I say.
The banks will remain unbiased.
Then I'm afraid the Separatists will be
unable to pay the interest on our loans.
But the banks will collapse and the...
Not if you raise interest rates
on the Republic.
What?
You know I can't do that.
But you can, and you will.
Or everything that you've fought
so hard for will be destroyed.
By the new order of the Traxus Division,
and in an attempt
to stabilize the banks,
it is essential that interest rates on
loans to the Republic
be raised immediately.
What?
But you can't do that!
Clovis!
Clovis?
What are you doing?
This is an outrage!
We warned you this would happen!
And what of the Separatists?
From the little information Senator
Amidala has been able to establish,
there will be no raise
on their current loan.
I knew from the beginning
that Clovis would do this.
We knew that Clovis would do this.
Correct you might have been
about Clovis.
It's incredibly foolish for him
to make a move like this so early.
He will turn the whole Republic
against him.
Not clear to us are his objectives.
Want this, he might.
Something's wrong.
This doesn't make sense.
I would like to call for restraint
and allow us time
to analyze the situation.
You may begin your attack.
It is time to make Rush Clovis
look like a powerful Separatist.
Right away, sir.
It looks like an invasion fleet, sir.
We're caught out here in the open.
Get the men off this landing pad
and beyond the city gates.
Senator Amidala, come in, please.
What is it, Commander Thorn?
We're under attack
by the Separatist garrison.
Looks to be a full invasion.
Invasion?
We can't get to you.
I suggest you get to a ship
as soon as you can.
Let's move! Hurry!
For the Republic!
Our garrison has been
attacked by the Separatists.
And it appears
they are staging an invasion of Scipio.
An invasion?
What do they hope to achieve?
With this news, the Senate will
vote immediately to attack Scipio.
It appears war has
already come to Scipio.
I want you off that planet immediately.
I can't.
Surely you can get to a ship.
General Skywalker,
I'm afraid I'm trapped.
Let me go!
Invoke an emergency meeting
of the Senate.
There is no time to lose.
I feel it is only right that you should
handle this matter, my boy.
A lot will be entrusted to you.
Don't touch me.
What have you done to her?
Clovis, what is going on?
I didn't want this, Padmé.
Why don't you tell her
what you did want and how you got it.
Dooku?
Padmé, this is not what it seems.
Hasn't she joined our cause?
Clovis here told me how instrumental
you were in getting him to power.
If I had known...
Either you're with us,
or you're against us.
Arrest her.
We can't do this, Dooku.
The Separatist Senate
will never approve.
Hey.
No, no!
No!
Are you insane?
This was not part of the deal.
What deal?
What have you done here, Clovis?
He's given us the banks.
Gone are our debts,
and gone is any credit for the Republic.
All of your idealism was just a front.
There was nothing I could do.
Everyone has their price, my dear.
It is with grave news I come before you.
Count Dooku and
his Separatist betrayers
have manipulated us, my friends.
The war must go to Scipio.
Clovis has been their puppet of deceit,
as the Separatists are
currently invading Scipio.
We must stop them
and secure the planet.
We have handed the entire
economic system over to Count Dooku.
We are doomed! Invade!
As Supreme Chancellor,
I must abide
by the consensus of the Senate.
We shall commence
a mercy mission to Scipio
to be led by General Anakin Skywalker.
The banks will be secured at all costs.
And the Republic will not crumble.
We'll obtain victory!
Yeah, war on Scipio.
Great emotions you will find on Scipio,
will you not?
I am worried for Senator Amidala.
I'm afraid we may be too late.
Correct you were about Clovis.
But let go of your selfishness you must
if you are to see clearly.
Not all is as it seems.
I understand, Master.
Lord Tyranus, the Republic fleet
will be arriving shortly.
Very good, my Lord.
Clovis has blindly played his part,
it now appears he coordinated
the entire Separatist takeover.
And because of this treachery,
the banks will be firmly placed
under the control of
the Supreme Chancellor.
Why are you doing this?
You wouldn't understand.
I had to strike a deal with Dooku.
But don't worry, I am the one in control.
As soon as things have settled down,
I can get rid of him.
And I'll control it all again.
Listen to yourself.
The Republic is sending its armada
to take back the banks.
You've brought war
right where there cannot be war.
Your actions have destroyed the banks
once and for all.
Rex, have you gotten a fix
on Senator Amidala's position?
We'll have a better lock
once we get near the city.
But initial scans suggest
she's still alive, sir.
Good.
Hawk, we're gonna need air support
once we're on the ground.
You'll have it, General.
Me and the boys are ready to fly.
My Lord, we have
fully engaged Republic forces.
But we are suffering heavy losses.
We have accomplished
what we came here for.
It is time to withdraw.
But, sir, our forces are
still engaged in battle on the planet.
Leave them.
As you wish, Count Dooku.
Sir, a Republic attack fleet
has just entered orbit,
and is approaching the city.
Get me Count Dooku.
It appears Count Dooku has
left the planet's surface.
What?
And the Separatist forces
are in full retreat.
We are alone.
Rex, hold the droid forces here.
-I'm gonna push on and get Padmé.
-Copy that.
Such plans I had.
You know, I've spent
so much of my life misunderstood.
What will they say about me now?
What will I have left behind?
Clovis, you have to turn yourself in.
It's over, Clovis.
Stay away from me.
I didn't do anything wrong.
You have to believe me.
You don't wanna do this.
You don't understand.
You've all been deceived.
Yeah, by you.
No, by Dooku.
I'm not the villain here.
Tell him, Padmé.
Let me go, Clovis.
No!
I can't hold both of you.
Let me go.
No, Anakin, don't!
Try and climb.
I am.
I'm losing you.
I'm sorry, Padmé.
No!
It's okay. You're okay.
I'm sorry, Anakin. I'm sorry.
It's over now. It's all over now.
It is clear to the Banking Clan
it was Rush Clovis
who was behind the corruption
that almost caused our collapse.
In hope of a better tomorrow,
we cede control of the banks
to the office of the Chancellor
of the Galactic Republic.
It is with great humility that
I take on this immense responsibility.
Rest assured,
when the Clone Wars end,
I shall reinstate the banks
as we once knew them.
But during these treacherous times,
we cannot, in good conscience,
allow our money
to fall under the manipulations
of a madman like Count Dooku
or Separatist control again.
May there be prosperity and stability
at all our Republic lands.
May our people be free and safe.
Long live the banks.
Long live the banks!
http://hiqve.com/