h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
Darkness on Dagobah!
All attention is focused on Yoda,
who claims
to hear the voice of a long-dead Jedi.
Convinced that he is guided
by Qui-Gon Jinn,
he finds five priestesses
who will teach him how
to manifest consciousness after death.
After many trials,
Yoda travels to Moraband,
ancient home planet of the Sith.
For now he must face the true evil
that may be his undoing
and one that seeks
to control the galaxy.
Careful, we must be.
Deserted, this planet was,
long ago, after many wars.
Again, leave you, I must, my friend.
Guard the ship, you will.
If return, I do not, by three night falls,
take the ship to Coruscant, you shall.
Tell them of where I went.
We are the Sith.
Afraid of you, I am not.
We shall see.
There is no life after death.
Only nothingness awaits you, Jedi.
Your fear feeds our hunger for power.
They will know you are here,
we will tell them.
You will die and be nothing.
Sir, you have been ordered
to go to Coruscant immediately.
Tell Lord Sidious I am on my way.
Why do you come to my tomb, Jedi?
To learn.
Do you know who I am?
Yes.
Darth Bane,
the ancient Sith Lord, you are.
And know why I am not forgotten?
Created the Rule of Two, you did.
The Sith killed each other.
Victims of their own greed.
But from the ashes of destruction,
I was the last survivor.
I chose to pass my knowledge
on to only one.
I created a legacy so resilient
that now you come before me.
Have you come to be my apprentice?
You must kill me to gain my place.
Dead, you are, already.
Then what stands before you?
An illusion.
Real, you are not.
-You do not fear me?
-No.
Exist, you do not, anymore.
Yoda.
I sense we have a great opportunity
to strike a deadly blow
to the Jedi Order.
But we must act swiftly.
A warning, I must give you.
Yes.
All your trials you have faced
have been our doing.
And you have passed them well.
But inside, there is a place
where we have no control.
For it is a place of absolute darkness.
What happened here?
It is the chamber
where the Sith would sacrifice Jedi.
The Sith of your time will find you there.
And you will find them.
Be careful, for what they may offer
will certainly feel like an answer.
Only the presence of someone
significant to you
would allow you to sense this
ripple through time and space.
My old master, Yoda!
Yes,
Master Yoda has come to Moraband,
although why, I do not know.
We shall, however, use the strong bond
that once existed
between you and your master
to allow us to see things
that we otherwise could not.
How can this be done, Master?
It is an old art of the dark side.
Now, hold out your hand, Apprentice.
I need but a drop for the ritual to begin.
Now, concentrate on Master Yoda,
bring all your focus to him.
But will he not sense our presence?
We shall come to him
with a familiar face,
a long-lost face.
One he would be eager to see again,
one whom he would ask
and want answered
all the questions he seeks.
Help me.
Please, please free me.
Sifo-Dyas? Alive, you are!
Help me please, Yoda.
I have been imprisoned for so long.
Know who did this to you?
What if I could tell you
who the Sith Lord is?
Free me and I will reveal it.
No!
He knows how to achieve
what you seek.
Captivated by the physical realm,
the Sith are.
What else is there?
Free me and together
we can know who the Sith Lord is.
Gain the power you deserve,
and save the future.
-No.
-You must free me!
Nothing to show me, the Sith have.
We shall see.
Sidious!
There is no question,
the ship was carrying Count Dooku.
We've scanned the area
and he is meeting with someone
inside the building.
Thanks, Rex.
-Master Yoda, what are your orders?
-Orders?
Are you all right, Master?
-Where am I?
-I don't understand.
Tell me, you must!
The industrial sector on Coruscant.
What is happening here?
A rogue shuttle
slipped through the security grid.
-We suspect Dooku was on board.
-And?
Master, this is your mission.
Are you sure you're all right?
Clouded, the dark side has made me.
Tell me, who is inside?
We intercepted a transmission
calling Dooku to Coruscant.
We believe he is meeting with
his master, the Sith Lord.
Feel it, I do. Feel their power.
Your orders, Master?
Capture them, we will.
The time has come to discover
the identity of this Sith Master.
-And if they escape?
-Escape, not.
If it comes to it, execute them, we must.
End it now, we will.
Move in.
I've got two confirmed targets.
Be ready for additional unfriendlies.
It appears we have company.
Take them!
We meet at last, Darth Sidious.
You cannot stop what is to come.
Skywalker, no!
No!
Save him, Jedi? Can you save him?
Why not let him go?
Let him die
and you can stop all that I will do.
No!
The future is not yours yet.
Tempted, I will not be.
Sacrifice all, I am ready to do.
We have failed to break Master Yoda.
He is strong.
We will need more time
if we are to defeat him and the Jedi.
Yoda.
Come back to us, Yoda.
Died, have I?
In a way.
Now does my training begin.
The one you know as Qui-Gon Jinn
will commune with you
and guide your training.
Like us, you shall learn to maintain
your consciousness after death.
Enlightenment.
Spirit.
Balance.
There is another Skywalker.
There is another Skywalker?
Yes, time to go home, it is.
The Council has assembled,
they are eager to hear your report.
Afraid not much there is
to say of my journey.
So, nothing significant
happened to you out there?
Yes and no.
To the end, we are coming now.
Did your journey give you insight
on how to win the war?
No longer certain
that one ever does win a war, I am.
For in fighting the battles,
the bloodshed,
already lost, we have.
Yet, open to us, a path remains,
that, unknown to the Sith, is.
Through this path,
victory we may yet find.
Not victory in the Clone Wars,
but victory for all time.
http://hiqve.com/