h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
NARRATOR: After suffering a series
of disastrous defeats
at the hands of General Grievous,
the Republic’s foothold in the Outer Rim
is in jeopardy.
Commissioned to protect
the strategic world of Bothawui,
Anakin Skywalker
and his weary battle group
are all that stands between the system
and domination by the Droid Army.
Among our most recent losses
was the battle group at Falleen.
The Separatist fleet commanded
by General Grievous is headed your way.
Seems like that coward always knows
where and when to attack us.
You're heavily outnumbered, Anakin.
I advise retreat.
If we run, the Separatists
will take control of this sector.
-I can't let them do that.
-And that is your problem.
Master Kenobi is right. We should regroup.
We don't stand a chance against...
-Ahsoka...
-Suicide is not the Jedi way, Master.
You should listen to your Padawan.
As you listen to yours, my old master?
No, we're going to stay and fight.
And I think I know how to beat Grievous
at his own game.
(COUGHING)
Our spies were right, General.
The Jedi have positioned a fleet
beyond the planetary rings.
Move our ships through
the asteroid field to engage them.
Through the field, sir?
If we attack from above,
they will have the advantage.
So we will go through the rocks.
-That didn't sound good.
-All power to the forward shields.
What if they attack us from behind?
They can't. The asteroids will protect us.
(WHOOSHING)
Gold Squadron, tighten formation.
Slow approach. Let's draw them in.
Yes, sir.
(BEEPS WORRIEDLY)
Don't worry, Artoo.
Grievous is falling right into our trap.
Resolute command to Gold Leader.
We are standing by.
Enemy closing to Zone 6.
-Patience, Ahsoka.
-CLONE OFFICER: Zone 4.
Zone 3.
General, we have a clear shot
at their cruisers.
Good. Good!
They're right on top of us!
Should we commence firing?
Wait... Wait...
Concentrate fire
on the closest Republic cruiser.
Roger, roger.
(FIRING)
(RUMBLING)
We're outgunned!
We're not gonna last
a Mynock minute out here!
Hang on, Ahsoka. We've got them
right where we want them.
Watch your stabilizer, Gold 6!
It's no good. Incoming's too heavy.
Gold Squadron, take evasive action!
Sir, yes, sir! Breaking off!
(R2-D2 BEEPING EXCITEDLY)
No, Artoo, we're not retreating.
Good thing you gave us that extra power.
Let's finish them off!
(FIRING)
Ahsoka, they're in position.
Unveil our little surprise.
Right away, Master. Rex, old boy,
it's time you joined the party.
With pleasure, sir.
General, we've been outflanked.
All units, fire at will!
(FIRING)
Impossible!
Forward cannon, let them have it!
(RUMBLING)
This is too easy!
Get us out of here!
Uh, where are we supposed to go?
(GRUNTS)
Uh, General?
Well, I guess I'm in charge now.
(WHIRRING)
(RUMBLING)
Grievous!
(FIRING)
Let's finish this.
All batteries, target that command bucket!
(LAUGHING)
He's powering up his hyperdrive, Artoo.
Hang on!
More speed, Artoo!
(R2-D2 BEEPING EXCITEDLY)
See what you can do about that, buddy.
(BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Uh-oh.
I got a bad feeling about this.
(SCREAMING)
(WHIRRING)
(GROANS)
-What happened?
-You owe Rexster your skin, Skyguy.
Just doing my job, sir.
It was your plan that won the day.
Grievous is AWOL, but his fleet of tinnies
is nothing but spare parts.
(GRUNTING) Good work, both of you.
Where's Artoo?
I'm sorry, Master, he's gone.
(SIGHS)
Congratulations, Anakin.
Your resourcefulness always amazes me.
Thank you, Master.
-You look troubled.
-I lost Artoo in the field.
Well, R2 units are a dime a dozen.
I'm sure you'll find a suitable replacement.
I could take a squad out there,
track him down.
Anakin, it's only a droid.
You know attachment
is not acceptable for a Jedi.
It's not just that, Master.
How do I put this?
I didn't wipe Artoo's memory.
What? He's still programmed
with our tactics and base locations?
If the Separatists get a hold of him...
What possessed you
not to erase that droid's memory?
Master Obi-Wan,
sometimes Artoo having
that extra information
has come in handy.
Well, then find that droid, Anakin.
Our necks might very well depend on it.
Right away, Master.
You ready to go, Snips?
Master, they just delivered
your replacement astromech droid.
This is R3-S6.
(R3-S6 BEEPS)
I've heard that the new R3s
are far faster in thinking skills
and more powerful than the old R2 units.
And best of all, Master, he's gold!
A gold droid
for Gold Leader of Gold Squadron?
You can't replace Artoo.
(R3-S6 BEEPS IN CONCERN)
Don't worry, Goldie.
You'll get to know him later. Come on.
(R3-S6 BEEPS)
There's my ship!
Artoo's gone. He must have escaped.
He's gotta be around here somewhere.
Artoo isn't on the scanners,
but there is a ship out there.
Looks like a Trandoshan scavenger,
probably combing the battlefield
for salvage.
The historical texts say...
Archive texts can only teach you a part
of the picture, my young Padawan.
You'll learn a lot more
through some hands-on experience.
(RATTLING)
Ugh!
What's that smell?
(SNIFFS) Ugh.
You'll get used to it.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUMBLING)
Hey! We'd like to buy a droid. You selling?
(LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
(FARTS)
Ugh!
We're looking for an R2 unit.
You happen to pick up any recently?
An R series? No, no, not for a long time.
Pookums here really has her heart set
on another R2.
She lost the last one.
"Pookums"? Oh, brother.
Nice R3 unit. Trade for a C-14?
-Not on your life, lizardo.
-Now, let's see how much I have here.
Tell you what, I may have an R2 unit
buried somewhere in the hold.
Help yourself, but be careful.
There are many unique items down here.
(EXCLAIMS)
(R3-S6 BEEPS)
Master?
ANAKIN: These must be the unique items
we were warned about.
These assassin droids
can be very unpredictable.
They're switched off.
They don't look so tough to me.
Nothing looks tough to you.
Take my word for it, they're deadly.
(R3-S6 BEEPING)
R3, access the computer
and find the inventory manifest.
Artoo's got to be around here somewhere.
(R3-S6 BEEPING)
(WHISTLE)
-Did you hear that?
-Hear what?
-That sounded like Artoo!
-How can you tell the difference?
It came from down here. R3, get this open.
(R3-S6 BEEPS)
-We don't need the lights on!
-No, Goldie, the hatch.
Never mind. I'll do it myself.
(LIGHTSABER ACTIVATING)
(WHIRRING)
(BEEPS)
(GRUNTS) Master!
Goldie, shut these droids down!
(WHIZZING)
I'm afraid R3 is a little slow on the uptake.
(FIRING)
(LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
(SCREAMS)
(FIRING)
Back at you, piston head!
You were right about
the hands-on experience, gramps.
-Much better than the archives.
-Good job, but you missed one.
(LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
(BEEPS)
As for you, stubby,
you'd make a poor excuse
for a light switch.
-I'm sure he did his best.
-His best to get us killed?
Artoo would have never
made that mistake!
(BEEPS MOURNFULLY)
R3 can't even get the door open.
(WHIRS)
A little late, stubby.
(GRUNTS)
If you didn't have a lightsaber,
you'd be a dead man.
-Where's my droid?
-Master! What are you doing?
R2's not here.
Let's get out of here.
I told you
there were no R2 droids down here!
Look at this mess you made!
You owe me, Jedi!
You'll be sorry you ever
came aboard my ship, Jedi.
I'm about to make your life miserable.
What is it?
I'm en route
to the rendezvous point, General.
I've got the merchandise
you were looking for.
(LAUGHING)
It must be valuable.
A Jedi came looking for it.
Maybe it is worth more
than we negotiated.
Don't push me, slime.
You bring that R2 unit to me
as fast as you can get here, or else!
Ah. Yes, of course, General. Just kidding.
(WHIMPERS)
We have to assume that R2
was destroyed
in the explosion that claimed your ship.
-Yes, Master.
-Our intelligence has confirmed
that Grievous' spies
have been intercepting our transmissions.
He must have some sort of secret
listening post out there somewhere.
That would explain how he's been able
to ambush our fleets.
Split up your squadrons, Anakin.
Find that base and destroy it.
-It's as good as done, Master Kenobi.
-May the Force be with you both.
I'll sweep the outer corridor,
while the rest of your ships
focus on the center.
Are you sure you want to go alone?
I'm sure. More than one fighter
will just draw too much attention.
Yes, sir.
Master, you'll need a droid
to help you navigate.
-I think stubby is defective.
-Give him another chance, Master.
This is the perfect time for you and him
to, you know, bond.
(BEEPS)
All right. Come on, stubby.
(R3-S6 BEEPING EXCITEDLY)
May the Force be with you, Master.
(SNORING)
(R2-D2 BEEPING)
(BEEPING)
Removed your restraining bolt, have you?
What were you up to?
(BEEPS)
R3, have you verified those coordinates
on the search grid?
(BEEPS)
Okay, let's see what we can find.
Activate long-range scanners.
(BEEPS)
(ALARM BEEPING RAPIDLY)
No, not the tracking beacon!
Shut it down, R3! Shut it down!
(BEEPS)
That's Master Skywalker's
tracking beacon.
What's he doing?
Rex, get a hold
of as many men as you can.
Right away, sir.
A-ha!
There's our Jedi tracking beacon.
Skywalker, now you have fallen
into my trap!
ANAKIN: Why do I have to do everything?
Let's hope Grievous didn't hear that.
Yeah, he heard it.
(FIRING)
Time to leave.
Plot a course out of here
and prep the hyperdrive engines.
What are you doing?
I said, prep them, not drop them!
(GRUNTS)
Where's R2 when I need him?
-Launch everything we have!
-Sir, it's only one fighter. He can't escape.
Everything!
I know. I know! Missiles.
I hate missiles.
We're going on the offensive, R3.
Get ready to cut the engines.
(BEEPS)
Will you just do what I tell you?
Hit the stabilizers, R3.
-Hey, that was clever.
-Silence!
Move the cruisers into attack position.
All right, R3. Let's get turned around
before those fighters catch up to us.
(BEEPS)
You know, if this ship blows up,
you go with it!
(BEEPS)
What do you mean,
the laser guns won't fire?
Cargo bay doors open.
You better get inside.
I'd love to, but R3's having
a problem with the engines.
Destroy those ships!
Don't let them get away!
-Let's give him some cover, boys.
-Yes, sir.
Steady. Almost there.
I'm inside.
Now let's get out of here, Ahsoka.
Power it up, Rex.
We're going right between those tin cans.
(RUMBLING)
Hit it, Rex.
Uh, they got away, sir.
(GROWLS)
Hey, Goldie. What did you think
of your first adventure?
I'll tell you what I think.
I think I'm lucky to be alive!
(BEEPING)
-Great! Now you hurt his feelings.
-His feelings? What about R2?
He's still out there. I know it.
http://hiqve.com/