NARRATOR". Mystery on Mortis!
Sent to discover the origin
of a mysterious distress call,
Obi-Wan Kenobi, Anakin Skywalker
and his Padawan, Ahsoka Tano,
are stranded on a distant planet.
There, they discover three beings
more powerful with the Force
than any Jedi have seen before.
A father keeps a fragile balance
between his daughter,
who allies with the light side,
and the son,
who drifts ever closer to the dark.
With his strength failing, the father asks
Anakin to stay and take his place,
preserving the balance
between light and dark.
But after passing a perilous test,
Skywalker refuses.
Now, we ﬁnd our heroes
about to depart for their journey home.
Or so they think.
Anakin.
Anakin?
It's true, what they say.
You are the Chosen One.
Join me.
Together we can change
the balance of the universe,
my friend.
You must know
I will never join the dark side willingly.
How simple you make it.
Light and dark,
as if there is one without the other.
Aligned, you and I can restore balance
wherever we go.
Peace to the universe.
By becoming a Sith?
Never!
We will destroy the Sith!
And the Jedi.
- Were you having a nightmare?
Something like that.
If you're done napping,
I could use a little help here.
I'm coming.
Leaving so soon?
Not without this, you won't.
Ahsoka!
-What's going on?
-The son took Ahsoka.
What in the blazes are you talking about?
Move! Let me fly!
Look out!
I didn't think you saw it.
It was a giant tower! Of course I saw it!
Any sign of him?
No. But I think it's obvious
where he's taken her.
-We must hurry.
-Anakin, this wasn't a mistake.
He brought us here for a reason.
We must not get involved.
Any conflict here could have dramatic
repercussions for the universe at large.
I don't care. He's too powerful for Ahsoka.
I won't leave her alone.
We are in the middle of something
we don't truly understand.
We'd be wise
to confer with the father first.
There's no time.
This is what he wants, to divide us.
It's my fault he took her!
You must feel how strong this part
of the planet is with the dark side.
The father will know what to do.
He can't help us.
You cannot keep me here!
You hear me?
Save your energy.
You have been left to die.
Then I will escape!
Impossible.
I have been here for more years
than I care to remember.
lam a Jedi. We don't give up easily.
Jedi?
Hm.
But so young. Where is your master?
He will come for me.
And if he does not?
He Will!
What makes you so sure?
Thank you.
The chains.
The chains are the easy part.
It's what goes on in here that's hard.
Don't you see, child?
You are alone now.
If you are to survive,
you must forget your master.
I don't think l...
Ow!
What have you done?
You are mine now.
Anakin, always on the move.
How do I even find the father?
You are growing stronger, my son.
Am I, Father?
Vanity, however,
is getting the better of you.
How so?
You have done what is forbidden.
You have chosen the dark side
and allowed it to feed your anger
and desire for power.
By bringing the Chosen One here,
you've shown me my potential.
You've only yourself to blame.
Do not do this, Son.
Do not become what you should not.
Be strong, I implore you,
or else I will be forced to contain you.
You look frail, Father.
I am not dead yet.
Well, perhaps I am tired of waiting!
I hate you!
Father!
We will leave him to rest.
I must talk to him.
-Not until he's stronger.
-But your brother is losing himself
to the dark side.
He's taken our friend.
Then he must have his reasons.
The same reason he had for
attempting to murder your father?
He would never do such a thing.
But I saw him.
It is not his fault.
My nature is to do what is selfless,
but my brother's will always be
to do what is selfish.
Then know you must help us.
I cannot interfere
with the ways of the Force.
My father forbids it.
Your brother will flee this place
and wreak havoc on the universe.
You and Anakin combined
have the power to stop him.
Come with me.
I can go no further.
When you reach the altar,
it will give you what you need.
I don't understand.
He who wields the blade
will be able to control my brother.
Ahsoka.
Ahsoka!
It's me. You're safe now. Let's go.
Are you proud of me, Master?
What?
Of course, Snips.
Of course I'm proud of you.
Now let's get out of here.
He's right.
Right about everything.
You must join him.
He only wants what's best for the universe.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Always with the criticism, Master.
Never really believing in me, trusting me.
Well, I don't need you anymore.
Ahsoka. Ahsoka, listen to me.
He has done something to you.
Snap out of it!
- This isn't you, Ahsoka!
-Isn't it?
I feel more like myself than I ever have.
He asked me to give you a message.
He said if you don't join him,
he will kill me.
I won't let him.
Then you will be forced to kill me!
Sister! What a pleasant surprise.
And you brought a friend.
What have you done, Brother?
Done?
I have done what is right.
Or what is wrong,
depending on your point of view.
Our father is dying.
Did you do it?
He is just so selfish
and was taking too long to die,
so I decided to move things along.
Now, why are you here?
I won't let you leave this planet.
You are not strong enough
to keep me here.
Not alone, she isn't.
Are you referring to your friend,
the Chosen One?
You might want to check up on him.
He's a little preoccupied right now.
I don't want to fight you, Ahsoka.
And now the student will kill the master.
Getting ahead of yourself,
aren't you, Snips?
Don't call me that!
I hate it when you call me that!
Two Jedi. Finally, a challenge.
Can you feel it, Sister?
Can you feel the anger?
The hate? The fury?
Their conflict is feeding you, isn't it?
I must stop them.
No!
If you will stand in my way,
then I guess we must fight.
-Any suggestions?
-Yes! We cut her free!
-What is that?
-It can kill the son.
Where did you get that?
Give it to me!
You don't have to do this!
Then stand aside!
I can't.
I won't!
Stop this!
So glad you could make it
to our little party, Father.
You will stop this!
You are too weak for me, old man.
You mean nothing to me anymore.
Anakin! Now!
Everything has transpired
exactly as I planned.
You showed them the altar?
I am sorry, Father.
I didn't know how else to stop him.
Give it to me, child.
Ahsoka, no.
Thank you.
Your usefulness has come to an end.
No!
The Jedi have brought me the dagger,
and you have brought yourself.
Now, Father,
you will die.
Father!
Why?
My daughter, what have I done?
Do not hate him, Father.
It is his nature.
No!
All is lost.
The balance has been broken.
I thought by bringing you here I would...
But I have destroyed everything.
Can you help her?
There is no light.
The evil has been unleashed,
and the dark side shall consume her.
You must help her!
I cannot undo what is done.
There is no hope.
Yes, there is! There's always hope!
Then let my daughter's last act
be to breathe life into your friend.
Hey, Snips.
What's going on?
Uh...
Not much.
It's good to see you.
As the balance in this world crumbles,
so shall war escalate in your galaxy.
As my son has descended
into the dark side,
so have the Sith gained strength.
-We will stop your son.
-No!
You must go, now!
He needs your ship to leave the planet.
You must leave before he can take it.
What about you?
I shall mourn all that I have done
and all that is yet to be.
English - SDH