[narrator] Outer Rim under siege!
Separatist forces
have launched a major offensive.
Led by the evil droid General Grievous,
Republic forces are pushed to the brink.
In response to this overwhelming attack,
the Jedi Council
has dispatched its Generals,
sending them far from the Core Worlds
to bolster the beleaguered clones.
On the distant planet of Yerbana,
we find Commander Cody of the 212th
in desperate need of reinforcements.
Hit the targets! [screams]
Take cover! Take cover!
[grunts]
Look out! Look out! [screams]
Look out!
Aim for their eyes!
[screams]
General!
Cody, get down!
[grunts]
Well, I can see things
are going splendidly on this front.
It's no good.
We can't locate the tactical droid.
He's staying out of sight.
[grunts]
Anakin, where are you?
I'm right here.
What are you doing down there?
We are taking cover. Now get down!
You're not serious.
There's only a thousand droids
down there, tops.
What are you up to? Where's Captain Rex?
We already finished our battle,
so we decided to come help you with yours.
You're overdoing it. Again!
Master, I mean no disrespect.
If you want, I can hide here with you,
and we can let the people in the city
suffer longer.
Now, Anakin, you know I--
Or we can do things my way
and help them now.
[sighs] All right.
I know better than to try and stop you.
What's your plan this time?
Stay here.
[battle droid] One target approaching.
We can't hit it.
Identify target.
Cease fire.
All batteries take aim at the Jedi.
Ready. Aim.
Hold your fire! Hold your fire.
I have come to surrender.
Surrender? That's a relief.
Notify the tactical droid.
Your forces fought valiantly,
and I must admit that we are overmatched
by your superior firepower.
I congratulate you, for I have fought
in many battles on many planets...
always been victorious
against the droid army.
Though you have always...
Artoo.
How much longer are we stuck down here?
Great. I'll tell the boys.
All right, men.
Hang in there a little longer.
[groans, sighs]
Sir, yes, sir.
So, it is with these thoughts in mind
that I gladly surrender myself
to the mercy of the Separatist forces.
Why have you ceased fire?
Jedi Knight, Anakin Skywalker,
has surrendered to us, Commander.
There he is.
It's a trap, you fools. Open fire!
-Now, Artoo!
-[beeps]
[screams]
General.
Yes, Cody. You may join the fun as well.
Yes, sir.
-Blast them!
-Fire!
[indistinct shouting]
-[Cody] Go! Go, go, go!
-[clone trooper] Move it! Move it!
Bravo, Anakin. You've done it again.
Oh, I can't take all the credit.
Your state of helplessness
really sold them on my surrender talk.
Always glad to help, my friend.
[beeps]
Skywalker here. What is it Admiral?
[Yularen] Sir,
we've received a transmission
from someone
using your subspace frequency "Fulcrum."
Saw Gerrera?
Perhaps the siege at Onderon
has taken a turn for the worse.
No, sir, it's not Gerrera.
You had best take this transmission
here on the ship.
Both of you.
All right, Admiral.
What's so important you brought us
all the way back here?
Hello, Master. It's been a while.
Ah-- Ahsoka. Wha--
[chuckles]
[chuckling] I don't believe it!
How are you?
Where are you?
Are-- Are you okay?
I'm all right. Thank you.
I wish we had more time to talk,
but I have urgent information
for both of you.
What is it, Ahsoka?
Lady Bo-Katan and I have located
the renegade Sith Lord, Maul.
And if we move swiftly,
we believe we can capture him.
It all makes sense now.
What?
If Ahsoka hadn't left the Order,
then she wouldn't have been
where she needed to be.
That's one way to look at it, I suppose.
It's the only way to look at it.
We're gonna capture Maul, finally.
I thought you would be more excited
about this.
I am cautiously optimistic.
[beeps]
[continues beeping]
Ahsoka, [chuckling] I'm so glad--
We'll have to catch up another time.
Things are moving quickly.
Every minute we waste here
gives Maul an opportunity to slip away.
We understand. Please, follow me.
Bo-Katan had been tracking
Maul's movements for several months.
I was able to obtain some transmission
codes from the Pykes on Oba Diah,
which helped her pinpoint
some of his previous locations.
What were you doing on Oba Diah?
That's a long story
and not really relevant right now.
What is relevant
is that we know Maul is on Mandalore
in the city of Sundari.
You're certain of this?
He arrived two days ago.
So why not take him yourself?
Or, to be more specific,
what do you want from the Republic?
I don't have the numbers needed
for a siege.
Without a complete lockdown of the city,
Maul will escape again.
That's why
I'm proposing a joint operation.
If we are successful,
you'll have Maul and I'll have Mandalore.
If Republic forces aid you
in your assault,
it will break treaties
that are 100 years old.
We will effectively be drawn
into yet another war.
What's one more?
Well, we're not finished
with our first one yet.
I will advise the Jedi Council
of this development.
There's no time!
Maul's influence on Mandalore
is destroying my people!
He murdered their ruler, my sister!
I thought she meant something to you!
She did. And still does.
But I cannot allow my feelings
to cloud my judgment.
The council will decide
what our course of action will be.
I told you this was a waste of time.
So, that went well, all things considered.
You two certainly haven't changed.
[chuckles] Is that a bad thing?
Come on. I have a surprise for you.
-Commander.
-Sir.
They shouldn't salute me anymore.
Not since I left the Order.
It doesn't matter to them.
It's a sign of respect.
They know what you went through for them,
day after day, battle after battle.
Loyalty means everything to the clones.
Company, attention!
Go ahead. They've been waiting to see you.
As soon as Rex and the guys
knew you were back, they got to work.
The paint job is a little crude,
but we think it gets the idea across.
Glad to have you back, Commander.
Rex, thank you.
But you don't have to call me
commander anymore.
Sure thing, Commander.
Oh. I have one more surprise for you.
[alarm blaring]
Anakin, Rex, prepare all forces.
We're jumping to hyperspace immediately.
Yes, sir.
Men, with me.
Watch it! Watch it!
You heard him, lads! Let's go!
So, the attack on Mandalore was approved?
No, it's Coruscant.
Grievous has attacked the capitol.
What about the Chancellor?
Shaak Ti has been sent to protect him,
but Master Windu
has lost contact with her.
Not to worry.
Our fleet can be there within the hour.
So that's it?
You're going to abandon Bo-Katan
and her people?
Ahsoka, surely you understand this is
a pivotal moment in the Clone Wars.
The heart of the Republic is under attack.
I understand that, as usual,
you're playing politics.
This is why the people
have lost faith in the Jedi.
I had too,
until I was reminded of what the Order
means to people who truly need us.
Right now, people on Coruscant need us.
No. The Chancellor needs you.
That's not fair.
I'm not trying to be.
I'll divide the 501st,
make a new division
under Ahsoka's command.
Unfortunately, Ahsoka is no longer a part
of the Grand Army of the Republic.
We'll promote Rex to Commander
and have him lead the new division.
Ahsoka can go with him as an adviser.
What do you say?
I accept.
That is, if Obi-Wan agrees.
Very well.
May the Force be with you.
Oh, one other thing: I killed Maul once.
Best to capture him.
He doesn't seem to stay dead.
Thanks for the support. As always.
That's what friends are for.
If you're going to face Maul,
you'll need these.
I took care of them. They're good as new.
Maybe a little better.
You capture Maul.
I'll take care of Grievous.
With any luck, this will all be over soon.
Master Kenobi always said
there's no such thing as luck.
Good thing I taught you otherwise.
Anakin!
Good luck.
[beeps]
[pilot] Commander, I have Prime Minister
Almec of Mandalore on the comm.
Put him through.
What is the meaning of this invasion?
The Republic presence here
is a direct violation of our treaty.
Your time has come, Almec.
We know you're Maul's puppet,
and we are coming for him.
Ah-ha! Mistress Bo-Katan, the traitor.
I should have known
you were behind this incursion.
Siding with the Republic will make you
an enemy in the eyes of the people.
I'm fine with that.
You're nothing like your sister.
Saxon,
prepare our forces for an all-out attack.
Rook,
inform the syndicate of the invasion.
[alarm blares]
It's been a while
since we had a fight like this.
Are you ready?
Ursa,
can you confirm the target's location?
I can only confirm
that Maul has not left the city.
All other attempts to locate him
have been blocked.
Saxon is already scrambling his defenses.
-We've got incoming!
-[alert beeping]
[grunts, screams]
What are you waiting for? Get out there!
Sorry,
I didn't think to bring you a jetpack.
Don't need one.
Race you to the surface.
[chuckles]
[screams]
Thanks, Commander!
Beat you.
Some things never change.
[groans]
[beeps]
We're meeting stronger opposition
than anticipated.
They've already taken the docks
and are moving on your position.
Escape to the Undercity.
You will be met there.
Understood.
No sign of Maul yet.
We can't sustain a long siege.
I'll head for the throne room
and deal with Almec.
You must find Maul.
I want you to support Ursa at the docks.
We must ensure Maul doesn't escape.
If he's here.
If he's not, then all of this
plays right into his hands.
[beeps]
[Vaughn] Commander Rex, this is CT-0292.
I think we have something.
I'll be right there, Captain.
Captain Vaughn, what have you got?
We were cutting off this access point
to the Undercity,
when we engaged one of the leadership,
Gar Saxon.
He disappeared through there.
Seemed in a hurry.
What's down there?
A system of tunnels, sewage ports, mainly.
Some conduit access pipes.
Do they lead outside the city?
Unknown, sir.
Let's move in.
[Rook] The Jedi was sighted
entering the lower city.
Then it's just as our lord predicted.
[grunts]
[groans, grunts]
[screams]
[grunts]
-[groans]
-[grunts]
[grunts]
Where's Maul?
You were never the politician
your sister was.
He wanted you to bring the Jedi here,
but you brought the wrong one.
Ahsoka, come in.
You're walking into a trap.
Ahsoka!
Get down.
Vaughn, wait!
[screams]
-Look out!
-[grunts]
[grunts]
This way! Hurry.
Watch it! Watch it! [groans]
Stop. Stop! [screams]
[breathing heavily]
[sighs]
I'm sorry, Commander.
I was hoping for Kenobi.
Why are you here?