Trapped behind enemy lines!
Carrying secret information
vital to the Republic's war effort,
Jedi Master Even Piell and Captain Tarkin
were taken prisoner by the Separatists.
An elite strike team, led by
Obi-Wan Kenobi and Anakin Skywalker
landed on the planet Lola Sayu
and infiltrated the prison.
The team rescued Master Piell and Tarkin,
but they were pursued by the prison's
evil commandant Osi Sobeck.
During the escape,
their ship was destroyed.
Now we find them on the run,
desperate to escape the trap
that is the citadel.
We're clear!
What's our next move?
We're going to have to
fight our way off this rock.
Contact the Council,
see when they plan to rescue us.
I'll handle it.
Master PieH, it's good to see you alive,
my friend.
Likewise, Master Windu.
Our escape route has been compromised
and there are several squads of droids
closing in on us.
When can we expect your arrival?
Master Plo is already en route.
Gunships will arrive
to evacuate you and your men,
but do not delay,
only a small window of opportunity
shall we have.
Your rendezvous point will be this island.
Understood.
May the Force be with you.
Incoming!
No doubt there's more on the way.
Count Dooku, My Lord.
Commander Sobeck, you've been
avoiding my transmissions.
My deepest respect.
I was hoping to surprise you
with good news.
Good news would indeed be a surprise.
Have the prisoners been captured?
Not yet, My Lord.
But we've located their position
and my droids are moving in now.
i need not remind you that the prisoners
are carrying secret hyperspace coordinates
into the core systems of the Republic
and our Separatist home worlds.
This information will allow us to launch
a surprise attack on Coruscant,
striking a crippling blow to the Republic
and the Jedi.
Yes, My Lord. I will see to it
that they are soon back in our possession.
You should know, Commander,
right now your honesty is the only thing
keeping you alive.
They're boxing us in!
Lock in your cables!
Artoo, we need your droids
to hold off the enemy as long as possible.
Good. Everybody, follow me!
This is sheer madness!
We understand, sir.
We will delay the enemy
as long as possible.
Prepare for attack.
It was an honor to serve under you, sir.
Keep moving!
All for one and one for...
Keep moving, keep moving!
Master Tiin, you should be leading
the fighter attack.
Once you punch a hole
through their defenses,
I will lead the gunships down to the surface
and extract the team.
Depending on the size of their force,
l don't know how much time
we can buy you.
You will do your best, I'm sure.
If the team isn't at the extraction point
when you arrive,
you may be forced to leave them,
or put us all at risk.
I'm afraid Master GaHia is right.
They'll be there.
The prisoners have evaded us long enough.
Bring out the anoobas!
Use them for tracking only!
Contact me as soon as the fugitives
have been located.
Roger, roger.
What if your Jedi friends are not there
when we arrive?
Keep moving and you won't
have to worry about that, Tarkin.
Why did Master Piell have to share
half of the intel with that guy?
It's like he's not even grateful
we rescued him.
Captain Tarkin feels the Jedi should be
relieved from the burden
of leading the war effort.
That's ridiculous.
Maybe, but we aren't soldiers,
we're peacekeepers.
The Jedi code often prevents us from
going far enough to achieve victory.
A rather simple point of view.
Either way, he is a good captain.
Did you hear that?
Yes. We're going to have company.
Commander, the additional reinforcements
have arrived.
Tighten your grip, K2-B4.
The Republic will almost certainly attempt
a second mission
to infiltrate our defenses
and rescue the prisoners.
I'm counting on you to ensure
that nothing slips past our blockade.
You know, it's not wise
to argue with Master Piell.
It's certainly not a good career move.
General Skywalker,
I stand by my principles. No matter what.
Besides, I needn't worry about my career.
I've fallen into favor with the Chancellor.
He shall support me.
I happen to know the Chancellor
quite well, myself.
Oh... Really?
Really.
Let's keep moving.
If we're not at the rendezvous
at the exact time, we'll miss our window.
Those creatures are gaining.
If they've caught our scent,
they'll lead the droids right to us.
We're gonna have to deal with them.
What about using this cave
to surprise them?
If we can get them to pass by,
we can attack them from behind.
But we need a distraction.
Leave that to me.
And Obi-Wan, of course.
Okay, the rest of you, follow me.
Keep going!
Ahsoka and I will take care of the droids.
Master Piell!
I have to get help.
No. Don't leave.
Listen to me carefully, child.
The information, I need you to
deliver it back to the Council.
I should find Anakin or Obi-Wan.
They need to hear this.
No. You must listen.
But I wasn't assigned to the team.
I lied just so I could be
a part of the mission.
Whether you were meant to be
on this mission or not,
you are now the most important part of it.
Remember this.
And see to it that the information
I'm about to give you
is revealed to no one but the Jedi Council.
Sir! The anoobas have located the fugitives
along the northern shore.
Squad, come with me!
I will deal with this personally.
So much for the hunting party.
There are more squads on their way.
Oh, no.
He died honorably.
What about the information?
I have it. He told me just before he died.
We don't have much time.
Let's take this moment to honor him,
then we must move on.
He would have wanted us
to complete our mission.
There have not been battles like these
since the days of the Old Republic.
Indeed. Good hunting.
There's the extraction point.
Incoming!
Look what I found!
They are too many droid fighters.
We need more time
to break through the blockade.
We're out of time, Master Tiin.
We must break through now.
Very well. Wing commanders form up.
We're going in.
Captain!
If I can't have the information,
it will die with you.
My thanks, Padawan Tano.
I see you've trained her well.
The rescue ship should be here by now.
So should the rest of the Separatist army!
I believe you've worn out your welcome.
Admiral Coburn, we have the survivors.
Recall all fighters.
Yes, General.
Prepare to jump to lightspeed.
We're all ready, Admiral.
Of Master Piell's loss, we are sorry to hear.
He will be missed.
Because of his great sacrifice,
we now have the Nexus Route coordinates.
Captain Tarkin and Ahsoka
have each memorized half.
Debrief them both, we must.
With all due respect, Master Jedi,
I was instructed by Chancellor Palpatine
to bring the intel directly to him
for debriefing.
I promised Master Piell that
I would deliver it only to the Council.
And that's what I will do.
Hmm...
Personally meet with the Chancellor, I will.
Decide what is best to do, we shall.
Master Plo, there's something
we want to ask you.
Did you assign Ahsoka to the mission?
It appears I did.
Ajob well done, General Skywalker.
I wish more Jedi
had your military sensibilities.
Perhaps I can inform the Chancellor
of your valor.
I'm not sure what to think of your new ally.
Well, I think we need people like him.
This is a war. If we aren't willing to do
what it takes to win,
we risk losing everything we try to protect.
Unfortunately, war tends to distort
our point of view.
If we sacrifice our code, even for victory,
we may lose that which is most important,
ourhonon
English - SDH