-[grunts]
-Watch it.
You actually captured him. I'm impressed.
That is what the council wanted.
Still. You succeeded
where many have failed.
I've learned from the best, including you.
I wish I was good at something
other than war.
Your people need a new kind of leader.
My sister tried that.
I never understood her idealism.
[coughing]
Commander. I have the council waiting.
And Master Skywalker?
Were you able to contact him?
He was at the meeting
when I left to get you.
Go on. I can handle this.
[Mace] I sense a plot to destroy the Jedi.
The dark side of the Force
surrounds the Chancellor.
If he does not give up
his emergency powers
after the destruction of Grievous,
then he should be removed from office.
The Jedi Council
would have to take control of the Senate
in order to secure a peaceful transition.
To a dark place,
this line of thought will carry us.
Hmm.
Great care, we must take.
I understand your mission was a success.
Yes. I have Maul in custody.
I will escort Commander Rex
when he delivers him to Coruscant.
A great service to the Republic,
you have done.
I did my duty as a citizen.
Not as a Jedi.
No. Not yet.
Actually, I was hoping
to speak with General Skywalker.
I sent him to inform the Chancellor
that General Grievous
has indeed been located on Utapau.
Master Kenobi?
Engaged the enemy, he has.
Then the war could be over soon.
That depends on the Chancellor.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry, citizen. These matters
are for the council to discuss.
I understand.
Ahsoka. More to say, have you?
A message for Skywalker, perhaps?
No, Master. Thank you.
I'll tell him myself when I see him.
May the Force be with you, Padawan.
You didn't tell them
what Maul said about General Skywalker.
No, I didn't.
[breathes heavily]
Impressive. I suspect even Maul
couldn't get out of there.
A relic of a bygone era
when Mandalorians had reason
to imprison you Force-wielding maniacs.
I thought your sister
outlawed such devices.
She did. This is the last one.
Goodbye, Ahsoka Tano.
[Maul exhales]
[controls beep]
Something on your mind?
As a Jedi, we were trained to be
keepers of the peace, not soldiers.
But all I've been since I was a Padawan
is a soldier.
Well, I've known no other way.
Gives us clones all a mixed feeling
about the war.
Many people wish it never happened.
But without it, we clones wouldn't exist.
Well, then perhaps some good has come
from all of it.
The Republic couldn't have asked for
better soldiers, nor I a better friend.
Commander Rex,
the latest briefing has come in.
Want to have a look?
It might have an update
on General Kenobi's efforts.
You go. I'm sure it's more good news.
[Maul breathes heavily]
[lightsaber ignites]
[Sidious] You must choose.
[Mace] Don't listen to him, Anakin!
[Anakin] It's not the Jedi way.
He must live.
[Mace] He's too dangerous
to be left alive.
-[Sidious] Please don't.
-[Anakin] I need him.
-[Sidious] Unlimited power!
-[Mace screaming]
[Force lightning crackling]
[Anakin] What have I done?
[whispering] Anakin?
Execute Order 66.
Yes, Lord Sidious.
Rex. It's Anakin. I feel like
something terrible has happened.
[indistinct radio chatter]
Rex?
No!
I'll do it.
Rex, what's happening?
Stay back!
Find him. Find him.
Fives. Find him! Fives!
[grunts, groans]
[Ahsoka] Rex!
-She's down. She's down.
-Hold your fire! We got her!
Sir, are you all right?
Fine, just tired is all.
I want you to go to the detention level.
Execute Maul.
Yes, sir.
All right, men.
All right.
We know Ahsoka Tano is on board.
She's been marked for termination
by Order 66.
Under this directive,
any and all Jedi leadership
must be executed for treason
against the Republic.
Any soldier that does not comply with the
order will also be executed for treason.
-Understood?
-[clone troopers] Yes, sir!
[Rex] There are only so many places
to hide on this ship.
Gather up search parties. We'll fan out
and move section by section.
Come on. Let's get moving.
[Maul breathes heavily]
[heavy breathing continues]
[controls beeping]
[clone trooper] Look out! [grunts]
Don't make me regret this.
[groans]
You-- [coughs] You survived.
Is this your doing?
Choose your words carefully.
No, no. It was not my doing.
I do not know what has occurred,
but, surely, you have felt it.
The voices crying out. [coughs] The death.
The clones turned against me. Even Rex.
I don't know why,
they just suddenly weren't themselves.
[chuckles] Brilliant. Brilliant.
[chuckles]
I was not privy to my master's plan,
but now, now I see it.
He turned the Jedi's own army
against them.
[exhales]
Well, you've done the right thing
by coming to me.
Only together can we survive this.
Now, if you will follow my lead--
You don't understand.
I'm not here to team up with you.
I need a diversion, and you're it.
Now go cause some chaos.
It's what you're good at.
Uh, [sighs]
care to give me a fighting chance?
I'm not rooting for you. Now get going.
Sir, we finished our sweep
of the detention level.
The prisoner has escaped.
There's no sign of Tano or Maul.
Destroy the escape pods
and increase security on the hangar decks.
Right away, sir.
-[droid powers up, beeping]
-Shh.
[whispering] R7, I need your help.
[beeping]
I know. I know.
Shh. Quiet.
[droids beeping]
[whistling, beeping]
I don't know. I don't know
why the clones are doing this.
But we might be able
to do something about it.
[beeping continues]
-Are you sure you wanna help?
-[droid beeps]
It could be dangerous.
[beeping]
Okay, let's get started.
R7, patch into the central computer.
Bring up every secure file
on Clone Trooper CT-5555.
[R7 beeps]
Okay, Rex. What am I looking for?
An independent investigation confirmed
that the Clone Trooper CT-5555
experienced a malfunction
with his inhibitor chip.
Both the Senate committee and the
Jedi Council have accepted these findings.
However, a grievance report
was filed by CT-7567.
R7, bring up that report.
[beeps]
It's sealed?
Try Anakin's pass code. 8-1-0-8.
I already know this report is gonna fall
on deaf ears,
[sighs] but I owe it to Fives
to record what I saw.
I'm not sure I believe it myself,
but there's a possibility
that the inhibitor chips
the Kaminoans put inside of us
have a purpose
that we don't yet fully understand.
Fall back! Fall back!
[groans]
[grunts]
Ridge is down!
Maul's advancing toward the main hangar!
[Rex on radio] You must seal
the blast doors. Stop his advance!
Seal the blast door! Now!
[grunts, screams]
[screaming intensifies]
[Rex] Trooper, did you seal the doors?
Trooper? If you read this, seal the door.
We want to redirect his approach. Over.
[radio beeps]
[droids beep]
[R7 beeping]
Hey, hey. Out of the way!
[droid beeping]
Are you cross-wired?
[droids beep]
Rex. I think I know what's happening.
I saw your report on Fives.
It isn't your fault. You were programmed.
Your mind was altered to do this
when you were very young. I can help you.
-Where is she?
-[screeches]
I'm right here.
[screams, groans]
Careful. We're trying not to hurt him.
[droid beeps]
[clone trooper] They've got the commander.
Bring the charges.
Cheep, are all the doors sealed,
so the way is clear?
[beeps]
Okay. Let's get him to the medical bay.
[droids beeping]
[clone trooper] Move it! Move it!
Start working on these doors.
-R7, run a scan.
-[beeps]
See if you can find the inhibitor chip
the report talked about.
[beeps]
[medical droid beeps]
[beeping]
But the chip has to be there. Check again.
How close are they?
[beeping]
G-G, if they override the door controls,
you have to reseal it fast.
[beeps]
R7, anything?
I am one with the Force,
and the Force is with me.
[together] I am one with the Force,
I am one with the Force,
and the Force is with me.
[computer beeps]
You found it?
[heart monitor beeping]
R7, get him under and remove that thing.
[beeps]
I don't know if it will work,
but if it doesn't, we're dead anyway.
[R7 beeps]
[clone trooper] Go! Go!
Get ready on the door.
[G-G beeps]
[screams]
[grunts]
[groans]
[screams]
[grunts]
The door. G-G, the door!
Rex? Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, kid. I'm okay.
I'm sorry for what happened earlier.
[sighs] I almost killed you.
How widespread is this?
Ahsoka, it's all of us.
The entire Grand Army of the Republic
has been ordered to hunt down
and destroy the Jedi Knights.
[electricity pulsating]