h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
Separatist takeover complete!
Another Republic planet has fallen.
Onderon has seceded to the
Confederacy of Independent Systems
under the rule of a new king.
However, a small band of rebels
have taken refuge
deep within its vast and savage wilderness.
From an abandoned outpost,
they plot to take back the heavily fortified
capital city of Iziz
and end the Separatist occupation.
Unfortunately, the only way
to reclaim Onderon
will be through armed struggle.
But we lack
sufficient hardware and supplies.
Onderon is in your king's rule,
and at the outbreak of the Clone War,
he chose to align it with the Separatists.
Our true king has been silenced.
The one you recognize
is a traitor and a Separatist minion.
We need your help to survive this.
Find a way we shall.
We await your answer.
There are pockets of rebels on many
of these planets that just need guidance.
With training and resources,
they could attack soft targets
while the Republic continues
to engage them on the battlefield.
That sounds like terrorism, Anakin.
Well, I think of it as an insurgency.
To help realign these planets
with the Republic.
We can divide the Separatist forces
and press them on two fronts.
A means to an end fear cannot be.
Stop those who spread terror
the Jedi must.
Indeed. What you're suggesting
would open up dangerous possibilities.
We must not train terrorists.
Uh, rebels.
How we conduct war is
what distinguishes us from others.
Funding rebels to overthrow
a legitimate government
puts innocent lives at risk.
We can minimize collateral damage
by using arms that mainly affect droids.
The least we can do
is help them defend themselves.
Test the tactic while we're at it.
This could be a great new weapon for us.
Hmm.
Train and observe.
Send advisors we will.
I'll assemble a team.
I'm going with you.
What? You don't trust me?
Too much. That's what worries me.
This is Valkyrie 29-29.
We're coming up on the drop zone.
Go! Go! Go! Go!
We've spotted them, sir.
Stay where you are.
Identify yourselves.
It's all right. We're friends.
Jedi.
I'm Commander Tano. We're here
to help you take back your planet.
My name is Steela.
I'll guide you to our secret base.
Hmm?
Mmm.
A bit rough around the edges,
wouldn't you say?
That's why I brought Rex here.
They're not exactly what I would call shiny,
sir, but I can work with them.
-General Skywalker.
-At your service.
This is General Kenobi, Commander Tano
and Captain Rex.
We're looking forward to taking the fight
to those scrapping droids.
Yes, all in good time.
Saw. Saw Gerrera.
He fashions himself as our leader,
though no one elected him.
Well, for now, we're in charge.
And there is much to learn.
The Separatists have strength in numbers.
We're gonna show you
how to target and destroy them.
Now, to be clear,
we are not here to fight your war.
Rather, to show you how to conduct it
in the most efficient
and successful way possible.
Captain Rex.
I'll show you
how the 501 st destroy clankers.
First, I need volunteers to carry supplies
from our entry point a half-click west.
-Shouldn't be a problem.
-Excellent.
Lux, it's good to see you again.
It's good to see you, too, Ahsoka.
I didn't realize you had
such strong ties to Onderon.
Onderon is my home.
My mother represented it in the Senate.
Your voice is strong. Like hers was.
Have you reconsidered
joining the Republic Senate?
Even if we do take back Onderon,
it won't change how I feel.
I'm not fighting for the Republic.
Well, what matters now
is we need each other's help.
Just like we did on Carlac.
Carlac? What happened on Carlac?
Ahsoka is the reason I'm here
and not with Death Watch.
-Really?
-What he means is...
She saved me from a huge mistake.
Hmm...
Lux obviously thinks highly of you.
I guess so.
Let's hope that respect is well founded.
The pilot in the front hatch
controls the tank, the shells
and the short-range blasters.
The commander in the top hatch
controls the turret and the main cannon.
You have to take out both chambers,
otherwise the tank will remain operational.
Everyone, divide up into teams of two, and
we'll practice an assault on both hatches.
I'll take the top.
Let's see what you're made of, Bonteri.
Sorry about that.
You're a terrible soldier, Bonteri.
I'm not sure if they're more interested
in fighting the droids or each other.
They'll learn.
We just need time to train them properly.
Keep your eyes on the quick learners.
-In this fight, time is not on our side.
-Come on ! Hustle!
Go, go, go, go, go!
An unscheduled ship entered the
atmosphere in sector S-11
and failed to register.
The rebels may be operating in that area.
Check it out.
Come on, move it like a soldier!
Like a real soldier!
Come on, Donald ! Pick it up, Hutch!
- You can do better than that.
- Come on, hustle!
I said hustle!
That's what I'm talking about right there.
Go, go, go! Good. Good!
-You sure you're up for this?
-Saw...
-It was an accident.
-You would have had us both killed.
Just stop it.
Sit down, boy, this isn't the Senate.
You've got no talent for this.
It's going to take a lot more than muscle
to defeat the Separatists.
Politics have failed us. We have no choice.
We always have a choice.
Then make yours.
Look, if we're going to succeed,
you'll need to be exceptional
with words and action.
There will be time for both.
Destroyers are quick, pack twin blasters
and come with their own shield generators.
Nothing short of a cannon will pierce it.
But they do have two weaknesses,
and you will need to work together
to exploit them.
The shields deflect high-velocity attacks.
What the shields don't stop are slow
or stationary objects.
They're designed to absorb them
so nothing hinders their movement.
Destroyers are blind from behind.
A distraction combined with a rear assault
will give you a kill.
The trick is to get the right speed
on the droid popper.
These are unarmed. Just concentrate
on getting it past the shield.
Watch and learn.
Quite brilliant.
Hmm. Nice touch.
Thanks.
Not bad.
Ugh.
Be mindful of your frustration,
it will only hold you back.
Here, use your shoulder.
Let your arm swing,
and keep your eyes on the target.
Great.
Okay, let's get back to work.
Everyone pair up. We'll practice in groups.
Hey, Commander,
how about, uh, helping me practice?
Roger, roger. This is Command.
Copy that. I'll send a squad out now.
We've located the rebels.
Proceed to sector S-29.
Shoot to kill.
I can't get the distance or the speed right.
Don't give up. Learning this could save
your life and those around you.
A little backspin might help.
Just take it easy. Don't get frustrated.
-You got it.
-Good teacher, Jedi.
Oh!
Just forget it. I'll never learn this.
Uh, keep practicing.
-You made it look easy.
-Wasn't always that way.
Right, the Force. Is that your secret?
No, perseverance.
Look, you'll get the hang of it.
I wouldn't let it get you down.
I'm not feeling down.
I just know what I'm good at.
Impressive.
Most impressive.
Fixed targets are one thing.
How about this?
Nice job.
You've clearly mastered
your ability to focus.
Snips, are you losing focus?
-No, Master.
-Good.
A head shot is the only decisive way
to disable a droid.
They don't need arms, legs, or even bodies
to pass intel to Central Command.
All right. Shoot at will.
Wait a minute, what is that?
Droids!
Take cover!
It appears the training is over.
I'll take the left flank if you take the right.
No, Anakin, we can only protect them.
We cannot fight this war for them.
There are too many.
But Anakin, Ahsoka and I can hold them off
while you get your people out of here.
You didn't teach us to run.
Saw, use your disrupters
to take out the droids.
I'm on it.
Ready, disrupters, on my mark.
Now!
What is that?
-It looks like an explosive.
-How can you tell?
-Not bad.
-That is only the first wave.
-We'll handle this.
-No, I will.
Duck!
Hey, Bonteri, you ready to try again?
-Hey! What are you doing?
-What you taught us!
Surrender, rebel.
You will answer for your crimes
against the Separatist Alliance...
We, uh, need to clean you up.
I like it. Now you look more like
a soldier than a politician.
Well, maybe a good politician
needs to get dirty now and then.
Take confidence from this victory.
But rest assured,
there will be more droids coming
now that they know your position.
It doesn't matter, you're ready now.
We are going to take the fight to the droids.
You don't have to hide in the jungle
any longer.
Droids were a bit dim.
More so than I imagined.
They make up for it in numbers.
They're designed to overwhelm.
But they're not designed
to deal with our approach.
We hit them where they least expect it.
And before they realize what happened...
We fade in with the rest of the population.
Exactly.
We need a plan to get inside the city.
I have an idea.
Identification, please.
Halt!
What were you doing
outside of the city gates?
Hunting. We've been trekking for days.
Did you register before your excursion?
No, but most of our time is spent
in the bush collecting our traps.
We come to the city to sell.
You can't get thrip larvae like this in Iziz.
Only the biggest trees
on the other side of Onderon.
Hey, listen, we need to deliver
all of this in time for supper.
Hmm.
Are you scanning anything?
It's hard to tell
with so much organic matter.
Come on !
Our merchants are waiting inside.
Can you hurry it up?
-Let them through.
-Roger, roger.
Good plan.
Like Saw said,
those droids are dumber than we thought.
Not a bad start.
But now the hard work begins.
You must find recruits
and choose your targets wisely.
They'll be looking for us.
We should split up.
Regroup after nightfall.
I'll alert our brothers.
We'll make sure you have
the supplies you need.
Rex and I will take care of that.
Good luck.
You, too.
How do you think they'll do?
I have a feeling
we'll be pleasantly surprised.
So you admit our new strategy will work.
I am hopeful, Anakin.
Hopeful.
http://hiqve.com/