h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
Kidnapped!
During a Separatist invasion
of the planet Kiros,
thousands of peaceful colonists
were abducted by Zygerrian slavers.
Determined to find the missing colonists,
the Jedi travel to Zygerria,
home to the galaxy's
most notorious slave empire.
It looks like Zygerria
is a popular place these days.
Hmm.
Whatever is happening
is attracting plenty of high class scum.
Let's just hope the information our spies
gave us about the Queen is accurate.
Remember, I'll keep her occupied
while you locate
the missing people of Kiros.
How do you plan
on keeping the Queen occupied?
-With my magnetic charm, of course.
-Oh, yes, of course.
Hold on to this, will you, buddy?
Remind me why I'm the one
playing the part of the slave?
I tried it once, I wasn't any good at it.
Besides, the role of master
comes easily to me.
Really? Well, this time
try to be convincing at it.
Ugh!
How can a civilization this advanced
still practice slavery?
It makes them wealthy and powerful
at the expense of others.
Before the Hutts bought my mother,
she was sold in a market just like this.
Get up, you useless skug.
Master, the bonds, they are too heavy.
Tell it to my whip.
You don't want to do that.
You dare touch me!
Excuse my slave, friend.
She is freshly caught.
Hmm. What have we here?
You wear Zygerrian armor,
but you are not one of us.
Who are you?
I've come for an audience with the Queen.
Then you have an invitation?
We can't just let anyone in
to speak with Her Majesty.
No invitation, but I do bring news,
news the Queen will be eager to hear.
I doubt that,
you're nothing more than a brigand.
I wouldn't say that,
especially when the Queen learns
you prevented her from hearing
the news about Bruno Denturri.
Halt! Cease all hostilities.
This man is to be escorted to the palace,
by order of the Queen.
Make certain all preparations
are complete for this evening.
And fetch refreshments.
My Queen, I present Lars Quell.
Hmm.
So, you are the man who claims
to be acquainted with Bruno Denturri?
Yes, Your Highness.
However, when I spoke with him
he failed to describe your beauty.
Really?
And did Bruno
speak of my intense hatred of him?
Or did that escape his memory as well?
He needed not speak of it, Your Majesty.
In fact, Bruno Denturri
will not be speaking ever again.
What do you mean?
Bruno Denturri is dead by my hand.
Here is a slave from his palace,
compensation for my efforts.
Unhand me, brigand!
You impress me, Lars Quell.
She is quite a prize.
And to have defeated
Bruno Denturri in combat,
you must be quite the warrior.
Hmm.
Mmm-hmm.
The slave is certainly of fine stock,
Bruno always knew
how to choose a beautiful female.
Don't you dare touch me!
Though she will have to be processed.
Her demeanor leaves much to be desired.
What is your price for her?
With respect,
how can I price the beauty of this slave,
when I look upon
the magnificence of Your Highness,
whose beauty would make
the brightest star seem dull by comparison.
Lars Quell, you flatter me.
No, Your Majesty, however...
Lars, stop it. Stop it!
You are a bold one, aren't you?
My reputation precedes me then.
Perhaps we can find a way
to put a price on your slave.
Come, walk with me.
Sir, take a look at this.
Stand watch, I'll take a closer look.
Governor Roshti?
No! No!
Governor, I'm a friend, a Jedi, here to help.
-Where are your people?
-They're...
-Sir, did you find out where the others are?
-Not yet.
We've got to get him out of here.
You there,
what are you doing with that slave?
Slavery is the natural order of things.
The weak deserve nothing more
than to kneel before the strong,
bound to our service.
I will need men with your talents
to spread our ways across the galaxy.
Let me go!
You dare raise a hand against your master.
Clearly you require further processing.
No! I won't go back there.
Wait! Stop!
Such a waste.
But perhaps she was more trouble
than she's worth.
But you, Lars,
you are proving quite resourceful.
Very well, I will pay your price
for this slave girl.
It seems
I am in need of a new servant.
She is my gift to you, Your Highness.
You are a man of many surprises.
It pleases me.
I wish you to be my guest
at the slave auction,
and to sit at my side.
Well...
-Who is he?
-He hasn't talked, but I'll loosen his tongue.
Why would a slaver
try to rescue a slave from the palace?
It's suicide.
Wait. I know you from the hologram.
I never forget a Jedi.
Your Highness, Zygerrians,
and guests from a thousand worlds,
our auction begins
with slaves of unmatched quality
and impossible quantity.
I give you Togruta from the Kiros System!
Oh, no.
This handsome sample
represents a lot of numbering,
no less than 50,000 beings.
Note the compliance.
Virtually untrained in combat.
There will be no rebellion
from these slaves.
So where do you keep 50,000 slaves,
like the people of Kiros?
Your Majesty, I have urgent news.
All will be revealed in time.
Before we begin the auction,
I would welcome a most special guest,
Obi-Wan Kenobi, Jedi knight!
Down with the Jedi !
The Jedi are not so tough.
My friends, my good friends,
do not fear the Jedi.
They are no different from others
we have forced into submission,
for they have forsaken their ideals
to serve a corrupt Senate.
Every Jedi
has become a slave to the Republic.
The Jedi Order is weak,
and we will help break it.
Teach the Jedi his place.
Whip the Jedi ! Whip the Jedi !
Whip the Jedi ! Whip the Jedi!
Looks like
I have to rescue you again, old man.
I knew you'd have a backup plan.
Prove to me you are a slaver.
Swing that whip, or die beside him.
Those are some lousy options.
You leave me no choice, Highness.
Guards, subdue them!
Ahsoka, the Queen!
Looks like your slave empire
is finished, again.
Get that thing out of my face,
you little skug!
Such determination.
You destroyed my auction
and frightened my customers.
Count Dooku and half my kingdom
are demanding your death.
You should have listened to them.
My friends, where are they?
Continue to misbehave and they die.
A most curious Jedi who cares more
about his friends than his own mission.
Hero. General.
And now my servant.
I will not serve you.
Your heart is not in your words.
You will stand beside me,
a testament to my power.
Here, my bodyguard will need a weapon.
And you need not worry about your friends,
they will be quite safe.
The Queen has promised
once the other Jedi is tamed,
you will be mine, little skug.
Whoa!
You better hope that doesn't happen.
My people, we have found them.
Keep moving, skug.
General Kenobi, you are the first Jedi
I have entertained
at our educational center.
Few possess a Jedi's resolve,
and it is strength of will
that is my greatest enemy.
Now that I have your attention, Jedi,
be aware that it will not be you who suffers
should you defy me.
You were once a slave, weren't you?
What makes you think I was a slave?
The noble selflessness in your eyes.
Your commitment to the service
of something greater than yourself.
Your Jedi, the grand Republic,
even your friends.
I don't see commitment as slavery.
Oh, it is when it comes
at the cost of yourself.
What you could be!
With you willingly beside me,
there is nothing we could not accomplish.
We are nothing. You have all the power.
What if I freed your friends?
Would you promise to stay?
Commit to serving me?
If a Jedi as noble as you gave his word,
I think you might keep it.
I don't trust you.
Have I been anything but honest?
I have no reason to lie. I am who I am.
It is you, you, who are the complicated one.
Now, Master Skywalker, the future
of your friends lays in your hands.
If they are to live as slaves,
it will be you who keeps them that way.
http://hiqve.com/