h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
NARRATOR: Invasion!
Separatist leader, Wat Tambor,
has taken control of the planet Ryloth
and subjugates its people
through a brutal droid occupation.
In a daring surprise attack,
Jedi Anakin Skywalker
and his Padawan, Ahsoka Tano,
defeated the space blockade
guarding the planet.
Now, Jedi Generals Mace Windu
and Obi-Wan Kenobi
lead a massive invasion
to liberate the starving people.
OBI-WAN: The first trick will be
getting our troops on the ground.
If you take the city of Nabat first,
we'll have our landing zone.
Well, it's time to meet the natives.
You must not allow the clones
to reach the surface.
Our new proton cannon
are in the optimum position
to prevent that, sir.
What?
(STATIC WARBLING)
What if they focus the attack
on your cannon?
I am utilizing the prisoners
from this village as living shields.
I calculate the Jedi will not risk
the prisoners' safety with a direct assault.
We need to remember why we're here.
We came to aid the Twi'leks,
not destroy their home. Cody.
That means we'll be taking it back
the hard way.
Minimal destruction with blasters
and droid poppers only.
No rockets or detonators. Check your aim.
Keep an eye out for the locals.
-Am I understood?
-ALL: Sir, yes, sir.
(SIGHS) If we're here to free the tail-heads,
the least they can do is get out of our way.
-Sir, the enemy is in range.
-Fire at will.
(FIRING)
General, the enemy fire
is penetrating our shields!
Get me Kenobi.
We can't risk landing the larger transports
until you take out those guns.
Pull back. We'll take care of it.
Who's up for a challenge?
We're not getting any reinforcements
until those guns are out of commission.
Here we go again.
Commander, the Republic transports
have turned away,
but the gunships
are still heading toward us.
Just as I calculated.
Prepare for their ground assault.
-I think I see movement in the trees.
-Fire! Fire!
Come on, men. Let's go! Go, go, go!
(LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
That bunker's gonna be
a problem, General!
Leave the bunker to me!
Bring in your troopers on my signal!
-You two wanted action. Follow me.
-You heard him, Waxer.
Let's take them out. Now!
(EXPLODES)
-We've got to get closer to the wall.
-Try again. I'll give you some help.
(GRENADE CLATTERS)
(EXPLOSION)
Ghost Company, let's move.
Sir, I've lost contact
with our outer defenses.
The Republic troops have overrun
the village perimeter.
-Find out how the Jedi plan to attack.
-Roger, roger.
The wall is secure, sir.
Are we moving on to the guns?
We need to know
what the droids have in store for us.
-Send your best men to scout ahead.
-Will do, sir.
-Boil, Waxer, come with me.
-WAXER: I guess we're the best.
Buildings are just buildings.
What really makes a city
are the inhabitants that live in it.
BOIL: So, where are they?
We'll check out the courtyard.
You two take the south sector.
Be back at command by 0620.
Yes, sir.
I tell you, Boil, this is creepy.
-Do you think they killed all of them?
-Well, there are no bodies.
They were driven from their homes.
I don't think they had a...
(CLATTERING)
BOIL: Had a what?
WAXER: (SIGHS) Choice.
(FOOTSTEPS CREAKING)
Not gonna be easy
getting to those guns, sir.
There is always a way, Wooley.
(FOOTSTEPS CREAKING)
Wait. Twi'leks!
They're holding all the survivors hostage.
We have to report this to General Kenobi.
We found the guns.
They're in the courtyard here and here.
But there's a complication.
They've taken the locals hostage
and they're using them as shields.
The Twi'lek prisoners
will make this difficult but not impossible.
I still have a good plan
for taking out those guns.
MACE: Getting the villagers out of
harm's way is our first priority.
I have faith in you, General Kenobi.
Cody, we'll go in with everything we have.
Clear those hostages.
So, it's General Kenobi
who is leading this assault.
-He is known for his deceptive maneuvers.
-Roger, roger. Download his file.
-Ah! It's just a little girl.
-Well, what are we gonna do with her?
BOIL: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Why do we have to do anything?
-We've got a mission to finish.
-WAXER: We should do something.
I say we take her with us.
You can't be serious.
She'll only slow us down.
(LOW DRONING)
-Look, she's afraid of us.
-Not us. Quick, hide!
BOIL: That was a recon unit.
We better get moving.
-WAXER: We can't leave her here.
-(SIGHS) Fine. We'll take her.
Be careful.
Don't worry, Waxer,
I don't think she's armed.
(BOIL EXCLAIMS IN PAIN)
-The little tail-head bit me!
-Stop, stop. You're scaring her.
She probably thinks we're droids.
It's all right. See?
I'm flesh and blood, just like you.
-She looks half starved.
-Here.
(SNIFFS)
Nerra, nerra.
No, I'm Waxer. He's Boil.
Oh, you made a friend.
Mission accomplished.
(SIGHS) Can we go now?
Come on, kid. Come on.
Look, she doesn't even want to go.
The little monster was fine
before we came along, so let's move.
(CALLS OUT)
(PANTING)
(MURMURING)
-Sergeant, are the creatures ready?
-I starved them like you ordered, sir.
(GROWLING)
-Are you sure they will not attack us?
-I need a test to verify my theory.
(BUZZING)
Sir, what are you doing? Oh, no.
(DROID SCREAMS)
(GROANS) Not my motivator!
As I calculated,
the creatures require organic meat.
-Well, that's a relief.
-It will not be for the clones.
They will provide a most generous supply.
(NUMA PANTING)
I wonder what happened to her family.
They're probably dead.
Hopefully, she'll survive this mess.
So, what happens to her?
I mean, after we leave.
I don't know. Don't get any ideas.
We're not taking her with us.
-She's gone.
-I'm sure the little biter will turn up.
Hey! There you are.
(NUMA GIGGLES)
How'd she get in front of us?
Nerraa! Nerraa!
WAXER: No, don't go that way!
That's where the recon droid went!
-Waxer, let it go!
-I'm not just gonna let the droids get her!
I'm just trying to keep you alive.
Darned if I know why.
Where's she going?
Wait! Hold on there!
-Hey, there you are!
-(SIGHS) Good, you caught her.
You know, I have binders if we need them.
What?
What are we doing here anyway?
I guess this was her home.
Poor little thing, she lost it all.
(SQUEAKING)
(SNIFFLING)
(CRYING)
It's okay now. We're here to help.
(SOBBING)
Don't cry, kid.
We'll keep you safe. I... I promise.
The men set, Cody? What is it?
Waxer and Boil are not responding.
They never returned from scouting.
OBI-WAN: That isn't like them.
They may have run into trouble.
Sergeant,
use the high-powered transmitter
-to see if you can reach Waxer and Boil.
-Yes, sir.
Let's get the rest of the men moving.
The others will catch up.
They are on the move.
Sergeant, the attack is coming.
Release the beasts.
-It is time to execute my plan.
-Roger, roger.
(BUZZING)
(ROARING)
(COMLINK BEEPING)
It's the Commander!
We're way overdue, Waxer!
We're gonna end up polishing R2 units!
Wait! How are we gonna explain all this?
Her?
You're asking me?
Maybe if we hurry back,
we can tell him we ran into a little trouble.
BOIL: That's for sure.
And our transmissions were jammed
by the droids.
It's worth a try.
But mark my words, this will end badly.
(SPEAKING TWI'LEKI)
(GUTKURR SNARLING)
I think I know
why the kid never came back here.
(SNARLING)
You see what happens
when we don't follow orders?
(GROANS)
Let's get out here!
(ROARING)
(THUDDING)
BOIL: These suckers won't give up!
WAXER: You grab the gun,
and I'll hold them back.
(BANGING)
(SNARLING)
(ROARS)
CLONE 2: They're not stopping!
CLONE 1: Aim for their eyes!
CLONE 2: Look out, look out. Fall back!
The Republic ground troops
have been routed, Emir.
(EXPLOSION)
What was that?
I calculate the remaining clones
are attempting a desperate final offensive.
Their chances of success against us
are 742-1.
-You had better be right.
-I am a droid. I am always right.
(SNARLING)
(FIRING)
(LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
(SNARLING)
CODY: No, wait.
-Incredible.
-Quiet, rookie.
Shoot the bridge!
(SNARLING)
(RATTLING)
Don't shoot.
Waxer, Boil,
where have you two slackers been?
-Sir, there is an explanation.
-We got sidetracked.
I think I see what sidetracked you.
The clones have defeated the creatures.
Yes, but their numbers are thin.
Prepare for their final attack.
Hello, little one.
(NUMA GASPS)
She brought us here through the tunnels
and knows her way around them
pretty good, sir.
(SPEAKING TWI'LEKI)
The girl can lead us through the tunnel
to the prisoners.
Cody, we're going to need a diversion.
Yep, this is about the worst job
in the droid army.
(LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
Huh? What? And it just went into overtime.
(BUZZING)
(DROID MUMBLING)
(SPEAKS TWI'LEKI)
I'll take care of this. You keep her here.
(TWI'LEKS MURMURING)
(FOOTSTEPS CREAKING)
CODY: There they are. Let's go.
(LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
CODY: Pull back! Pull back!
(SPEAKING TWI'LEKI)
Commander, we have a problem.
The Jedi is freeing the prisoners.
(CONSOLE BEEPING)
(FIRING)
(SPEAKING TWI'LEKI)
-Waxer, Boil, come with me.
-BOIL: We're with you, sir.
(FIRING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTS)
Ready, General.
(POWERING UP)
Setting Alpha 5 or 6?
Where's the override?
(GRUNTING)
(DROID SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
Nerraa?
(TWI'LEKS CLAMORING)
(TX-20 LAUGHING EVILLY)
You lose, General Kenobi!
(TWI'LEKS CLAMORING)
TX-20: Does not compute!
Does not compute!
Does not compute! Does not...
(THUDDING)
(TWI'LEKS SHOUTING)
(TX-20 SCREAMING)
Great job getting rid of those cannons.
Now we have a more difficult objective.
We must take the capital
and free this world.
See you later, little one.
Hey, Numa, stay out of trouble.
Don't be afraid. We'll be back.
Nerraa! Nerraa!
Nerraa!
-Sir, what is that she keeps calling us?
-Nerra. It means brother.
http://hiqve.com/