A great escape!
Cad Bane and his notorious crew
of bounty hunters
liberated Ziro the Hutt
from a Republic prison
after holding the Galactic Senate hostage.
The Jedi Council has assigned
Obi-Wan Kenobi to retrieve Ziro the Hutt
with the help of Jedi Knight Quinlan Vos.
Unknown to the Jedi, we find Ziro
in the clutches of the five Hutt families
on the distant world of Na! Hutta.
Gentlemen, gentlemen,
I see no need for resentment
in light of this joyous occasion
of my freedom.
Of course I do appreciate
the help in my escape.
I have no illusions
about the fact that my escape
was a result of the highly sensitive
knowledge that I possess.
A holo-diary cataloguing
the nefarious deeds of this council.
Kill me and the diary will show up
on the step of the Senate.
The cold, hard reality is
that as long as I control
this highly sensitive material,
my memory will only get duller.
Yes, take me to my room!
I only hope
the accommodations are satisfactory.
Ah...
Sir, you seem troubled.
Quinlan Vos has that effect.
Ah... Yes, that Jedi has quite a reputation.
That may be overstating it, Cody.
Let's just say he's crazy.
Ship entry from the west, sir.
Hey, Kenobi!
Hey, Commander, looking good.
Kenobi, you look worse for wear.
How's Temple life?
Good seeing you, too.
Yes, well, if you could tell time
half as well as you can stick a landing,
we wouldn't be behind schedule now,
would we?
Well, that's your opinion, man.
Let's get down to business.
Ziro the Hutt was broken out
during a hostage takeover.
Yeah, I read the briefing about that mess.
I suspect Jabba the Hutt is behind this.
He still has it out for Ziro
over the kidnapping of his son.
Well, my information indicates that
Ziro has damaging evidence
against the Hutt Council.
My guess is they've taken him
to the Hutt home planet, Nal Hutta.
As for this bounty hunter, Cad Bane,
we must capture and return both
he and his quarry, Ziro, to the courts.
I trust you and I can keep eyes forward
in this common goal?
No problem. I owe Bane one anyway.
I'll fly, you're my co-pilot.
I was afraid he'd say that.
Sounds like that rough crowd out there
is an easy one tonight.
All in a night's work, baby.
Course, having Ziro locked up
in the detention cell block
probably isn't hurting their mood.
Ziro's here?
If you'll excuse me, I need to step outside.
Gardulla has a request.
She wants to know
which one of you is stronger.
Stop them, they're fighting!
Ziro, honey, my true love,
what happened to you?
I thought you were coming back for me.
I waited so long.
I thought you didn't love me anymore.
Our separation last time was a bit abrupt,
and I do blame Jabba for that.
Jabba?
He forced me to have you sent away
from Coruscant,