[narrator] Betrayal.
Jedi Padawan Ahsoka Tano
was wrongly accused of treason
by the Jedi Council
and hunted
by the Grand Army of the Republic.
Believing his apprentice was innocent,
Anakin Skywalker
discovered the true villain
was Ahsoka's close friend, Barriss Offee.
Unable to reconcile her relationship
with the Jedi Order,
Ahsoka decided to walk away
from the only life she had ever known.
What?
No, no, no.
Whoa!
[groans, grunts]
-Hey!
-Sorry!
-[beeping]
-[sighs]
Watch out!
[driver snorts]
[grunts]
[sighs] All right.
-[engine sputters]
-Oh, no.
Whoa!
Come on!
[grunts] Come on!
[engine whines]
[shouts, grunts]
[grunts]
[Ahsoka grunts]
What a piece of junk.
Now, how am I gonna fix this?
Oh! Bad crash. Nice roll, though.
Thanks... I guess.
That bike is trash.
I don't know what I was thinking
when I bought it.
Look at this mess.
The repulsor blew. The compressor is shot.
Sounds like you know
a thing or two about engines.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
I'm Trace.
Ahsoka.
As for your bike, you're in luck.
You happened to crash onto
one of the best repair shops on 1313.
So you're a mechanic?
That I am, and I'd be glad
to fix your bike for a price.
I can fix my own bike.
I just need some tools.
Have it your way.
But the tools are still gonna cost you.
I don't have much in the way of credits.
Don't worry. Down here, no one does.
Come on.
[beeps]
That's a Nebula-class freighter.
Or at least it was.
Good eye.
I'm turning it into something
with a bit more speed. I think.
Your space is over there.
Why don't you get that thing inside
and settle in?
Thanks.
Don't take too long. Time is money.
Hey, why are you helping me?
Shouldn't I?
Seemed like the right thing to do.
You can leave if you want.
No. It's all right.
I'll stay.
Thank you.
That's good. I really need the money.
How's it going down there? Need any help?
Not if you're gonna charge me.
Hey, I don't know where you're from,
but down here, everything has a price.
If you're gonna stick around,
you better get used to it.
Well, you might be in luck.
This engine isn't going to run
without a new sparker.
Got one I can buy?
Got bad news.
The only sparkers I got are right here.
And I ain't got no more.
That won't do. I need to get out of here.
Why? You running from something?
Maybe this was a bad idea.
I don't know what I'm doing here.
Hey! What did I say?
Look, you can stay here
as long as you like.
If you can pay me. What's with you?
[engine rattling]
[engine stops]
No sense in keeping you here
if you're gonna be miserable.
I appreciate the help.
What's it gonna cost?
It's on the house.
You know, where I come from,
it's very different from here.
Obviously.
So where do you come from anyway?
I...
um...
used to live in
the upper levels of Coruscant.
Ah, up there where the air is clear, huh?
You're probably better off down here.
Why's that?
I'm sure you have your problems up there
with the Jedi running around
starting wars, policing everything.
The Jedi didn't start the war.
They're trying to stop it.
Sure. Sure, they are.
Look, it doesn't really matter anyway.
They've forgotten all about us.
What do you mean?
It's just... when you're a kid,
you hear stories.
I guess they're not
what I thought they'd be.
It's not safe down here
or anywhere on Coruscant.
That's why I've got my ship,
so I can make my living in the stars.
Just me and my sister Rafa.
We'll get away from the Jedi,
this war, all of it.
Martez, your sister said
she was paying me today.
Where is she?
Let me handle this.
Don't do anything. Got it?
All right.
Hey, hey, Pintu.
Rafa said she was coming to see you.
Well, since she's not here,
I guess you're gonna have
to pay me instead.
I'd back off if I were you.
-Stay out of this.
Now, where's my money?
I got it. Right... here!
[grunts]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
[groans]
[gasps, groans]
[grunts]
[groans]
On second thought,
some help would be great.
Huh?
[groans]
[grunts]
[grunts, groans]
[screams]
[screams, groans]
I think you wanna leave now.
[groans]
[breathes heavily]
Tell Rafa this is far from over.
Whoa!
Where did you learn to fight like that?
My older brother taught me.
Maybe you can teach me someday.
Come on, we gotta go
tell my sister about Pintu.
Uh...
Nope.
-Meh.
-Rafa.
Rafa, does that belong to you?
Not yet.
Oh, Trace! What happened to your face?
Pintu came by to get paid.
You weren't there.
You plan on paying him?
I am.
I got a big job coming through
that'll make everything good for us.
Is it legitimate this time
or the usual job?
Hey, what did I teach you?
We can't count on anyone--
So we count on ourselves. I know.
That's right. That's how we survive.
Who is this interesting creature?
My name is Ahsoka.
Lovely name, Ahsoka.
Ahsoka, this is my sister, Rafa Martez.
How'd you end up with this moof-milker?
She fell from the sky. I mean, really.
Dropped right in on the mech bay platform.
Where exactly are you from?
I'm from Topside.
Your sister's been helping me out.
Really? [scoffs]
How much is she charging you?
Not enough to pay your debt.
Not that it's any of your business,
but I am sorry about that, Trace.
You promised
you would stay away from Pintu.
I needed money for this place,
for repairs and other things.
You could have at least
given me a heads-up
that you weren't gonna pay him.
You're right. Won't happen again.
Good. I can only take
so many punches to my head
and still be considered a pilot.
Here's our next payday.
How can I help you, my friend?
I've got three droids
that need to be built.
My business partner
brokered a deal with a...
a Rafa Martez.
You're looking at her.
And that deal will be honored.
This may not look like a droid factory,
but that's to throw off the authorities.
My associate does assembly in the back.
Who's your associate?
Don't worry about that yet.
My, uh, business partner,
he said you build droids
better than anybody.
Then they know quality.
Look, just bring them 'round back.
So, Trace, feel like building some droids?
It's been a while since I built a droid.
But it's not too difficult,
just more moving parts.
Just make sure
you affix the restraining bolt
to that pile of moving parts
before you punch the power cycle.
Got one right here.
What's your worry?
I've had my fair share
of run-ins with droids.
The majority are fine,
but some are just cross-wired
from the start.
And this is no astromech.
[droid beeps]
[grunts]
You seem to know a lot about everything.
Not everything.
I still don't understand people.
What's to know?
There are good people and bad people,
and some are just cross-wired
like this binary load lifter.
Binary load lifter.
Wait a minute.
I do know this type of droid.
[grunts]
[beeps]
[droid powers off]
Are you all right?
Type two load lifters were a fraud.
They were repurposed demolition droids
prone to violence.
Naturally.
Well, good thing
we put the restraining bolts on.
-[droid beeps]
-Trace, the bolt.
[grunts]
[cats meow, hiss]
What the...
No. That-- That's not...
No, no. No, no.
Trace, that's my droid. Where's it going?
It's a test run. Nothing to worry about.
This isn't funny, Trace!
[Trace shrieks]
-[screams]
-Stop!
-[grunts, beeps]
-[screams]
-[gasps]
You said demolition droid, right?
Yeah.
Go back to Rafa's and get
the tracking device for that droid.
What are you gonna do?
Find a speeder and meet you there.
Where's the droid?
Working on it.
Where's Trace?
Gotta go.
Trace, I trusted you.
We're going to owe more credits
than we were paid for this thing!
Stop. Stop. It's really close.
Where? Do you see it?
Yeah. It's headed straight for us.
[screams]
-[screams]
-[pedestrian] Hey!
The off switch, it's on its face plate.
Okay. But let me grab it first.
Got it!
[groans]
See? Nothing to it.
[Trace] Oh, no. This was a bad idea.
Yeah, that happens.
I gotta cut it loose.
[computer beeps]
-We can't let it get away.
-Take the controls!
Just hit the blue button!
[beeps]
[grunts]
Come on. Come on!
[droid beeps]
Hey, kid.
Oh, no. Oh, no, no, no, no, no! Ah!
-Come on, you got it.
-There you go, all good!
Bad. Bad.
Look there. Look, they have it.
Trace?
See? Nothing to worry about.
We had it all under control.
I am not going to dismantle those droids.
A deal is a deal.
They could hurt someone.
Honestly, not my problem.
You don't know
what those droids could be used for.
They're dangerous.
One tore apart the sector.
Without a restraining bolt.
Trace, did you put the bolt on all three?
Yeah, but what if one comes off?
Why is this a discussion? We all know--
That you're new here.
Trace, I'll do the right thing.
I'll meet you at the wharf, okay?
Rafa, just be smart.
Come on, Ahsoka.
[driver] Wahoo!
[soft music playing]
[cat meows, purrs]
Do you ever get a say with Rafa?
She's my older sister.
She doesn't always get it right,
but I know she's trying
to make things better for us.
At what cost?
Did you tell that guy about the droids?
Actually, I charged the Twi'lek double.
You gave them back.
You said be smart.
Look, they weren't mine to keep.
We don't build them, somebody else would.
I don't give them back,
that's more trouble
for the Martez sisters.
Rafa.
I used the credits to pay off Pintu.
If I didn't get the credits
for those droids,
they were gonna keep coming after us.
Here's enough to buy new tools.
That makes it worth it, right?
I guess so.
Stick with me, Trace.
One day, we'll have enough credits,
Pintu will be coming to us for work.
[music continues]
I'd better go finish my speeder.
You're not sticking around?
I think it's for the best.
Hey.
Thanks for saving me out there.
You're welcome.
Now, let's get that speeder working.
Come on.