NARRATOR". Conflict with no end in sight!
Across the galaxy,
the quagmire of war continues.
While clone troopers suffer casualties
at alarming rates,
the Galactic Senate
convenes an emergency session
to debate the true cost of the war.
Order! Order! Let Senator Saam finish.
This is a matter not of philosophy.
More troops are needed.
The Republic cannot afford to let
the Separatists gain any more ground.
Our generals inform us that troops
in the field continue to perform valiantly.
What we cannot afford
is to be irresponsible.
The Republic is near bankruptcy
due to the cost of this war.
Bankruptcy is not necessary, my friends.
If we pass Senator Saam's bill
to open new lines of credit,
we will gain access to the needed funds.
Won't this bill essentially
deregulate the banks?
A small price to pay to finance the war,
is it not?
-Keep the war going!
Members of the Senate,
do you hear yourselves?
More money. More clones.
More war.
Say nothing of fiscal responsibility,
what about moral responsibility?
Hasn't this war gone on long enough?
Senator Amidala, are you suggesting
we surrender to the Separatists?
Of course not. But negotiation
might be a better course of action.
You can't negotiate with those animals!
Keep the war going! Vote now!
Members of the Senate,
I suggest we table any emergency bill
until it is determined
whether or not deregulation
is the right course of action.
Very well.
We shall let calmer heads prevail.
That legislation would have meant
billions for us.
I tried my best to push the bill through.
You did your part, Representative.
Senator Amidala is the problem.
I thought age might temper her idealism.
I know people
who could do something about her.
That task is more difficult
than you presume.
Gentlemen, the Banking Clan
and Trade Federation
are about business, not violence.
Hmm. In this case, our business is violence.
Precisely.
With or without Senator Amidala,
the Galactic Senate is unlikely
to deregulate the banks
until this war hits home.
What exactly are you proposing?
Perhaps some unexpected bloodshed
on Coruscant may change a few minds.
Coruscant? Coruscant has not been
attacked in over 1,000 years.
Then it has a false sense of security.
There are some powerful clients
on the other side who could help us,
shall we say, make the point.
I like this plan.
No one cares what you think.
You must ask the Jedi Council
to speak with Chancellor Palpatine.
Don't involve me in this.
A peaceful solution
is the only way out of this morass of war.
That's not my role, Padmé.
Why not? Why isn't it your role?
Aren't we Jedi Knights?
Isn't it our duty to speak our minds
to advise the Chancellor?
Uh...
I'd suggest you teach my young Padawan
a thing or two about politics.
After today's debate, I was hoping
she learned a great deal.
Truthfully? I don't understand any of it.
I know the Separatists are evil,
but all anyone argued about
was banking deregulation,
interest rates and, well,
almost nothing about why
we're fighting in the first place.
War's complicated, Ahsoka,
but let me simplify it.
The Separatists
believe the Republic is corrupt,
but they're wrong,
and we have to restore order.
Maybe talking to the Jedi Council
isn't the role for you, after all.
Thanks for your help. Come on, Ahsoka.
Hey-
You told me to teach her
about politics.
So I'm going to.
There is a problematic situation
brewing in the Senate.
We must ensure that everything
my master has set in motion
does not unhinge.
My representatives in the Republic
are relying on you, General.
See that your droids
complete their mission.
But, of course, Count. They will not fail.
If only I could talk
to Senator Bonteri.
-Who's he?
-He is a she.
A senator in the Confederacy
of Independent Systems.
Your friend is a Separatist?
One of Dooku's pawns?
The Separatists used to be a part
of the Republic.
I was close
with many of the senators who left.
I may not agree with them,
but they're more than pawns.
If you think negotiating
is the right thing to do, let's talk to her.
The Senate's made it illegal.
Illegal?
They say official meetings would
only legitimize the Separatists.
Well, Master Skywalker and I hold
what we call "aggressive negotiations"
all the time.
It's a shame you can't hold
more peaceful talks when you want.
You just gave me an idea.
You're a Jedi,
which gives you special clearance.
Right.
And Jedi are allowed to travel
to neutral worlds, like Mandalore,
where we could then board a cargo ship
to a Separatist system.
Are you suggesting
I use my status as a Jedi
to smuggle you behind enemy lines?
It's just that you could get us
through to meet with her,
and I haven't seen her,
or her family, in so long.
Relax, I'll help you.
Besides, Master Skywalker said
you should teach me about politics.
Right.
You know, you two have more in
common than you think.
It's no wonder you get along so well.
Huh. Of course.
-So, where are we heading?
-Raxus.
Have all the preparations
been made?
I am about to deploy the infiltrators.
You must hurry, the Senate is restless.
I don't take orders from you,
only Count Dooku.
You have been designed for this mission
to be the ultimate infiltration units.
Some of you may not return.
Actually, none of you will return.
But don't let that get in your way.
ls that clear?
Get them to Coruscant.
Roger, roger.
Move along, please, move along.
Identification, please.
Excuse me, is this Platform B?
-Platform B is the next one, ma'am.
-This way.
Oh, thank you.
Hello, old friend.
Ahsoka, this is Mina Bonteri.
She was my mentor
when I was growing up on Naboo.
You're a Separatist?
Well, of course, my dear.
What were you expecting?
Now, come, I have a transport waiting.
Lux, come down here and help
our guests with their luggage, please.
Padmé, it's so good to see you.
Yes, how things have changed
since the last time we met.
Let's go inside. There's much to discuss.
Please, allow me.
-May I?
-I can handle it.
He's grown so much, Mina.
Time won't stop, even if we are at war,
and I'm afraid these events
are shaping his young life.
With all due respect, as a Separatist,
didn't you create this war?
- Ahsoka!
-It's all right.
That's a very polarized point of view,
my dear.
Would it surprise you to know that
many of the people you call Separatists
feel the same way about the Republic?
And the Jedi?
Lux's father was like that.
Maybe I could speak with him.
If only you could.
A year ago next week.
He was setting up a base on Aargonar
when clones attacked.
My husband fought bravely in self-defense,
but was killed.
Excuse me, I think I'll get some air.
Ah, the cleaning droids. Finally!
Don't waste any time, get to work!
You're a Jedi, aren't you?
Yes, why do you ask?
Before the war,
I was always told Jedi were good.
And now?
I don't know anymore.
There are a lot
of terrible things happening.
A lot of killing. And now my friends
are saying the Jedi are to blame.
I'm the first Jedi you've ever met,
aren't l?
Well...
Yes.
Look at me. I'm not so bad, am I?
No, not bad at all.
Well, it seems boys are the same
whether they're Republic or Separatist.
Wait!
How many Separatists have you met?
What?
Well, I mean, you think we're all
the bad guys,
but how many of us
have you actually met?
And droids don't count.
Well, other than military officers,
like Grievous and Ventress, none, I guess.
You and your mother are the first.
Well, look at me. Am I so bad?
I sense Dooku's dirty hand in all of this.
He's just the leader of the Senate.
He's not the leader of the entire universe.
Oh, I forgot. You actually admire the man.
We'll never entirely agree on Dooku,
my old friend.
But we can agree on the need
to stop this war, the question is how.
That is why it was so urgent
that I speak with you.
The Republic Senate
is holding a critical vote
on whether or not to escalate
the war effort.
However, many of the delegates
are undecided as to what to do.
How interesting.
You would find the Separatist Parliament
in a similar dilemma.
I am certain if you could convince
your representatives
to extend an olive branch of peace
towards the Republic,
there might be enough sympathy
in the Senate to finally open negotiations.
I admire your spirit, Padmé.
I can at least put the motion on the floor.
Thank you, Mina, that's all I ask.
To peace, then.
To hope.
How many lives on both sides
have to end before we see the futility?
Surely there's room in the galaxy
for Confederate and Republic planets
to coexist.
I move that we immediately open
peace negotiations
with Chancellor Palpatine on Coruscant.
The Corporate Alliance
will never allow this to happen.
This is a democracy,
and unlike the Republic,
corporations do not rule us.
- Nay!
-Quiet!
In accordance with the bylaws
of Independent Systems,
a voice vote is required.
AH in favor of initiating peace negotiations
with the Galactic Republic, say aye.
Aye !
-Aye !
All those opposed?
Nay!
The ayes have it.
This is quite troubling.
Your own Senate voting to end the war?
I assure you, gentlemen,
your worries are gravely exaggerated.
How can you be sure
this groundswell of peace won't continue?
Where is the attack we were promised?
We need fighting to feed the machine
and our profits.
After our attack,
the chances of peace will disappear.
The Banking Clan, the Trade Federation,
and the Techno Union
will all get their fair share and then some.
Well, this is goodbye.
I've been disappointed before,
and yet I almost feel as if, this time,
the tide has turned in the war.
You should hurry.
Goodbye, young one.
You really believe the Republic
will vote for peace?
I hope so. I wouldn't want to meet you
on the battlefield.
For your sake.
Go, you two. Quickly.
Team leaders, come in.
Commence Phase 2.
Proceed with high-security infiltration.
All right, everybody have your passes out.
Hmm. Generator maintenance, eh?
Hmm.
Well, everything checks out,
good luck down there.
Whoa! Wait a minute!
Power generators are that way.
Stupid droids.
Well, well, well.
This is quite a stunning development.
Your Excellency, we would be remiss,
if not irresponsible,
-to reject the Separatists' proposal.
-Of course.
An end to the fighting
would mean there's no need
to borrow money for more clones.
I can see why
you would want so badly to believe
that the Separatists desire peace.
I don't understand.
In the past, whenever we've reached out
our hands in peace,
they've been slapped away.
Can we believe that they're ready to sue
for peace so easily?
If I might speak with you confidentially.
I know that this is sincere.
I've been in contact
with my old friend Mina Bonteri,
and the origin of the proposal is with her.
Bonteri?
How was the dialogue established?
Does it matter, Chancellor,
if the result is an end to the war?
I see your point, my child.
Then, we shall put the vote to the floor.
Sweeper droids?
We didn't schedule a cleaning.
What's going on?
Given that the Separatists have
put a call for negotiations on the table,
the need for additional troops
seems ill-timed.
Which means there is no need
to deregulate the banks.
I say we vote that down now.
There is a move to vote
on the proposed bill
to lift regulations on the Banking Clan.
Dooku promised he would stop this vote!
You may enter your votes.
We're under attack!
The bombing of the power generator
has been confirmed as a Separatist attack.
They must pay for what they have done.
But it was the Separatist Congress
that issued the bill of peace.
Obviously a tactic to lower our defenses
and launch this attack.
No! That's not true!
I move to immediately
deregulate the banks.
We need a bank loan
to get more troops now!
What are we waiting for?
I'm afraid we've been given little choice.
To ensure the safety of the Republic,
we must deregulate the banks.
I'm returning your Padawan.
I'm sorry your talks with Bonteri failed.
How did you know?
We have eyes and ears
everywhere, Ahsoka.
That was dangerous and careless
going to Raxus.
Not to mention illegal.
You went too far this time.
You would do the same.
You do the same all the time.
This was too much.
Maybe so, but I did realize something,
the politics of this war
are not as black and white
as I once thought they were.
English - SDH