h
ht
htt
http
http:
http:/
http://
http://h
http://hi
http://hiq
http://hiqv
http://hiqve
http://hiqve.
http://hiqve.c
http://hiqve.co
http://hiqve.com
http://hiqve.com/
As the war between the Republic
and the Separatists intensifies,
many are driven
from their home planets,
and it is up to Senator Amidala
to secure aid for them.
All eyes turn to the Banking Clan
and the planet Scipio.
In an effort to remain independent
from the Republic and the Separatists,
all operations are divided
and money transactions
are performed in a neutral zone
surrounding the main vault.
For operations to continue,
there must be no war on Scipio.
However, worry about the stability
of the Banking Clan
is brewing within the Republic
as the wellspring of money
may be in jeopardy.
Welcome to Scipio, Senator.
If you will follow me,
we will be traveling
into the neutral zone.
I am afraid your guards
will have to wait outside.
Of course.
As Council of Five,
we are honored but surprised
that you have traveled all this way
for a mere bank transfer.
A transfer that has
not been forthcoming.
By request of the Supreme Chancellor,
I am here to expedite matters.
Of course.
We would merely request that you
meet with our special representative
who will go over the terms
and conditions of your loan.
Senator Amidala.
Clovis.
You two know one another?
Sir, I was assured
that this transaction would be free
of prejudice and partisan allegiance.
This man is a known Separatist
and traitor to the Republic.
-Padmé...
-I can assure you
Rush Clovis is our most trusted
and best negotiator.
I am sorry, gentlemen.
But I insist that this man be removed
from these negotiations.
Until then, we have nothing further
to discuss.
Milady no longer requires
your assistance this evening.
Thank you.
Milady, watch out!
I would stop right there if I were you.
How did you get a blaster
into the neutral zone?
We're resourceful.
Now, why are you breaking in
to my quarters?
Padmé, you don't understand
what is going on here.
I need your help.
Last time you needed my help,
I ended up poisoned,
and you did nothing.
That's not true.
You stole data files from me.
That revealed the location
of a Separatists' droid factory
sponsored by you!
Look, it's not safe. We can't talk here.
Senator, I really don't think...
It's all right.
I want to hear what he has to say.
The simple fact is the economics
of this war are not adding up.
You're here for a bank transfer,
but I can assure you
there is no money in the bank.
That's absurd.
They were ready
to give me the funds today.
They will give you
your first installment, yes.
But they're robbing one side
to save the other.
The entire Banking Clan
is on the verge of collapse.
Collapse? Where is the evidence?
In the vault.
The accounts are sealed there,
and no one is allowed to see them
besides the Core Five.
Convenient.
Well, now that you're here,
you must put pressure on them.
And do what exactly?
Help me gain access to the vault.
You're insane to think
I would ever trust you.
I'm sorry, but I cannot help you.
Take your hands off me!
I've risked everything to tell you this.
Don't you see they're trying to kill me
because of what I know?
Please believe me.
Our past must count for something.
I can't stay here. Think about what I ask.
If what you are saying is true,
then this information Clovis is offering
is vital to our security.
I need you to be very clear
in this matter for the Republic.
Is he telling the truth?
Yes. I'm sure.
Perhaps then, in this scenario,
it would be best for you
to trust an old friend
and do what he suggests.
I have decided to accept Clovis
as the representative of this transaction
as long as I can go into the vault
and accompany the funds
throughout the entire process.
No outsider
is ever allowed into the vaults.
I come with the authority
of the Supreme Chancellor.
If you have something to hide,
then that is something
we should discuss.
Hide?
I think considering
last night's attack on the Senator,
it is only fair that we are transparent
and agree to these terms.
What harm will come of it?
The vault will be open
first thing in the morning.
Please make sure
you are here, Senator.
Where exactly are we, Clovis?
This is my personal residence.
A bit remote,
but we'll have more privacy here.
Once I detonate the charge here
at the main power source,
the vault will go
into immediate shutdown.
No one will get in or out.
This will give you very little time
before the emergency generator cycles
and takes over.
You'll then use this
to locate the exact files
and download them
from the mainframe.
The vault is one
of the most secure in the galaxy.
But it was designed to keep people out.
Once you're inside,
and the power is down,
there is little they can do.
You make it sound so easy.
If you don't mind, Senator,
I will retire for the night.
Of course, Teckla.
The information we get tomorrow
will go a long way
to expose, perhaps,
the real criminals behind this war.
These are war profiteers.
I've exposed that before.
Nobody cares.
Truth is not on the battlefield.
It's late.
Good night, Clovis.
Clovis, where are you going?
I have some business to attend to.
This was your idea.
I should very much like for you
to await the Senator's return.
If you'll follow me,
the credits for the Republic
are in this section.
What happened to the lights?
I can't see a thing!
Find out what is going on,
and open the vault immediately.
Power has been cut,
and the security lock has engaged.
It will take some time to switch over.
-Where is the Senator?
-We got separated in the darkness.
I'm here.
No thanks to your security system.
This isn't a vault. It's a tomb.
What is going on?
My deepest apologies, Senator.
It seems I'm witness
to many firsts on Scipio.
Is this an unfortunate incident
or a cover up?
I'm not sure what you mean.
I'm afraid I'm going to have to report
on your sad state of affairs
to the Chancellor.
Let's see if you got what we needed.
As I said, the vaults are empty.
The Chancellor
must see this immediately.
Senator Amidala,
you are under arrest for espionage.
No, there's been some kind of mistake.
Take her away.
I have powerful friends.
The Chancellor will hear about this.
This way, Master Jedi.
Well, well, well.
What exactly is going on here?
Ani. I'm so glad to see you.
I guess I'm not only useful
for fighting wars after all.
-How long have I been in here?
-A few days.
They say Teckla is dead. Is it true?
Yes. She was found shot
at the bombsite.
-By who?
-They don't know.
The Muuns say
she sabotaged the power grid.
What exactly is going on here?
You have to get me out of here.
-Clovis is...
-Clovis?
What exactly does Clovis
have to do with this?
I can't explain it here.
How could you ever put your trust
in a man like Clovis after what he did?
It's for the Republic, Anakin.
Something is very wrong
with the banks.
Why is it that when Clovis is around,
your excuse is always that
you're doing it for the Republic?
Anakin, please.
You know, maybe
I'll just leave you here.
Ani.
You've already been released
into my custody.
You better come with me
before I change my mind.
Anakin, please trust me.
I can't leave without the files
Clovis and I took from the vault.
Where exactly do you suggest we look?
The disks may be outside the city
at Clovis' private residence.
Fine. I'll do this for you,
not for Clovis. Artoo.
Have the ship ready in case I need you.
Over there.
Cozy place.
Someone was looking for the files.
They must know Clovis has them.
Well, maybe they found
what they were looking for,
and that's why he's missing.
We can only hope.
Anakin, you're not helping things.
You don't seem to understand
how important these files are.
They'll expose a corruption that goes
to the very core of the Banking Clan.
Clovis!
Padmé.
I knew you'd come.
You again?
Yes, me again.
All right, lover boy, where's the disk?
I'm not about to hand over
the information to some pilot.
I'm a Jedi Knight who can save your life
if you hand over the files!
So, what's it going to be?
You gonna give us the disk?
Why? So you can leave me stranded
like last time?
Well, that depends on
how well-behaved you are.
Can you both stop bickering
so we can get out of here?
Down!
Thanks.
It wasn't you I wanted to save.
Anakin, get us out of here.
Follow me!
Run for it!
Artoo, bring the ship around
and pick us up.
Look out!
Anakin!
Did we lose him?
I'm all right.
Artoo, hone in on my signal. Artoo?
Hey, nice catch.
It seems your mission was a success,
bounty hunter.
From this point,
I will deal with them myself.
http://hiqve.com/