Captured!
Returning from a perilous assignment
in the Outer Rim,
Jedi Master Even Piel|'s cruiser
has fallen under attack and been boarded.
Seeking vital information he carries
about secret hyperspace lanes
called the Nexus Route,
Separatist forces have taken him alive.
Now, the Jedi are preparing
a stealth mission
into the heart of Separatist space
in an effort to rescue Master Piell
from the deadly prison
known as the Citadel.
As you are aware,
the Citadel is their most isolated
and impenetrable detention facility.
No one has ever escaped.
There's a first time for everything.
Indeed there is.
Their security has prevented our probes
from obtaining recent reconnaissance,
so we've been forced
to construct a crude map
based upon data from the archives.
And since the data is extremely old,
the map will be difficult to rely on.
So we're essentially going in blind.
Beg your pardon, General,
but how do we know
Master Piell is still alive?
The Separatists won't dare kill Master Piell
until they have what they need.
He obtained the coordinates
of a secret hyperspace lane
known as the Nexus Route
which travels into the heart of both
the Republic and Separatist homeworlds.
They could prove vital
in maneuvering our forces
deep into remote Separatist sectors.
Or the enemy could use them
to slip through our defenses
and attack Coruscant.
These hyperspace lanes are of
immense interest to both our sides,
and could tip the scale of the war
to whomever is in possession of them.
That is all.
Based on the archive schematics,
we've narrowed it down
to three possible locations
they could be holding him at.
My greatest concern is infiltrating
their outer security.
The life-form scanners
will not be easy to fool.
I've got a thought about that.
Master! I'm sorry I'm late.
I just heard about the briefing.
We're going to rescue Master Piell, right?
You two have much to discuss.
Ahsoka, I'm sorry I didn't tell you earlier,
but you won't be coming along on this one.
Not coming?
But you're breaking into the Citadel!
No one's ever done it.
The Citadel wasn't designed
to hold common criminals.
It was created to hold Jedi
if any of us lost our way.
It's not a place for Padawans.
You're just being protective again.
That's not fair. How am I supposed to learn
if you won't let me share the risk?
This isn't a mission for learning.
You either do or die.
And that's not a risk I'm willing to share.
Artoo! Look out! Behind you!
You're being followed by battle droids!
These are your troops?
They're battle droids!
What do you mean, they've been
reprogrammed to follow your orders?
We are awaiting your word, Commander.
You heard him. Move out!
Don't you go thumbing your gears at me
just because you have a bunch of
dim-witted droids following you about!
Really.
We're trusting those droids
to get us into the Citadel?
It's the only way. We're flying right
into the heart of Separatist territory.
Droids won't be detected.
Artoo.
Make sure they don't stray
from the flight plan.
It's all under control, sir.
I was talking to Artoo.
Master Plo? May I speak with you?
What is it, little ‘Soka?
It's about the mission.
Master Skywalker doesn't want me to go.
That is his choice.
I know.
But I think he's being overly protective.
He's picking and choosing
which assignments I can be a part of.
He is your master.
Yes, but it's not for him to decide
when and how
I should put my life in danger.
That should be my choice.
I've never been carbon-frozen
before, General.
It's the first time for us, too.
This is your idea? Carbon freezing?
Hey, you wanted to shield us
from the life-form scanners.
Are we sure this thing is safe?
I don't want to end up a wall decoration.
Try to relax.
We'll be unfrozen as soon as we arrive.
May the Force be with you.
Citadel Command has contacted us.
This is Central Command.
Please identify yourself.
This is cargo shuttle 1138,
requesting access to Citadel prison.
Make sure every part of that ship
is scanned for life forms.
Yes, Commander.
Make no mistake. The Jedi will be
coming for their imprisoned brother.
They're not about to let
one of their own be tortured
into handing over information that will
help the Separatists win the war.
What is your cargo?
What is our cargo?
Supplies and frozen rations.
Do not deviate from your current course
until we have confirmed your cargo.
They're scanning us for life forms.
I don't think this is working.
Quiet! You're gonna blow it.
The shuttle has no life forms, Commander.
Scan complete. You may proceed.
Fear. A Jedi spends his whole life
training against it.
But at the Citadel,
breaking Jedi is our specialty.
Within these walls,
they will learn to fear us.
And if not, they die.
-Hey, Snips.
-Hey, Master.
I must have carbon sickness,
because I could swear that's Ahsoka.
Your eyes are fine.
It's Ahsoka's hearing that needs help.
I received orders to join the team.
I thought you knew.
Orders? From who?
I discussed it with Master Plo.
He didn't tell me.
You were already in carbonite.
Well, I gave you a specific order
not to come!
If there's one thing I've learned
from you, Master,
it's that following direct orders isn't
always the best way to solve a problem.
I see Anakin's new teaching method
is to "Do as I say, not as I do."
Welcome aboard.
Guard the shuttle, Artoo.
We'll contact you
when we're ready for take-off.
- I see the entry point.
- You were right.
The wind conditions are too strong
for jetpacks.
Yes. We'll have to do it
the old-fashioned way,
with ascension cables and a steel grip.
-I don't think so.
-What do you mean?
Electra-mines.
There's nowhere to put a grappling hook
at that height,
and we hit one of those, the mission's over.
They'll know we're here.
I suppose that means we free-climb it.
You hanging in there, Snips?
Couldn't be better.
I could do without the wind, though.
The entry point is just a few more meters.
They locked the door! It's ray-shielded!
Ray-shielded? That wasn't the plan!
Well, it's in the plan now.
There's an opening up there.
We know. They're ventilation ducts.
But they're far too small
for us to gain access.
Too small for you, maybe,
but I think I can squeeze through.
Well, we hadn't planned
on Ahsoka being here. Perhaps she's right.
See? I can handle myself after all.
Sir, one of the cargo shuttles was
cleared for landing but never arrived.
Charger!
Well, they know we're here.
Sir, a mine in sector 9-G was
just detonated.
Mindless droids!
Activate all security protocols!
Lock everything down!
Where are my special units?
They are here, sir.
Clear.
Take out their surveillance.
The walls are electrified. Go! Go, go, go!
Longshoﬂ
We must keep moving.
You're weakening.
You decide when the pain will stop.
Just give me the information.
No droid will ever break me.
Say goodbye to your one good eye.
Secure the entrance!
Master Piell, are you all right?
Obi-Wan. What took you guys so long?
At least your sense of humor is still intact.
It takes more than they got to break me,
young Skywalker.
So you have the coordinates
for the Nexus Route?
I got them, all right.
Half of them, anyway.
My captain's got the other half.
I erased the computers
when we were boarded
and had both of us memorize
part of the intel.
That way, if somehow I cracked,
the information would be useless to them
without the other half.
Where's your captain?
Being held with the other officers,
I assume.
We're gonna need a new plan
for getting out.
We need to keep moving.
Anakin!
Master!
You fools! I hope you enjoyed
the reunion with your fellow Jedi,
because you're going to be my guests
for a very long time!
They're magnetized.
Oh, no, you don't.
- Are you all right, sir?
- Yeah. Let's get out of here.
I hear something.
General.
Captain Tarkin.
I never thought I'd see you again.
And you brought friends.
Tarkin, this is Obi-Wan Kenobi
and Anakin Skywalker.
Well, now that you've found us,
how do you expect to get us out?
If they've locked this fortress down,
there's at least ten squads on their way.
It's going to be impossible to escape.
What if we split up?
My team will create a diversion,
while Anakin leads the others away.
That way, if one of us is captured,
the enemy will only have part
of the information and not all of it.
General Kenobi, I think it's better
if we stick together.
A stronger force
would have a better chance
-of protecting the information.
-Not in this situation.
But surely we'd have more strength
in numbers, rather than divide us.
Obi-Wan has a point. I'll go with him,
you go with Skywalker.
They escaped, sir.
Captain, show this droid what happens
when we use that word.
Sir! They've been spotted
heading for the upper levels.
They're trying to steal a transport.
Seal the landing platform
and send all battalions to their positions.
Bring them back alive.
Hey!
Everybody in.
This is one of the original fortress tunnels.
The advantage of old archive data.
The tunnel's clear!
Looks like Obi-Wan's distraction worked.
Things seem to be going as planned.
It's when things do not go as planned
that concerns me.
- What then?
-it's when things don't go as planned
that we Jedi are at our best. Trust me.
I reserve my trust for those
who take action, General Skywalker.
Then let me remind you,
we rescued you back there.
And I reserve my trust
for those who understand gratitude,
Captain Tarkin.
English - SDH